[
  {
    "Question": "When stereotypes and prejudice are put into action, the result is?",
    "A": "unconscious bias.",
    "B": "racism.",
    "C": "bias.",
    "D": "discrimination.",
    "answer": "D: discrimination.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Even when things are not going well for Mark, he still believes everything will work out al l right. Mark has a(n) __________ attitude.",
    "A": "positive",
    "B": "indifferent",
    "C": "superior",
    "D": "negative",
    "answer": "A: positive",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ben and Tasha are coworkers who are applying for the same supervisory position in the company and now they are NOT speaking to each other. The reason for the conflict is",
    "A": "exclusion.",
    "B": "unclear boundaries.",
    "C": "authority.",
    "D": "unclear expectations.",
    "answer": "C: authority.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ethical employees are responsible workers who can be counted on to",
    "A": "do whatever it takes to get ahead.",
    "B": "complete the tasks they start.",
    "C": "copy the actions of celebrities.",
    "D": "discuss personal issues with coworkers.",
    "answer": "B: complete the tasks they start.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is important to do when giving verbal directions to make sure the audience understands?",
    "A": "Maintain eye contact",
    "B": "Ask questions",
    "C": "Use gestures",
    "D": "Explain information",
    "answer": "B: Ask questions",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one of the main reasons why small businesses are strongly promoted and supported by local government?",
    "A": "They are important to the economy.",
    "B": "They serve only their local communities.",
    "C": "They may become a big business.",
    "D": "They are owned by one person.",
    "answer": "A: They are important to the economy.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Managers often ask their employees to help orient new workers. One advantage to involvi ng veteran staff members in the orientation process is that",
    "A": "veteran staff members are more likely to require new hires to develop performance goals.",
    "B": "veteran staff members are more knowledgeable about compensation than their managers.",
    "C": "new hires often have questions that they feel uncomfortable asking their managers.",
    "D": "managers don't have to meet with new hires if veteran staff members orient them.",
    "answer": "C: new hires often have questions that they feel uncomfortable asking their managers.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When an employee searches online using a keyword and obtains 578 responses, the next logical step would be to?",
    "A": "start from #578 and work backwards until the best one is found.",
    "B": "use more words for descriptors or a more precise keyword.",
    "C": "open all 578 responses looking for the best one.",
    "D": "go to another search engine and see if it works better.",
    "answer": "B: use more words for descriptors or a more precise keyword.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "By developing a brand promise, a company can",
    "A": "ensure that all of its products will meet customers' expectations.",
    "B": "communicate its commitment to meeting customers' expectations.",
    "C": "obtain a trademark from the government.",
    "D": "establish a licensing agreement with the government.",
    "answer": "B: communicate its commitment to meeting customers' expectations.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a characteristic common to all integrated software packages:?",
    "A": "Performs interrelated functions",
    "B": "Calculates break-even points",
    "C": "Includes forecasting tools",
    "D": "Requires minimal training",
    "answer": "A: Performs interrelated functions",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way money functions in society is that it helps people communicate a product's",
    "A": "attributes.",
    "B": "income.",
    "C": "market.",
    "D": "value.",
    "answer": "D: value.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The most efficient way to obtain the current interest rates on certificates of deposit purchased through Main Street Community Bank is to",
    "A": "visit the bank's website.",
    "B": "go to the bank to get a product brochure.",
    "C": "make an appointment with a bank teller.",
    "D": "call the bank's financial officer.",
    "answer": "A: visit the bank's website.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Students at a local high school must now pay to participate in the sports program because the school levy failed. This situation is the result of what type of change?",
    "A": "Governmental",
    "B": "Personal",
    "C": "Social",
    "D": "Technological",
    "answer": "A: Governmental",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mr. Martin said, \"I want to return this software and get my money back. Before I bought it, your salesperson told me that it was compatible with my computer, but i t isn't.\" What is the reason for Mr. Martin's complaint?",
    "A": "The salesperson used high-pressure sales tactics.",
    "B": "The product was defective.",
    "C": "The salesperson provided inaccurate information.",
    "D": "The product was labeled incorrectly.",
    "answer": "C: The salesperson provided inaccurate information.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Paper money like the U.S. dollar, the euro, and the Indian rupee is also called",
    "A": "discretionary income.",
    "B": "fiat money.",
    "C": "commodity money.",
    "D": "fiduciary wealth.",
    "answer": "B: fiat money.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To have a high tolerance for ambiguity, what must individuals l earn to accept?",
    "A": "Risk is always rewarded. C. Contingency plans are unnecessary.",
    "B": "Failure is not an option. D. Outcomes are often uncertain. 39. Which step in the process of maintaining a positive attitude includes \"thought stopping\"? A. Think pos itively",
    "C": "Have a sense of humor B. Surround yourself with positive people",
    "D": "Act positively",
    "answer": "D: Act positively",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your daily personal grooming habits directly impact your personal",
    "A": "hygiene.",
    "B": "relaxation.",
    "C": "skills.",
    "D": "education.",
    "answer": "A: hygiene.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a question you should ask yourself to determine whether y ou're facing a problem or a true ethical dilemma:?",
    "A": "Is money at stake?",
    "B": "Could someone be unhappy?",
    "C": "Is there an easy or hard choice?",
    "D": "Could someone be hurt?",
    "answer": "D: Could someone be hurt?",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When determining if a personal vision is realistic, a person must determine if the vision will have?",
    "A": "measurable goals. C. few setbacks.",
    "B": "limited resources. D. permanent results. 45. Inspired people are generally A. more open to new experiences.",
    "C": "more extrinsically motivated. B. less absorbed in their work.",
    "D": "less satisfied with their life.",
    "answer": "D: less satisfied with their life.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one of the qualities of a good telephone voice?",
    "A": "Varying tone C. Monotone",
    "B": "Stern control D. Decisiveness 10. One way to effectively contribute to a group discussion when you don't know much about the topic being discussed is to A. ask questions to clarify what someone else is saying. B. bring up a different topic that you know more about.",
    "C": "let the more informed group members handle the conversation.",
    "D": "quickly form an opinion to share with the group.",
    "answer": "A: Varying tone C. Monotone",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an important consideration when selecting graphics and posting them on a business's website?",
    "A": "Log files C. Descriptive links",
    "B": "Font size D. Download time 79. Tim works for a manufacturer that produces food items. He manages the flow of products from production to consumption. He decides where and how to store the products as well as how and when to transport them to customers. In which part of operations does Tim work? A. Quality assurance",
    "C": "Quality inspection B. Scheduling",
    "D": "Logistics",
    "answer": "D: Logistics",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an effect of automatically paying bills online:?",
    "A": "Bank accounts are never overdrawn.",
    "B": "Payments may be late.",
    "C": "It is easier to keep track of payments.",
    "D": "The lack of paper is good for the environment.",
    "answer": "D: The lack of paper is good for the environment.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Information management should ensure that information is",
    "A": "inaccessible. C. pleasant.",
    "B": "abundant. D. retrievable. 72. Payroll, hotel reservations, and sales orders are handled by a(n) __________ type of information system. A. executive support system",
    "C": "decision support system B. knowledge work system",
    "D": "transaction processing system",
    "answer": "D: transaction processing system",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why does Dan order extra copy paper, Post-it notes, and printer ink cartridges for the department when he places an order for office supplies?",
    "A": "To reduce the need to forecast",
    "B": "To ensure product qualit y",
    "C": "To meet minimal expectations",
    "D": "To prevent stockouts",
    "answer": "D: To prevent stockouts",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After a job interview, an applicant should prepare a follow-up letter that",
    "A": "is long and detailed.",
    "B": "includes a resume.",
    "C": "is short and typed.",
    "D": "contains a photo.",
    "answer": "C: is short and typed.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an example of a written business inquiry?",
    "A": "An email requesting vendor pricing and discounts",
    "B": "A memo outlining an upcoming meeting agenda",
    "C": "A form describing an employee's performance review",
    "D": "A report summarizing annual financial information",
    "answer": "A: An email requesting vendor pricing and discounts",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do many businesses provide their employees to encourage them to continue their education to gain additional skills and knowledge?",
    "A": "Discretionary income C. Expense account",
    "B": "Workers' compensation D. Tuition reimbursement 100. Jayne Jacobs is the assistant sales manager for Progressive Electronics. Using a hierarchical chain of command, Jayne is most likely to report to A. Tom Mitchell, vice president of operations. B. Paula Cardenas, vice president of sales.",
    "C": "Mark Peterson, sales manager.",
    "D": "Marjorie Lazarus, customer service supervisor.",
    "answer": "D: Marjorie Lazarus, customer service supervisor.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do people usually take into consideration when identifying occupations that the y want to pursue in life?",
    "A": "Natural talent",
    "B": "Personal conduct",
    "C": "Mental health",
    "D": "Social attitude",
    "answer": "A: Natural talent",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following information should be shared immediately with all staff:?",
    "A": "A customer has requested that the business extend its hours.",
    "B": "An employee of the business has been caught shoplifting.",
    "C": "A customer has complained about the service s/he received.",
    "D": "An employee of the business may soon be transferred out of town.",
    "answer": "C: A customer has complained about the service s/he received.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the benefits of being adaptable is that it enables employees to",
    "A": "manage their time.",
    "B": "deal with change.",
    "C": "take the initiative.",
    "D": "avoid a conflict.",
    "answer": "B: deal with change.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },

  {
    "Question": "What might an employee receive from a business for routinely helping customers with their problems an d\nsatisfying their needs?",
    "A": "A promotion",
    "B": "An honorarium",
    "C": "A gratuity",
    "D": "A suspension",
    "answer": "A: A promotion",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Leadership is especially important at the beginning of a business because",
    "A": "businesses cannot afford to pay employees.",
    "B": "startup failure rates are high.",
    "C": "every company must have a president.",
    "D": "only certain types of people can be leaders.",
    "answer": "B: startup failure rates are high.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You want to get straight A's and impress your teachers, so you consider cheating on tests to ma ke sure you do well. You're facing an ethical dilemma because of your",
    "A": "desire to prove yourself.",
    "B": "conflicting values.",
    "C": "pressure from others.",
    "D": "bad role models.",
    "answer": "A: desire to prove yourself.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is production important to businesses?",
    "A": "It eliminates competition.",
    "B": "It creates goods and services businesses can sell.",
    "C": "It enables businesses to charge high prices.",
    "D": "It informs businesses about consumers' needs and wants.",
    "answer": "B: It creates goods and services businesses can sell.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When sales revenue exceeds the cost of goods sold and operating expenses, the business receives a(n)?",
    "A": "capital.",
    "B": "income.",
    "C": "profit.",
    "D": "loss.",
    "answer": "C: profit.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Financial information is not useful if it does not contain understandable",
    "A": "language.",
    "B": "footnotes.",
    "C": "investment analysis.",
    "D": "recommendations.",
    "answer": "A: language.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is important for employees to demonstrate a customer-service mindset when they are",
    "A": "handling problems.",
    "B": "contacting suppliers.",
    "C": "placing orders.",
    "D": "preparing schedules.",
    "answer": "A: handling problems.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An upscale department store tracks customer purchases made with store credit cards and then tailors promotional messages and merchandise offers to specific clients based on their purchases. What software allows the retailer to manage this strategy?",
    "A": "Spreadsheet C. Database",
    "B": "Word processing D. Systems tools 76. Which of the following is an example of an integrated software application: A. SMS",
    "C": "Point-of-sale B. Java",
    "D": "URL",
    "answer": "C: Point-of-sale B. Java",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Some energy companies offer free electricity at night and on weekends because during those times",
    "A": "supply and demand are equal.",
    "B": "the substitution effect occurs.",
    "C": "demand is greater than supply.",
    "D": "supply is greater than demand.",
    "answer": "D: supply is greater than demand.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When return on capital is positive, the company is?",
    "A": "growing in value.",
    "B": "losing value.",
    "C": "low on cash.",
    "D": "paying out dividends.",
    "answer": "A: growing in value.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The things that people buy to satisfy their economic wants are known as",
    "A": "free goods.",
    "B": "economic goods and services.",
    "C": "economic votes.",
    "D": "tangible objects.",
    "answer": "B: economic goods and services.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first thing an employee should do when s/he accidentally spills cof fee in the tile hallway?",
    "A": "Leave it for the cleaning crew",
    "B": "Wait for the floor to dry",
    "C": "Tell others about the spill",
    "D": "Wipe it up immediately",
    "answer": "D: Wipe it up immediately",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The number of levels of management that a business needs usually depends upon the",
    "A": "location of the facility.",
    "B": "age of the employees.",
    "C": "goals of the company.",
    "D": "size of the business.",
    "answer": "D: size of the business.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Romaiza is looking at her monthly bank statement for her checking account. For the month, she had two separate withdrawals for $4.75 each, a $125 deposit, another $9 withdrawal, a $744 deposit, and a $378 withdrawal. Romaiza started the month with $1,049 in her account. What should the balance of Romaiza's statement be at the end of the month?",
    "A": "$1,521.50",
    "B": "$1,539.50",
    "C": "$1,526.25",
    "D": "$1,516.75",
    "answer": "A: $1,521.50",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The employee didn't listen to the manager's explanation about how to perform a certain task bec ause s/he had done a similar job before. Which of the following factors caused the employee not to li sten effectively:",
    "A": "Past experiences",
    "B": "Attention span",
    "C": "Age differences",
    "D": "Language skills",
    "answer": "A: Past experiences",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is one way that workplace accidents are costly to employees:?",
    "A": "Lost sales",
    "B": "Lost production",
    "C": "Lost profits",
    "D": "Lost income",
    "answer": "D: Lost income",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What element of voice is important in order to communicate effectively with others?",
    "A": "Documentation",
    "B": "Vocabulary",
    "C": "Grammar",
    "D": "Articulation",
    "answer": "D: Articulation",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first step in developing a personal plan of action?",
    "A": "State your goal(s).",
    "B": "Record your progress.",
    "C": "Evaluate the effectiveness of your plan.",
    "D": "Develop a plan for achieving your goal.",
    "answer": "A: State your goal(s).",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When posting a new page to an existing website, the new page should be linked to the?",
    "A": "personal computer.",
    "B": "pop-up ads.",
    "C": "home page.",
    "D": "online catalog.",
    "answer": "C: home page.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a reason why innovation is important:?",
    "A": "Innovation helps the economy.",
    "B": "Innovation ensures a business will succeed.",
    "C": "Innovation eliminates competition.",
    "D": "Innovation leads to creativity.",
    "answer": "A: Innovation helps the economy.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You cannot communicate with your computer without",
    "A": "Windows.",
    "B": "a wireless mouse.",
    "C": "an operating system.",
    "D": "a mobile device.",
    "answer": "C: an operating system.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When providing feedback to a coachee, a good coach will be?",
    "A": "creative.",
    "B": "tactful.",
    "C": "aggressive.",
    "D": "vague.",
    "answer": "B: tactful.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Todd needs to develop an overall plan for his business but does not know what type of information to include in the document. Todd logs onto a search engine to quickly locate the information he needs. Which of the following search terms is most likely to provide Todd with desired search resul ts:",
    "A": "Plan components",
    "B": "Develop planning document",
    "C": "Business plan elements",
    "D": "Business document components",
    "answer": "C: Business plan elements",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Health and safety regulations in business usually require businesses to",
    "A": "hold regular safety meetings.",
    "B": "purchase fireproof supplies.",
    "C": "report workplace accidents.",
    "D": "stay open 24/7.",
    "answer": "C: report workplace accidents.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lucia, a business owner, just hired a new employee. What is one thing she should be sure t o do on the employee's first day?",
    "A": "Let the employee work on trivial tasks for a few days so that s/he can ease into working.",
    "B": "Start the new employee on work right away so that s/he becomes accustomed to his/her job duties.",
    "C": "Provide the new employee with all the details of every project s/he will be working on.",
    "D": "Assign the new employee a mentor who can answer any questions s/he may have.",
    "answer": "D: Assign the new employee a mentor who can answer any questions s/he may have.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Riverbrook High School's student government has a rule that members cannot discuss plans with anyon e\noutside of the organization until they have been released to the whole school. This rule is related to",
    "A": "conflicts of interest.",
    "B": "health and safety.",
    "C": "confidentiality.",
    "D": "use of property.",
    "answer": "C: confidentiality.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the most appropriate method for supervisors to use when communic ating about personal or confidential issues with individual employees:?",
    "A": "Telephone conference call",
    "B": "Company newsletter",
    "C": "Face-to-face meeting",
    "D": "Staff memo",
    "answer": "C: Face-to-face meeting",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the benefits of buying whole-life insurance is that over time",
    "A": "the face value increases.",
    "B": "the deductible decreases.",
    "C": "it pays high interest.",
    "D": "it builds up cash value.",
    "answer": "D: it builds up cash value.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Property and income are not distributed equally in a private enterprise system becaus e skilled workers usually",
    "A": "receive higher salaries.",
    "B": "belong to a union.",
    "C": "work longer hours.",
    "D": "pay higher taxes.",
    "answer": "A: receive higher salaries.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements best describes revolving credit accounts:?",
    "A": "Credit is used for consumed utilities that have not yet been paid.",
    "B": "Credit is paid in installments within a certain period of time.",
    "C": "The credit limit is set at the time the credit account is opened.",
    "D": "Interest is not charged if a credit user makes payments on time.",
    "answer": "C: The credit limit is set at the time the credit account is opened.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Candace accidentally opens an email sent by her employer with a subject line titled \"Confidential information for Alyssa.\" What should Candace do?",
    "A": "Ask Alyssa if she was expecting an important email.",
    "B": "Read it and share the information with Alyssa.",
    "C": "Forward the email message to Alyssa.",
    "D": "Close the email and tell her employ er what happened.",
    "answer": "D: Close the email and tell her employ er what happened.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the characteristics of effective communication is conciseness. A concise statement is one that",
    "A": "presents only relevant information. C. would be described as wordy.",
    "B": "contains many adjectives. D. is as vague as possible. 42. Frank hurt Maggie's feelings when they disagreed about something. Now, Maggie goes out of her way to avoid Frank and not confront him about the situation. What conflict response mode is Maggie using? A. Withdrawal",
    "C": "Negotiating B. Yielding",
    "D": "Forcing",
    "answer": "A: presents only relevant information. C. would be described as wordy.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The office photocopier is jammed again! Fortunately, there is an instruction manual to gui de you through the process of removing the jammed paper. What is the best way to use the manual to clear the photocopier?",
    "A": "Perform the first step, and then verify that you have performed it correctly in the manual. R epeat this process in sequential order until all the steps are completed.",
    "B": "Read the entire manual in sequential order and then perform all of the steps in reverse order to remove the jammed paper.",
    "C": "Briefly skim the manual in reverse order and then follow the steps in sequential order to remove the jammed paper.",
    "D": "Read step one and then perform step one. Repeat this process in sequential order until all of the",
    "answer": "D: Read step one and then perform step one. Repeat this process in sequential order until all of the",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Marisa believes that she possesses the skills to make a positive contribution to the w ork team. Marisa is exhibiti ng",
    "A": "empathy.",
    "B": "ethical standards.",
    "C": "systematic behavior.",
    "D": "self-confidence.",
    "answer": "D: self-confidence.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should a business employee do immediately after taking a telephone message for a cowork er?",
    "A": "Contact a supervisor",
    "B": "Write an inquiry",
    "C": "Thank the caller",
    "D": "File the information",
    "answer": "C: Thank the caller",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why should a purchasing specialist evaluate supplier performance?",
    "A": "To develop a purchase contract",
    "B": "To determine whether they should use the supplier again",
    "C": "To purchase items to sell to wholesalers and retailers",
    "D": "To assist in new product development",
    "answer": "B: To determine whether they should use the supplier again",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What information should be included on a r\u00e9sum\u00e9?",
    "A": "Work experience, education, and personal interests",
    "B": "Education, work experience, and contact information",
    "C": "Contact information, political affiliation, and education",
    "D": "Personal goals, education, and references",
    "answer": "B: Education, work experience, and contact information",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is one of the basics of goal setting:?",
    "A": "Wishing for your goal",
    "B": "Reviewing and updating your goal",
    "C": "Sharing your goal with others",
    "D": "Defending your goal",
    "answer": "B: Reviewing and updating your goal",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For financial information to be relevant, it must also be",
    "A": "digital.",
    "B": "certified by an auditor.",
    "C": "timely.",
    "D": "perfect.",
    "answer": "C: timely.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tony works for a large insurance company. His job is to support the company president, schedul e his/her appointments, and answer his/her phone calls. Tony works in",
    "A": "operations management.",
    "B": "administrative services.",
    "C": "marketing communications.",
    "D": "human resource management.",
    "answer": "B: administrative services.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for employees to effectively communicate information about the busines s to customers?",
    "A": "To promote teamwork",
    "B": "To display integrity",
    "C": "To build morale",
    "D": "To provide service",
    "answer": "D: To provide service",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When the company president finished his speech complimenting the staff on their work and pr omising raises and bonuses, the staff members rose to their feet and applauded him. The staff mem bers were expressing their approval through?",
    "A": "sign language.",
    "B": "nonverbal communication.",
    "C": "animated conversation.",
    "D": "inappropriate behavior.",
    "answer": "B: nonverbal communication.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following examples best depicts the relationship between personal values and careers:?",
    "A": "Tomas's values give him the skills to confront his coworker.",
    "B": "A company only hires people that fit with its vision.",
    "C": "Isaac decided to take a position that aligned with his values.",
    "D": "Riley only spends time with people who share her values.",
    "answer": "C: Isaac decided to take a position that aligned with his values.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "While conducting research, it is important to understand and be able to recognize the difference between factual information and opinions. Which of the following statements best represents factual information:",
    "A": "It cannot be verified.",
    "B": "It is discovered.",
    "C": "It is created.",
    "D": "It is subjective.",
    "answer": "B: It is discovered.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Workers who must rely on each other to carry out their jobs would be described as __________ workers.",
    "A": "ineffective",
    "B": "self-sufficient",
    "C": "interdependent",
    "D": "efficient",
    "answer": "C: interdependent",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Pablo takes a phone call for a coworker. In order for Pablo's coworker to be able to follow up with the caller, Pablo should ask the caller for their",
    "A": "name, current address, and extension number.",
    "B": "name, organization, and phone number.",
    "C": "phone number, last name, and zip code.",
    "D": "phone number, last name, and address.",
    "answer": "B: name, organization, and phone number.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you monitor projects, you are more likely to?",
    "A": "find flaws in your team's work.",
    "B": "struggle to stay focused on the goal.",
    "C": "achieve better project results.",
    "D": "take over all of the project work.",
    "answer": "C: achieve better project results.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When planning to make your vision a reality, you must first consider?",
    "A": "how many volunteers to hire. C. your personal financial goals.",
    "B": "the wording of your mission statement. D. the resources that you will need. 47. Which of the following is a charac teristic of someone who leads by example: A. Pessimistic",
    "C": "Plays favorites B. Disinterested",
    "D": "Enthusiastic",
    "answer": "D: Enthusiastic",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about developing self-understanding:?",
    "A": "No one else can help you identify your interests.",
    "B": "Self-understanding and self-information are the same.",
    "C": "You can learn as much from your failures as you can from your successes.",
    "D": "Choosing a career should be based on your current skills and talents.",
    "answer": "C: You can learn as much from your failures as you can from your successes.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When operating machinery in the workplace, employees can reduce the risk of injury to themselves and damage to the machinery by?",
    "A": "reading t he appropriate promotional materials.",
    "B": "following the manufacturer's operating instructions.",
    "C": "performing maintenance activities themselves.",
    "D": "requesting a trained supervisor to operate the machinery.",
    "answer": "B: following the manufacturer's operating instructions.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the primary function of the random-access memory (RAM) component of a computer?",
    "A": "Reads the computer code that provides visual effects",
    "B": "Serves as a temporary holding area for files and programs",
    "C": "Stores data and programs permanently",
    "D": "Enables the user to apply point-and-click commands",
    "answer": "B: Serves as a temporary holding area for files and programs",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The goal of quality circles is to",
    "A": "complete a specific one-time task.",
    "B": "improve performance in many areas.",
    "C": "solve a large organizational problem.",
    "D": "increase social contact among organizations.",
    "answer": "B: improve performance in many areas.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it sometimes difficult to be honest about strengths?",
    "A": "Few people have strengths.",
    "B": "No one likes to recognize strengths.",
    "C": "Weaknesses are more significant than strengths.",
    "D": "We don't want to brag.",
    "answer": "D: We don't want to brag.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the best method a responsible worker could use to become more productive:?",
    "A": "Read current industry materials",
    "B": "Watch coworkers do their jobs",
    "C": "Follow unwritten company rules",
    "D": "Behave with honesty and integrity",
    "answer": "A: Read current industry materials",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Laws that prohibit violence against others are an example of which function of the law?",
    "A": "Enacting social change",
    "B": "Maintaining order",
    "C": "Ensuring equality",
    "D": "Resolving disputes",
    "answer": "B: Maintaining order",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is effective to follow a step-by-step order when applying written directions to",
    "A": "achieve tasks. C. read materials.",
    "B": "give commands. D. take notes. 4. Addison wants to encourage the speaker who is giving a presentation to her class, so she nods when the speaker makes a good point, makes eye contact, and uses other forms of __________ communication. A. negative",
    "C": "nonverbal B. verbal",
    "D": "written",
    "answer": "A: achieve tasks. C. read materials.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If Saeed is concerned that a data breach altered the completeness of his information, he is concerned about t he __________ of the data.",
    "A": "confidentiality",
    "B": "privacy",
    "C": "integrity",
    "D": "availability",
    "answer": "C: integrity",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a groupware application:?",
    "A": "Job rotation",
    "B": "Email filters",
    "C": "Database sharing",
    "D": "Relationship marketing",
    "answer": "C: Database sharing",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the importance of the computer hard drive in a computer system?",
    "A": "It permanently stores the computer program files and data.",
    "B": "It facilitates the computer's audio transmissions.",
    "C": "It allows the user to view the computer data.",
    "D": "It transmits power to other computer devices.",
    "answer": "A: It permanently stores the computer program files and data.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Two years ago, Tommy borrowed $12,500 from his bank to purchase a new vehicle. Unfortunatel y, he lost his job about a year ago, and he hasn't been able to make a payment on the loan for six months. As a result, the bank is taking steps to seize his automobile. This is called a",
    "A": "forbearance.",
    "B": "foreclosure.",
    "C": "repossession.",
    "D": "debt consolidation.",
    "answer": "C: repossession.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Computer programs that allow businesses to manage all types of activities, such as inventory control and finance, are known as",
    "A": "integrated software application packages.",
    "B": "electronic communications programs.",
    "C": "interactive information display packages.",
    "D": "wireless connectivity programs.",
    "answer": "A: integrated software application packages.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Taylor works as a public relations manager. His career is in the area of",
    "A": "marketing research.",
    "B": "operations management.",
    "C": "professional selling.",
    "D": "marketing communications.",
    "answer": "D: marketing communications.",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an employee maintaining a safe work environment:?",
    "A": "Steve takes the elevator instead of the stairs during the practice fire drill.",
    "B": "William follows his employer's rules when he is operating heavy equipment.",
    "C": "Kaylee trips over the computer wires that are lying on the floor of her office.",
    "D": "Anna fails to tell her supervisor that the caution light is blinking on the equipment.",
    "answer": "B: William follows his employer's rules when he is operating heavy equipment.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an important component of computer systems:?",
    "A": "Internet",
    "B": "E-commerce",
    "C": "Software",
    "D": "Website",
    "answer": "C: Software",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To be reimbursed for business expenses, Luke must obtain and complete an expense-reimbursemen t form, attach the original transaction receipts to the completed form, and submit the documentation to hi s manager for approval. What is Luke doing?",
    "A": "Following company procedures",
    "B": "Developing company policies",
    "C": "Evaluating company feedback",
    "D": "Assessing company guidelines",
    "answer": "A: Following company procedures",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Information usually comes in either physical form or __________ form.",
    "A": "verbal",
    "B": "note card",
    "C": "book",
    "D": "electronic",
    "answer": "D: electronic",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a workplace security issue occurs, an employee should report the problem to the appropriate __________ agency.?",
    "A": "health",
    "B": "fire prevention",
    "C": "law enforcement",
    "D": "welfare",
    "answer": "C: law enforcement",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Joe finishes stocking shelves, he waits to be told what to do next. Joe's manager would like for Joe to keep himself busy. Which of the following traits would Joe's manager like for Joe to develop:?",
    "A": "Initiative",
    "B": "Creativity",
    "C": "Leadership",
    "D": "Assertiveness",
    "answer": "A: Initiative",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During an interview, a job applicant can indicate to the interviewer an interest in the position by",
    "A": "staring out the window.",
    "B": "looking at their feet.",
    "C": "maintaining eye contact.",
    "D": "slouching in their chair.",
    "answer": "C: maintaining eye contact.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business uses computer technology to manage its money and move it among different accounts, it is taking advantage of?",
    "A": "electronic data interchange.",
    "B": "electronic transfer of funds.",
    "C": "expert systems.",
    "D": "hardware.",
    "answer": "B: electronic transfer of funds.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Some customers give the true reason for making a complaint, while others hide the true reason. In which of the following situations is the customer giving the true reason:",
    "A": "Requesting a different style of shoes when the main concern is price",
    "B": "Returning a dry-clean-only dress after washing it",
    "C": "Saying an appliance doesn't work when it was actually dropped",
    "D": "Returning a carton of milk because it has an expired freshness date",
    "answer": "D: Returning a carton of milk because it has an expired freshness date",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Marlena is feeling overwhelmed at work because she has so many different tasks to work on. Some are due t he\nnext day, while some are due over the next few weeks. What's the first thing she should do to figure out how her\ntasks should be prioritized?",
    "A": "Start anywhere-getting something done is better than nothing.",
    "B": "Ask her boss if she can delegate her work to someone else.",
    "C": "Complete the easiest task first.",
    "D": "Make a list of her tasks and determine what's most urgent.",
    "answer": "D: Make a list of her tasks and determine what's most urgent.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If individuals are not self-employed, which of the following is a type of earned income they might receive:",
    "A": "Trust disbursements",
    "B": "Vacation pay",
    "C": "Child support income",
    "D": "Interest and dividends",
    "answer": "B: Vacation pay",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Althea just received her first paycheck at work. She's excited, but as she looks at her pay s tub she gets confused. She wants to know how much money she made in this pay period, but there are so many different numbers. If Althea wants to know how much money will actually be deposited in her b ank account, she should look at the",
    "A": "net pay.",
    "B": "gross pay.",
    "C": "federal income tax.",
    "D": "state tax.",
    "answer": "A: net pay.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "\"I'd like to have that in writing before I give you my money,\" best describes the ________ __ customer.",
    "A": "slow/methodical",
    "B": "dishonest",
    "C": "disagreeable",
    "D": "suspicious",
    "answer": "D: suspicious",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Employees who arrive at work on time and direct their own work-related activities duri ng the course of the day usually possess positive __________ skills.",
    "A": "inner-qualitative",
    "B": "self-conceptual",
    "C": "self-management",
    "D": "personal-orientation",
    "answer": "C: self-management",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When employees demonstrate adaptability, they are able to be?",
    "A": "honest.",
    "B": "creative.",
    "C": "flexible.",
    "D": "aggressive.",
    "answer": "C: flexible.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Once you know your group's purpose, what should you do next?",
    "A": "Contribute in a useful way",
    "B": "Find out what people know about the subject",
    "C": "Volunteer a new idea",
    "D": "Agree on ground rules",
    "answer": "D: Agree on ground rules",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a reason why it is important to monitor projects:?",
    "A": "It saves time and resources. C. It eliminat es accountability.",
    "B": "It allows projects to go off track. D. It makes team members more competitive. 86. In searching out suppliers, industrial purchasers should obtain __________ from potential vendors. A. purchase orders",
    "C": "buying plans B. price qu otations",
    "D": "resource files",
    "answer": "A: It saves time and resources. C. It eliminat es accountability.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jon is constantly checking and responding to email during the workday. Because of this, it takes him twice as long to finish writing a report. This is an example of how",
    "A": "perfectionism allows people to better manage commitments.",
    "B": "organization leads to overcommitment.",
    "C": "commitment leads to professional success.",
    "D": "technology hampers one's ability to manage commitments.",
    "answer": "D: technology hampers one's ability to manage commitments.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses develop specific policies in order to increase their",
    "A": "company benefits. C. sales and profits.",
    "B": "employees' morale. D. inventory levels. 19. What type of difficult customer may be the most trying on your patience and do the most damage to the image of your business? A. Domineering/S uperior",
    "C": "Suspicious B. Disagreeable",
    "D": "Slow/Methodical",
    "answer": "C: Suspicious B. Disagreeable",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of information may be listed in the work experience section of a r\u00e9sum\u00e9 if the pe rson has had only a few paying jobs?",
    "A": "Career objectives",
    "B": "Technical training",
    "C": "Volunteer positions",
    "D": "Personal references",
    "answer": "C: Volunteer positions",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a variable expense:?",
    "A": "Gasoline",
    "B": "Rent",
    "C": "Car payment",
    "D": "Gym membership",
    "answer": "A: Gasoline",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following might indicate a job applicant's initiative when applying for an entry-level position:?",
    "A": "Sending a letter of application C. Showing up for an interview",
    "B": "Completing an application blank D. Having a physical examination Test 1251 BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CORE EXAM 4 32. You overhear two classmates gossiping about one of your friends. What can you do to show your loyalty? A. Ignore the conversation to show that you don't listen to gossip and rumors. B. Tell your classmates to stop talking about your friend, and defend your friend.",
    "C": "Tell your friend all of the hurtful comments that were said about them.",
    "D": "Join in the conversation so that your classmates won't gossip about you next.",
    "answer": "A: Sending a letter of application C. Showing up for an interview",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Paul is a 45-year-old manager of a large company who makes offensive, gender-related com ments to Elizabeth, a 28-year old buyer, who has been with the company for six months. Paul's beh avior violates Elizabeth's workplace rights because he is engaging in",
    "A": "age discrimination.",
    "B": "cultural supremacy.",
    "C": "sexual harassment.",
    "D": "ethnocentrism.",
    "answer": "C: sexual harassment.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You cannot communicate with your computer without",
    "A": "Microsoft Windows.",
    "B": "a wireless mouse.",
    "C": "an operating system.",
    "D": "a mobile device.",
    "answer": "C: an operating system.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a text-oriented graphic that is often used to illustrate a business process or organizational structure:?",
    "A": "Flowchart",
    "B": "Pictograph",
    "C": "Map",
    "D": "Pie chart",
    "answer": "A: Flowchart",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kara has natural artistic talent and thinks that she might want to work as an interior designer. Kara's artistic ability is an example of a(n)",
    "A": "hobby.",
    "B": "mindset.",
    "C": "aptitude.",
    "D": "vision.",
    "answer": "C: aptitude.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When posting on your company's social media page, it is important to?",
    "A": "avoid posting any content that is new or interesting.",
    "B": "ensure your message aligns with company values.",
    "C": "make aggressive attacks on your competitors' products.",
    "D": "say whatever is on your mind at the current moment.",
    "answer": "B: ensure your message aligns with company values.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mary has been an employee at the Acme Company for nine years and has been having troub le motivating herself to complete tasks on time. Her supervisor feels she needs to develop her self-esteem through affirmations. Why should Mary write and use affirmations?",
    "A": "To carry 3x5 index cards around with her for a week",
    "B": "To daydream about being a superstar in life",
    "C": "To develop a positive aspect of her life",
    "D": "To know the difference between self-esteem and affirmations",
    "answer": "C: To develop a positive aspect of her life",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When employees demonstrate adaptability, they are able to be?",
    "A": "aggressive.",
    "B": "flexible.",
    "C": "honest.",
    "D": "creative.",
    "answer": "B: flexible.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tia has many interests and doesn't know which career path is best for her. One method Tia can use to determine the best occupational options for her is to",
    "A": "develop a general interest questionnaire.",
    "B": "have friends and family critique her personality type.",
    "C": "complete an aptitude assessment survey.",
    "D": "surf the Internet for job descriptions.",
    "answer": "C: complete an aptitude assessment survey.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kayla is an introvert who enjoys working alone. She also prefers structure and routine in her day. Which of the following careers would best suit Kayla's personality:",
    "A": "Accountant C. Marketing specialist",
    "B": "Elementary school teacher D. Public defense attorney 95. Technological advancements have made it possible for s ome entrepreneurs to A. reduce the need for maintaining financial records. B. operate their businesses entirely from their computers.",
    "C": "run their businesses with fewer computer skills.",
    "D": "eliminate the need to pay income and Social Security taxes.",
    "answer": "A: Accountant C. Marketing specialist",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Should you be able to adjust to change more quickly over time?",
    "A": "Yes, the more change you cope with, the faster you adjust.",
    "B": "Yes, practicing adjusting to change makes it go faster.",
    "C": "No, adjusting to change takes most people very little time.",
    "D": "No, the length of time it takes depends on the kind of change.",
    "answer": "D: No, the length of time it takes depends on the kind of change.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lucy, who works for the Green Corporation, is responsible for handling special events and res ponding to requests for information about the company. Lucy works in",
    "A": "merchandising.",
    "B": "marketing research.",
    "C": "marketing communications.",
    "D": "professional selling.",
    "answer": "C: marketing communications.",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Allison is attending a business seminar. Because the seminar presenter is speaking very quickly, Allison is having a difficult time taking accurate notes. What technique would help Allison take notes qui ckly?",
    "A": "Write notes on index cards",
    "B": "Use abbreviations and symbols",
    "C": "Focus on the subtopics",
    "D": "Ask the speaker to provide handouts",
    "answer": "B: Use abbreviations and symbols",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a lending investment:?",
    "A": "Stocks",
    "B": "Bonds",
    "C": "Antiques",
    "D": "Homes",
    "answer": "B: Bonds",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If William wants to determine the dollar amount that he has earned before taxes and other deductions for the pay period, he should look at the __________ on his paycheck stub.",
    "A": "net pay",
    "B": "gross wages",
    "C": "year-to-date gross earnings",
    "D": "year-to-date net income",
    "answer": "B: gross wages",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kevin developed a letter stating that his company will be offering discounts on certain products for a limited time. Kevin's letter is an example of a(n)",
    "A": "request for data. C. instruction al guide.",
    "B": "informative message. D. expression of personal opinion. 15. A person who publicly tweets negative comments about their company is most likely to be A. laughed at.",
    "C": "promoted. B. fired.",
    "D": "prosecuted.",
    "answer": "B: informative message. D. expression of personal opinion. 15. A person who publicly tweets negative comments about their company is most likely to be A. laughed at.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You are able to rely on your boss to answer your questions and treat all of your coworkers f airly. This means that you __________ your boss.",
    "A": "support",
    "B": "trust",
    "C": "like",
    "D": "resemble",
    "answer": "B: trust",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When businesses invest funds to expand, they are involved in the process of?",
    "A": "selling.",
    "B": "capitalism.",
    "C": "finance.",
    "D": "depreciation.",
    "answer": "C: finance.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of analyzing data to evaluate project success:?",
    "A": "Planning to complete a future project",
    "B": "Deciding to evaluate your team's level of satisfaction",
    "C": "Comparing projected sales to actual sales",
    "D": "Telling stakeholders that you achieved project goals",
    "answer": "C: Comparing projected sales to actual sales",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an action employees can take to maintain a customer service mindset:?",
    "A": "Decide how to spend their break time",
    "B": "Maximize conversations with coworkers",
    "C": "Listen to the words of soothing songs",
    "D": "Devote their full attention to customers",
    "answer": "D: Devote their full attention to customers",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The costs of government regulation of business are paid for through",
    "A": "tariffs.",
    "B": "interest.",
    "C": "prices.",
    "D": "taxes.",
    "answer": "D: taxes.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When management and employees have the same idea of what the business is capable of bein g in the future, they are sharing a(n)?",
    "A": "vision.",
    "B": "goal.",
    "C": "dream.",
    "D": "idea.",
    "answer": "A: vision.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a leader takes ownership of a problem, makes sure it is fixed, and takes steps to prevent it from happening again, s/he is demonstrating",
    "A": "flexibility.",
    "B": "adaptability.",
    "C": "responsibility.",
    "D": "social awareness.",
    "answer": "C: responsibility.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What types of skills are extremely important for an applicant to use effectively during an em ployment interview?",
    "A": "Occupational",
    "B": "Communication",
    "C": "Management",
    "D": "Educational",
    "answer": "B: Communication",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As Justin is cooking, his sister reads the recipe directions to him out loud. Justin isn't s ure if she said one teaspoon of vanilla or two. He gives her a puzzled look, and his sister reads the directions again. Which of the following steps for following directions does this situation illustrate:",
    "A": "Take notes",
    "B": "Accept responsibility",
    "C": "Acknowledge directions verbally or nonverbally",
    "D": "Eliminate distractions",
    "answer": "C: Acknowledge directions verbally or nonverbally",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When writing a business letter in block format, what information follows the date?",
    "A": "Body of letter",
    "B": "Sender's name and address",
    "C": "Recipient's name and address",
    "D": "Salutation/Greeting",
    "answer": "C: Recipient's name and address",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a person uses a decision-making model to make a decision, they can trust that?",
    "A": "their intuition is right. C. they achieved success.",
    "B": "they made the best choice. D. they made a good effort. 92. Which of the following individuals is most likely to meet their employer's expectations for proper employee behavior: A. Charlene, who oversleeps and is late to work once or twice a month B. Penelope, who asked a successful veteran coworker to serve as her mentor",
    "C": "Dave, who has a tendency to take credit for his team's work",
    "D": "Tim, who waits a week or more before replying to his manager's emails",
    "answer": "D: Tim, who waits a week or more before replying to his manager's emails",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Achievement-oriented, emotionally intelligent people usually are",
    "A": "transparent.",
    "B": "prosperous.",
    "C": "motivated.",
    "D": "impatient.",
    "answer": "C: motivated.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following types of insurance do businesses frequently offer as part of their employee benefit plan:?",
    "A": "Liability",
    "B": "Property",
    "C": "Health",
    "D": "Automobile",
    "answer": "C: Health",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What components must \"balance\" in a balance sheet?",
    "A": "Assets plus liabilities should equal net profit.",
    "B": "Income plus expenses should equal owner's equity.",
    "C": "Assets minus liabilities should equal owner's equity.",
    "D": "Income minus expenses should equal owners' equity.",
    "answer": "C: Assets minus liabilities should equal owner's equity.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To reinforce the company's customer-friendly image, managers should consistently",
    "A": "emphasize the importance of production planning.",
    "B": "provide employees with stock options, profit sharing, and bonuses.",
    "C": "communicate the company's servi ce-quality expectations to employees.",
    "D": "reorganize the company's resources.",
    "answer": "C: communicate the company's servi ce-quality expectations to employees.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a technique that can help you determine what your values are:?",
    "A": "Brainstorming",
    "B": "Deducting",
    "C": "Guessing",
    "D": "Listening",
    "answer": "A: Brainstorming",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements about change is true:?",
    "A": "People tend to respond well to personal change.",
    "B": "It is the only thing that is constant in our lives.",
    "C": "It rarely causes problems for many businesses.",
    "D": "People tend to feel threatened by change.",
    "answer": "B: It is the only thing that is constant in our lives.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a trend in information management:?",
    "A": "Increased compliance laws and regulations",
    "B": "Decreased competition",
    "C": "Decreased number of electronic documents",
    "D": "Increased number of workers in the office",
    "answer": "A: Increased compliance laws and regulations",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an uninsurable risk:?",
    "A": "Business interruption",
    "B": "Customer buying habits",
    "C": "Fire",
    "D": "Personal injury",
    "answer": "B: Customer buying habits",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When writing a check, what information goes after the phrase \"Pay to the order of\"?",
    "A": "Your signature",
    "B": "The amount paid",
    "C": "The name of the recipient",
    "D": "The current date",
    "answer": "C: The name of the recipient",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As Ben assesses his personal strengths and weaknesses, what can he do to keep from foc using too much on his weaknesses?",
    "A": "Identify one strength for every weakness",
    "B": "Compare himself to others",
    "C": "Develop a list of false generalizations",
    "D": "Ask others for critical feedback",
    "answer": "A: Identify one strength for every weakness",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Carmen had an accuracy rating of 91 percent last year. This year, she won't be satisfied unless her accuracy rating is at least 92 percent or higher. Which behavior of an achievement-oriented person does this illustrate?",
    "A": "Taking moderate risks",
    "B": "Not being satisfied with current performance",
    "C": "Demonstrating leadership",
    "D": "Desiring feedback",
    "answer": "B: Not being satisfied with current performance",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The disadvantage to using credit cards to pay for goods and services is that y ou",
    "A": "pay interest on purchases.",
    "B": "establish a credit rating.",
    "C": "earn quarterly dividends.",
    "D": "defer cash payments.",
    "answer": "A: pay interest on purchases.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of investing in bonds:?",
    "A": "They are issued by corporations or governments.",
    "B": "Their returns do not keep up with inflation.",
    "C": "You must pay a penalty for early withdrawal.",
    "D": "They may take a long time to provide a return.",
    "answer": "D: They may take a long time to provide a return.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is important to do when giving verbal directions to make sure the audience understands?",
    "A": "Explain information",
    "B": "Ask questions",
    "C": "Use gestures",
    "D": "Maintain eye contact",
    "answer": "B: Ask questions",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When sending an email message to a group of customers, what should you do to protect the privacy of each individual?",
    "A": "Enter email addresses in the Cc field",
    "B": "Copy and paste the message text into a separate email for each customer",
    "C": "Send an initial email to each customer asking permission to send them a group message",
    "D": "Enter email addresses in the Bcc field",
    "answer": "D: Enter email addresses in the Bcc field",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Camille is conducting research for a report that she is writing about the mercury levels in fish. Which of the following is the most reliable source for Camille to use:",
    "A": "A recent blog entry that was written by Dr. H arold Corning, a retired brain surgeon",
    "B": "A chapter from a high school physics textbook that was published in 2001",
    "C": "An online article that was written last month by a well-known marine biologist",
    "D": "A 2019 newsletter from a nonprofit organization that studies the effects of air pollution",
    "answer": "C: An online article that was written last month by a well-known marine biologist",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Christie's coworkers know that she won't repeat what they tell her if they ask her not to do so. This indicates that Christie is a(n) __________ coworker.",
    "A": "trustworthy",
    "B": "tactful",
    "C": "straightforward",
    "D": "efficient",
    "answer": "A: trustworthy",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a way for employers to prevent recordkeeping or payroll fraud:?",
    "A": "Require sales staff to observe customers on the selling floor",
    "B": "Provide procedures for the personal use of office supplies",
    "C": "Divide cash-related responsibilities among different employees",
    "D": "Train salespeople to be familiar with prices",
    "answer": "C: Divide cash-related responsibilities among different employees",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which of the following situations would a business use a spreadsheet software program to estimate the effect of change on its financial situation:",
    "A": "A salesperson kept all appointments.",
    "B": "Customers purchased more products.",
    "C": "Mailing labels are needed for a catalog.",
    "D": "Sales are expected to increase by 5%.",
    "answer": "D: Sales are expected to increase by 5%.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a key to effective note-taking?",
    "A": "Capturing every detail C. Creative thinking",
    "B": "Active listening D. Using an outlin e 11. Alma is preparing a presentation about her department's budget to make to the company president. She wants to use a visual representation of the budget that shows parts in relation to the whole. Alma should consider using a A. pie chart.",
    "C": "line graph. B. table.",
    "D": "bar graph.",
    "answer": "B: Active listening D. Using an outlin e 11. Alma is preparing a presentation about her department's budget to make to the company president. She wants to use a visual representation of the budget that shows parts in relation to the whole. Alma should consider using a A. pie chart.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you say what you think, you should remember to?",
    "A": "try to use very little body language.",
    "B": "keep talking until others agree.",
    "C": "show respect for others' opinions.",
    "D": "keep your original ideas to yourself.",
    "answer": "C: show respect for others' opinions.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Irene has always kept and filed every piece of paperwork she receives. When she needs to find a specific document for her boss, Irene wastes hours looking through her filing cabinets before she finally finds it. What should Irene do to make her filing more efficient?",
    "A": "Create a system and keep only what she needs.",
    "B": "Store all of her documents virtually online.",
    "C": "Hire a new employee to handle her files.",
    "D": "Purge her old documents, throwing everything away.",
    "answer": "A: Create a system and keep only what she needs.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a user-owned, nonprofit, cooperative financial institution:?",
    "A": "Credit union",
    "B": "Commercial bank",
    "C": "Insurance company",
    "D": "Savings and loan association",
    "answer": "A: Credit union",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Being respectful when considering conflicting viewpoints means",
    "A": "not jumping to conclusions.",
    "B": "listening to your gut instead of facts.",
    "C": "avoiding people who are different from you.",
    "D": "thinking about things subjectively.",
    "answer": "A: not jumping to conclusions.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Penelope wants to use an interactive channel to communicate with her employees. Which chann el of communication should she choose?",
    "A": "A phone call",
    "B": "A voice mail",
    "C": "A letter",
    "D": "A report",
    "answer": "A: A phone call",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mason Publishing included the following statement in a newsletter that was sent to its sales staff about its new tablet: \"CEO Lucinda Marcelli said, 'This product supports our ongoing efforts to revolutionize the ways in which students across the country learn.'\" This is an example of",
    "A": "summarizing the features of a new item by using a testimonial.",
    "B": "including a quotation to introduce an item during a sales meeting.",
    "C": "paraphrasing a comment to explain s pecific product benefits.",
    "D": "using a quotation to communicate product information.",
    "answer": "D: using a quotation to communicate product information.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jonathan works in his small town's only grocery store. He is on a first-name basis with most of the customers who come in. Cheryl is a difficult customer. Sometimes she's really friendly, and other times she snaps at Jonathan. She is a(n) __________ customer.",
    "A": "dishonest",
    "B": "suspicious",
    "C": "irritable/moody",
    "D": "slow/methodical",
    "answer": "C: irritable/moody",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The newly redesigned Toyota Corolla is an example of __________ innovation.",
    "A": "position",
    "B": "process",
    "C": "product",
    "D": "paradigm",
    "answer": "C: product",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ashley is helping Laia make soup. Ashley says, \" Chop up your carrots. But first, find your cutting board. And before that, make sure you have all your ingredients.\" What mistake is Ashley ma king in giving directions?",
    "A": "Giving directions that are too challenging",
    "B": "Giving directions out of order",
    "C": "Using too many big words",
    "D": "Using too much negative language",
    "answer": "B: Giving directions out of order",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If some of a new employee's job tasks are unfamiliar and seem complicated, they should",
    "A": "try to figure them out without help.",
    "B": "seek clarification from the supervisor.",
    "C": "hide the problem for as long as possible.",
    "D": "seek support from coworkers.",
    "answer": "B: seek clarification from the supervisor.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Three-way light bulbs are all made with the same size base. This is an example of a production process that\nuses __________ parts.",
    "A": "branded",
    "B": "standardized",
    "C": "graded",
    "D": "segmented",
    "answer": "B: standardized",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "At school, everyone teased a student about being scared when the business's power went out while they wer e\non the job. When you related how scared you were when the same thing happened to you, you wer e\ndemonstrating __________ behavior.",
    "A": "indifferent",
    "B": "unique",
    "C": "empathetic",
    "D": "callous",
    "answer": "C: empathetic",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is fiat money:?",
    "A": "A $20 bill C. Gold",
    "B": "A check D. A credit card 53. Every two weeks, Jana receives an automatic deposit in her checking account from her employer for work she has performed. This is an example of which form of income: A. Interest",
    "C": "Wages B. Rent",
    "D": "Dividends",
    "answer": "A: A $20 bill C. Gold",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of investing in bonds:?",
    "A": "They are issued by corporations or governments.",
    "B": "You must pay a penalty for early withdrawal.",
    "C": "They may take a long time to provide a return.",
    "D": "Their returns do not keep up with inflation.",
    "answer": "C: They may take a long time to provide a return.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of accounting would most likely be used by a small-business owner who does not off er credit?",
    "A": "COD method",
    "B": "Accrual method",
    "C": "Cash method",
    "D": "Check method",
    "answer": "C: Cash method",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Insurance is a key element in lifelong financial planning that",
    "A": "provides protection against financial losses.",
    "B": "protects a person from unethical salespeople.",
    "C": "guarantees a solid financial future.",
    "D": "is available only to property owners.",
    "answer": "A: provides protection against financial losses.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Writing key points on notecards and then placing the cards in order of their importance is one way to",
    "A": "revise facts.",
    "B": "access files.",
    "C": "organize information.",
    "D": "verify accuracy.",
    "answer": "C: organize information.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a law:?",
    "A": "You must wait in line to check out at the grocery store.",
    "B": "You must follow the speed limit while driving.",
    "C": "Your school's dress code does not allow sleeveless tops.",
    "D": "You cannot use profane language at school.",
    "answer": "B: You must follow the speed limit while driving.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Molly works in operations. Her job is to make sure that the business has all the supplies it needs to keep production going smoothly. Molly works in the area of",
    "A": "purchasing.",
    "B": "financial analysis.",
    "C": "marketing.",
    "D": "human resources management.",
    "answer": "A: purchasing.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements has been edited properly:?",
    "A": "Roger's weekly sales-volume quota are $8,500.",
    "B": "Primary sources may be difficult to find.",
    "C": "Carole is developing a prodect analysis sheet.",
    "D": "Frank, Gus, and Bob is taking a client out to lunch.",
    "answer": "B: Primary sources may be difficult to find.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Information is created from",
    "A": "accounting records.",
    "B": "data.",
    "C": "personnel files.",
    "D": "technology.",
    "answer": "B: data.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The advantage of using electronic devices such as smartphones and laptops to manage busine ss activities and schedules is that they are",
    "A": "inexpensive.",
    "B": "portable.",
    "C": "indestructible.",
    "D": "responsible.",
    "answer": "B: portable.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Joel recently interviewed for an internship at a large accounting firm. After his interview, he made sure to send the interviewer a follow-up email saying the following: \"Ms. Brown, Thank you again for speaking with me this afternoon. Please let me know if you have any additional questions. If offered this internship, I would be thrilled to except!\" What communication mistake did Joel make?",
    "A": "He used an incorrect word.",
    "B": "He used inappropriate language.",
    "C": "He used filler words.",
    "D": "He used an inappropriate communication method.",
    "answer": "A: He used an incorrect word.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Smiling is an example of",
    "A": "verbal communication.",
    "B": "eye contact.",
    "C": "nonverbal communication.",
    "D": "gesturing.",
    "answer": "C: nonverbal communication.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it often necessary for employees to continue their education after working for several years?",
    "A": "To serve an apprenticeship",
    "B": "To attend college",
    "C": "To change careers",
    "D": "To take online classes",
    "answer": "C: To change careers",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Coins and paper money are types of",
    "A": "dividends.",
    "B": "contracts.",
    "C": "bonds.",
    "D": "currency.",
    "answer": "D: currency.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Brayden's group member suggests an idea for a project that Brayden doesn't agree with. Brayden listens politely to the group member's opinion before explaining his own thoughts. Which trust-building technique is Brayden using?",
    "A": "Taking responsibility for your mistakes",
    "B": "Not sharing confidential information",
    "C": "Keeping your promises",
    "D": "Showing respect for others",
    "answer": "D: Showing respect for others",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the benefit of shared vision to an organization?",
    "A": "It creates an ethnocentric environment.",
    "B": "It ensures that the team's goals are achievable.",
    "C": "It serves as a guide for decision making.",
    "D": "It supports a groupthink attitude.",
    "answer": "C: It serves as a guide for decision making.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The business manager tried to write a promotional letter that was simple, clear, and interesting so that customers who received it would",
    "A": "need to read it many times.",
    "B": "ask what it really meant.",
    "C": "find it entertaining.",
    "D": "easily understand it.",
    "answer": "D: easily understand it.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the disadvantages of using nonverbal communication is that it",
    "A": "is not a common f orm of communication. C. is not considered courteous.",
    "B": "may not be interpreted accurately. D. may not be associated with leadership. 8. To evaluate any idea objectively, it is important to consider A. personal opinions.",
    "C": "market research. B. potential problems.",
    "D": "competitors' activities.",
    "answer": "B: may not be interpreted accurately. D. may not be associated with leadership. 8. To evaluate any idea objectively, it is important to consider A. personal opinions.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The supervisor has given John directions for several new job tasks. To follow the directions effectively, John should first confirm",
    "A": "in what order to do the ta sks.",
    "B": "whether these will be regular tasks.",
    "C": "why the tasks need to be done.",
    "D": "who will be working with him.",
    "answer": "A: in what order to do the ta sks.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Serving as a volunteer in a specific industry or for a business-related organization i s one way that individuals might obtain",
    "A": "guidance counseling.",
    "B": "monetary compensation.",
    "C": "technical training.",
    "D": "work experience.",
    "answer": "D: work experience.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the major reasons that companies strive to have the most optimized supply chain is to",
    "A": "increase inventory.",
    "B": "increase suppliers.",
    "C": "eliminate defects.",
    "D": "lower costs.",
    "answer": "D: lower costs.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The freedom to compete is a characteristic of businesses that operate in a(n)",
    "A": "independent society.",
    "B": "communist economy.",
    "C": "imperial political environment.",
    "D": "market economy.",
    "answer": "D: market economy.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hannah has been feeling bored and grumpy lately, so she decides to take dance lessons at the local community center. Which step in the process of maintaining a positive attitude does this illustrate?",
    "A": "Have a sense of humor",
    "B": "Act positively",
    "C": "Look sharp",
    "D": "Realize that it won't happen overnight",
    "answer": "B: Act positively",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The ability to demonstrate interest and enthusiasm often leads to greater",
    "A": "emotional instability.",
    "B": "individual recognition.",
    "C": "personal integrity.",
    "D": "personal achievement.",
    "answer": "D: personal achievement.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If you are in doubt about selecting an item of clothing for work, it is usually best to choose the one that is",
    "A": "highly advertised.",
    "B": "most eye-catching.",
    "C": "conservative.",
    "D": "a current fad.",
    "answer": "C: conservative.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After Nick interviews for a job he really wants, he sends a letter to express his continued interest in the job and ask about the status of the position. Which type of business letter is Nick sending?",
    "A": "Order letter",
    "B": "Letter of resignation",
    "C": "Follow-up letter",
    "D": "Acknowledgement letter",
    "answer": "C: Follow-up letter",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To determine the types of information that the business needs to operate, it is often beneficial to",
    "A": "revise the business's goals.",
    "B": "upgrade the computer network.",
    "C": "develop a production schedule.",
    "D": "obtain employees' input.",
    "answer": "D: obtain employees' input.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of investing in a savings account:?",
    "A": "The rate of return doesn't keep up with inflation.",
    "B": "A minimum balance is required to keep the account active.",
    "C": "You must pay a penalty for withdrawing your money early.",
    "D": "There is a high potential for loss.",
    "answer": "A: The rate of return doesn't keep up with inflation.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tuition reimbursement is a way to combat the problem of limited",
    "A": "natural resources.",
    "B": "human resources.",
    "C": "capital goods.",
    "D": "consumer goods.",
    "answer": "B: human resources.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determine which function of marketing addresses the following question: Is the product pac kaged appropriately?",
    "A": "Product/Service management",
    "B": "Selling",
    "C": "Marketing-information management",
    "D": "Pricing",
    "answer": "A: Product/Service management",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Following up with customers when the product they ordered is delivered and used will often result in",
    "A": "intervention by your supervisor.",
    "B": "frustration for you and the customer.",
    "C": "repeat orders.",
    "D": "returned merchandise.",
    "answer": "C: repeat orders.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of Boris's coworkers at a deli cuts himself on the meat slicer. What should Boris do to help his coworker?",
    "A": "Attempt to treat the wound.",
    "B": "Stay as calm as possible.",
    "C": "Evacuate the room.",
    "D": "Allow his emotions to take over.",
    "answer": "B: Stay as calm as possible.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Anna's boss frequently demanded that she work late, even though she would not be paid for her overti me hours. Because of this, Anna lost respect for her boss and decided to look for a new job. This example demonstrates",
    "A": "how fairness has little impact on decision-making.",
    "B": "how fairness is important to professional relationships.",
    "C": "how the justice approach to fairness is limited.",
    "D": "how a lack of empathy undermines equality.",
    "answer": "B: how fairness is important to professional relationships.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is responsible for making sure that a business is a healthy, hazard-free place t o work that complies with government regulations?",
    "A": "The employer",
    "B": "Employees",
    "C": "The government",
    "D": "Local law enforcement",
    "answer": "A: The employer",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the co-signer of a bank loan legally responsible to pay if the borrower defau lts on the loan?",
    "A": "The interest amount owed only",
    "B": "The principle amount owed only",
    "C": "The balance of the loan owed",
    "D": "The original amount of the loan",
    "answer": "C: The balance of the loan owed",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To prevent injuries when operating machinery, it is important to",
    "A": "know standard first aid.",
    "B": "purchase the most efficient equipment.",
    "C": "purchase the newest equipment.",
    "D": "follow the instruction manual.",
    "answer": "D: follow the instruction manual.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Obtaining a line of goods for use in a business is one of the functions of",
    "A": "controlling.",
    "B": "selling.",
    "C": "organizing.",
    "D": "purchasing.",
    "answer": "D: purchasing.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which amount listed on a paycheck stub represents an employee's actual take-home pay?",
    "A": "Regular pay C. Overtime pay",
    "B": "Gross pay D. Net pay Test 1251 BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CORE EXAM 6 57. Lalita receives a check as a birthday gift. Before she deposits it in the bank, she signs her name on the back of the check in black ink. Lalita is __________ the check. A. writing",
    "C": "endorsing B. registering",
    "D": "withdrawing",
    "answer": "D: withdrawing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an ethical issue:?",
    "A": "Deciding whether to have french fries or a salad",
    "B": "Deciding whether to lie to a friend",
    "C": "Choosing between buying a new shirt or a new book",
    "D": "Choosing which movie to see this weekend",
    "answer": "B: Deciding whether to lie to a friend",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an example of a job title in corporate finance?",
    "A": "Product manager",
    "B": "Accountant",
    "C": "Salesperson",
    "D": "Credit analyst",
    "answer": "D: Credit analyst",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should employees be willing to accept when defending their ideas objectively?",
    "A": "Nonverbal support",
    "B": "Additional responsibility",
    "C": "Critical feedback",
    "D": "Personal attack",
    "answer": "C: Critical feedback",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Michael is a financial manager at his company. He needs to decide which project the company should invest in, so he estimates each potential project's value to the business. What process is Michael using?",
    "A": "The cash conversion cycle",
    "B": "Capital budgeting",
    "C": "Working capital management",
    "D": "Capital structure",
    "answer": "B: Capital budgeting",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The people who are impacted by a project in any way are called",
    "A": "workers.",
    "B": "team members.",
    "C": "customers.",
    "D": "stakeholders.",
    "answer": "D: stakeholders.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To be able to explain and defend their ideas objectively to others, individuals usually need to have effective __________ skills.",
    "A": "technical",
    "B": "verbal",
    "C": "reading",
    "D": "computer",
    "answer": "B: verbal",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should change leaders do after they're done leading a change?",
    "A": "Celebrate success.",
    "B": "Address resistance.",
    "C": "Explain why the change was necessary.",
    "D": "Create a communication plan.",
    "answer": "A: Celebrate success.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Choosing to buy an item at the check-out counter is often an example of",
    "A": "impulsive spending.",
    "B": "poor use of credit.",
    "C": "financial self-control.",
    "D": "smart shopping.",
    "answer": "A: impulsive spending.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of informal workplace communication:?",
    "A": "A project manager develops a production schedule to distribute to the project team.",
    "B": "Two coworkers share their opinions about a new work project during a coffee break.",
    "C": "A human resources manager conducts a training session for new employees.",
    "D": "The president of the Cantrell Corporation announces expansion plans in a press release.",
    "answer": "B: Two coworkers share their opinions about a new work project during a coffee break.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because operations managers control so much of a business's money, they must focus on",
    "A": "keeping costs low.",
    "B": "hiring the best employees.",
    "C": "creating effective advertising campaigns.",
    "D": "generating publicity.",
    "answer": "A: keeping costs low.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Gina has been called into a meeting while composing an important email message. So Gina will not need to delete and retype the message after the meeting, she should save th e message as a",
    "A": "reply.",
    "B": "draft.",
    "C": "postscript.",
    "D": "flagged response.",
    "answer": "B: draft.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following individuals is showing empathy:?",
    "A": "Victoria listens carefully to what others say.",
    "B": "Rico likes to say exactly what he thinks.",
    "C": "Bret prefers not to share his experiences.",
    "D": "Nikki is a very quiet person who keeps to herself.",
    "answer": "A: Victoria listens carefully to what others say.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the most effective methods of locating job leads is asking for tips from",
    "A": "retirees.",
    "B": "nonworkers.",
    "C": "friends.",
    "D": "minors.",
    "answer": "C: friends.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jennifer is a person who exhibits self-control in difficult situations. She alw ays remains calm, is patient, empathetic, and a good listener. Her self-control helps her",
    "A": "avoid a factual response.",
    "B": "express a negative reaction.",
    "C": "have a positive attitude.",
    "D": "react in a defensive manner.",
    "answer": "C: have a positive attitude.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following actions would most likely be taken by an organized employee:?",
    "A": "Having coworkers prioritize workload",
    "B": "Thriving on tight deadlines",
    "C": "Asking for help to complete tasks",
    "D": "Planning work ahead of time",
    "answer": "D: Planning work ahead of time",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following documents will allow the beneficiary of an estate to avoid probat e:?",
    "A": "Will",
    "B": "Living will",
    "C": "Living trust",
    "D": "Power of attorney",
    "answer": "C: Living trust",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a limit to economic freedom in a private enterprise system:?",
    "A": "Pricing systems",
    "B": "Profit motive",
    "C": "Personal choices",
    "D": "Private property",
    "answer": "C: Personal choices",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If you and your teammates cooperate with eac h other and you feel like you're \"all in this together,\" you benefit from shared",
    "A": "reflection.",
    "B": "competition.",
    "C": "innovation.",
    "D": "accountability.",
    "answer": "D: accountability.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If Diedra wants to open a savings account to save money for her dream vacation, she should place her money in a deposit-taking institution, such as a(n)",
    "A": "investm ent bank or mortgage company.",
    "B": "savings and loan bank or investment bank.",
    "C": "commercial bank or credit union.",
    "D": "mortgage company or credit union.",
    "answer": "C: commercial bank or credit union.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In which of the following situations would a businessperson write a persuasive inquiry using an indirect format:",
    "A": "A memo asking for a detailed sales report for the previous 6-month period",
    "B": "A letter requesting the date and time of a professional development workshop",
    "C": "An email message requesting membership eligibility requirements in an organization",
    "D": "A direct-mail letter asking for financial support to help a charitable organization",
    "answer": "D: A direct-mail letter asking for financial support to help a charitable organization",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a basic belief necessary to the development of assertiveness:?",
    "A": "I have the right to pressure you into changing your mind.",
    "B": "I have the right to decide how others will respond to me.",
    "C": "I have the right to express my feelings and opinions in any way I choose.",
    "D": "I have the right to ask others to respond to my needs.",
    "answer": "D: I have the right to ask others to respond to my needs.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cara hasn't met Joan, but she doesn't want to work with her. Cara believes that because Joan is a blonde, she is probably ditzy and won't do her sh are of the work. What does Cara need to learn about herself?",
    "A": "Cara is open-minded and fair.",
    "B": "Cara tolerates others' faults.",
    "C": "Cara is a good judge of people.",
    "D": "Cara stereotypes other people.",
    "answer": "D: Cara stereotypes other people.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your friend Maureen is nervous about an upcoming staff meeting at her company. Since you have a lot of experience attending and participating in meetings, she asks you for advice. You tell her that she should be sure to",
    "A": "keep quiet if she disagrees with someone else's point.",
    "B": "listen and look interested when someone is speaking.",
    "C": "think about what she will say while others are speaking.",
    "D": "take the opportunity to bring up unrelated concerns she has.",
    "answer": "B: listen and look interested when someone is speaking.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements regarding company policies is true:?",
    "A": "Company policies identify very specific employee actions.",
    "B": "Company policies and procedures are the same thing.",
    "C": "Company policies describe emergency measures.",
    "D": "Company policies identify general company rules.",
    "answer": "D: Company policies identify general company rules.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you know what your values are and align your behavior with them, you will?",
    "A": "feel conflicted in your decision-making.",
    "B": "be able to set prioriti es and goals easily.",
    "C": "find fulfillment in career but not personal life.",
    "D": "never again struggle with an ethical dilemma.",
    "answer": "B: be able to set prioriti es and goals easily.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Compounding can be described as",
    "A": "earning interest upon interest.",
    "B": "avoiding inflation.",
    "C": "risking the stock market.",
    "D": "meeting financial needs.",
    "answer": "A: earning interest upon interest.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of job shadowing:?",
    "A": "Tom asks an advertising manager about various professional organizations in marketing.",
    "B": "Kayla follows the public relations director of a local company to learn about their career.",
    "C": "Delia talks with an eve nt coordinator about the ways in which she can donate her time to a local charity.",
    "D": "Brian sets up a time to meet with a sales representative to find out about their job duties.",
    "answer": "B: Kayla follows the public relations director of a local company to learn about their career.",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If you want to avoid excessive debt, which of the following actions should you take:",
    "A": "Create a budget, and stick to it.",
    "B": "Avoid big purchases unless they're impulse buys.",
    "C": "Pay the minimum payment due each month on your credit card.",
    "D": "Use a credit card for purchases you can't afford.",
    "answer": "A: Create a budget, and stick to it.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important to read and reconcile bank statements?",
    "A": "To balance an account",
    "B": "To calculate interest",
    "C": "To withdraw excess money",
    "D": "To make a deposit",
    "answer": "A: To balance an account",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Special events, demonstrations, contests, and coupons are activities that are controlled by a business's __________ policie s.",
    "A": "employee",
    "B": "promotional",
    "C": "service",
    "D": "product",
    "answer": "B: promotional",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When doing business with clients from another culture, you should always be sure to?",
    "A": "always speak English, since it's considered the international language of business.",
    "B": "take the opportunity to tell the other person how you do things in your culture.",
    "C": "use humor to ease tension and make everyone more comfortable.",
    "D": "research the culture and history of the people with whom you're doing business.",
    "answer": "D: research the culture and history of the people with whom you're doing business.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a coworker is upset, Alexis tries to see things from their point of view. Alexis is demonstrating?",
    "A": "empathy.",
    "B": "integrity.",
    "C": "honesty.",
    "D": "transparency.",
    "answer": "A: empathy.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The basic structure of a web page is typically dictated by",
    "A": "JavaScript.",
    "B": "CDML.",
    "C": "online visitors.",
    "D": "HTML.",
    "answer": "D: HTML.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of production would most likely be used to produce prescription glasses?",
    "A": "Robotic",
    "B": "Batch",
    "C": "Mass",
    "D": "Unit",
    "answer": "D: Unit",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following adds meaning to the words a speaker uses:?",
    "A": "Tone of voice",
    "B": "Tempo",
    "C": "Accuracy",
    "D": "Economy of speech",
    "answer": "A: Tone of voice",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lainey figures out that she needs to hire two temporary people to enter data for her new website. Lainey is",
    "A": "planning communications.",
    "B": "developing quality standards.",
    "C": "identifying resources.",
    "D": "keeping the project organized.",
    "answer": "C: identifying resources.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Whether prices go up or down, the relationship between relative prices does not change if the __________ remains the same.",
    "A": "ratio",
    "B": "value",
    "C": "market",
    "D": "resource",
    "answer": "A: ratio",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For her new job, Tasha has been asked to write a report. She has found a website with information regarding her topic. Which of the following would help her identify whether the information on t his site is accurate:",
    "A": "A table of contents",
    "B": "A bibliography",
    "C": "A professional-looking website design",
    "D": "A date of modification less than one year old",
    "answer": "B: A bibliography",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before trying to generate possible solutions to problems, it is essential to identify all of the",
    "A": "consequences.",
    "B": "rewards.",
    "C": "outcomes.",
    "D": "facts.",
    "answer": "D: facts.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of processing a transaction with a debit card:?",
    "A": "When Naomi purchased office supplies, she presented the cashier with a card that automatically withdrew funds from her business's checking account.",
    "B": "Tyler provided his card number and expiration date to the online travel agency so he c ould obtain his airline tickets now and receive his bill for the tickets later.",
    "C": "After Ava finished her meal at an upscale restaurant, she presented the server with a card that provided Ava with a special discount off her bill.",
    "D": "Jayden purchased a new video game from Great Deal Electronics using a store-issued card",
    "answer": "A: When Naomi purchased office supplies, she presented the cashier with a card that automatically withdrew funds from her business's checking account.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first step to problem-solving in a group?",
    "A": "Implementing solutions C. Determining causes of the problem",
    "B": "Assessing solutions D. Defining the problem 17. An employee approaches a regular customer who appears to be looking for a specific item and says, \"Good morni ng, Mr. Hinkle, may I direct you to a particular product?\" Is this the most appropriate way to deal with that customer? A. Yes, employees should be well informed and able to help customers. B. No, employees are too busy to pay attention to only one custom er.",
    "C": "Yes, employees should always greet customers and call them by name.",
    "D": "No, employees are not expected to have conversations with customers.",
    "answer": "D: No, employees are not expected to have conversations with customers.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Integrity, trust, and accountability are examples of",
    "A": "technical skills.",
    "B": "ethical situations.",
    "C": "ethical principles.",
    "D": "consequences.",
    "answer": "C: ethical principles.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Important functions of a business's information system are to help it __________ its important facts and data.",
    "A": "organize and store",
    "B": "mediate and retrieve",
    "C": "duplicate and renew",
    "D": "analyze and instruct",
    "answer": "A: organize and store",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "According to the marketing concept, which option demonstrates customer orientation?",
    "A": "Advertising the features of a product",
    "B": "Convincing a buyer to buy",
    "C": "Finding out what a buyer wants",
    "D": "Researching a firm's competitors",
    "answer": "C: Finding out what a buyer wants",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Some businesses use an automatic reorder system to maintain an adequate",
    "A": "inventory of supplies.",
    "B": "work environment.",
    "C": "budget for expenses.",
    "D": "maintenance system.",
    "answer": "A: inventory of supplies.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a leader wants people to believe what they say and follow them, they must demonstrate",
    "A": "self-awareness.",
    "B": "competence.",
    "C": "the ability to share a vision.",
    "D": "decisiveness.",
    "answer": "B: competence.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a benefit of behaving ethically?",
    "A": "Tense relationships with customers",
    "B": "Decreased organizational productivity",
    "C": "Better, easier decision-making",
    "D": "Increased risk of legal trouble",
    "answer": "C: Better, easier decision-making",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a risk of being uninsured:?",
    "A": "Possible tax penalties",
    "B": "Increased premiums",
    "C": "Lower deductibles",
    "D": "Hospitals refusing care",
    "answer": "A: Possible tax penalties",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an informational message geared toward an external audienc e:?",
    "A": "An inventory report",
    "B": "An employee handbook",
    "C": "A print advertisement",
    "D": "An office calendar",
    "answer": "C: A print advertisement",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is appropriate for a participant to ask questions during a staff meeting when",
    "A": "s/he does not agree with the speaker. C. the agenda is being distributed.",
    "B": "another participant is speaking. D. s/he needs a poi nt clarified. 17. What is it important for an applicant to do during a job interview in order to be able to answer questions adequately? A. Respond quickly",
    "C": "Listen carefully B. Talk rapidly",
    "D": "Dress appropriately",
    "answer": "D: Dress appropriately",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Matthew and Miranda are equal partners in a small consulting firm. They have allocated 8% of last year's profits to make business improvements. Matthew wants to purchase a new copy machine, while Miranda would rather paint the building and make it look mor e inviting to their clients. What is the reason for Matthew and Miranda's conflict?",
    "A": "Authority",
    "B": "Inconsistent behavior",
    "C": "Limited resources",
    "D": "Unclear boundaries",
    "answer": "C: Limited resources",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determine whether the following statement is true or false: Employees must be taught how to use equipment properly and the potential dangers of not doing so.?",
    "A": "True; well-trained employees always use safety precautions.",
    "B": "False; employees know which equipment is dangerous and which is not.",
    "C": "True; the business is responsible for creating a safe work environment.",
    "D": "False; employees understand the hazards of misusing equipment.",
    "answer": "C: True; the business is responsible for creating a safe work environment.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following addresses employees' right to not be bullied in the workplace:?",
    "A": "Right to a safe work environment",
    "B": "Right to complain without retaliation",
    "C": "Right to union activity",
    "D": "Right to nondiscriminatory promotion practices",
    "answer": "A: Right to a safe work environment",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Taking responsibility for your team's success or failure in achieving the vision is part of a team leader",
    "A": "being enthusiastic.",
    "B": "establishing good working relationships.",
    "C": "being an example.",
    "D": "being a good listener.",
    "answer": "C: being an example.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The personnel office of a business carefully checks the background and references of its job appli cants. This is an example of handling business risks through",
    "A": "prevention.",
    "B": "retention.",
    "C": "avoidance.",
    "D": "transfer.",
    "answer": "A: prevention.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jeff is a data analyst at a consumer research company. When he needs to access a certain document, he knows exactly where and how to find it. This is an example of how information management helps businesses",
    "A": "save time and money.",
    "B": "maintain cre dibility.",
    "C": "comply with laws.",
    "D": "serve customers more effectively.",
    "answer": "A: save time and money.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an effective subject line for a professional email:?",
    "A": "New product information",
    "B": "Can we talk for a minute?",
    "C": "One more thing...",
    "D": "Mtg. rescheduled for 3 p.m.",
    "answer": "D: Mtg. rescheduled for 3 p.m.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Employees can most successfully navigate office politics and prevent unnecessary drama by",
    "A": "avoiding close relationships with coworkers.",
    "B": "staying to themselves and not talking to others.",
    "C": "refusing to spread false rumors around the office.",
    "D": "keeping concerns about the workplace to themselves.",
    "answer": "C: refusing to spread false rumors around the office.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Arnie needs to buy printer toner and copy paper from the company's office-supply vendor. What is the first step that Arnie should take?",
    "A": "Submit a receipt C. Prepare a purchase order",
    "B": "Request an invoice D. Complete an expense form 87. Why does Dan order extra copy paper, Post-it notes, and printer ink cartridges for the department when he places an order for office supplies? A. To meet minimal expectations",
    "C": "To prevent stockouts B. To ensure product quality",
    "D": "To reduce the need to forecast",
    "answer": "C: To prevent stockouts B. To ensure product quality",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a benefit that individuals receive from following rules of conduct:?",
    "A": "Increased organizational communication",
    "B": "Protection from consequences",
    "C": "Less ethical guidance",
    "D": "Increased financial compensation",
    "answer": "B: Protection from consequences",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do advertising agency account executives often participate in meetings and problem-solvi ng groups?",
    "A": "To place ads in local newspapers",
    "B": "To schedule production facilities",
    "C": "To develop ad campaigns for clients",
    "D": "To write copy for promotional brochures",
    "answer": "C: To develop ad campaigns for clients",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Among other factors, lenders generally evaluate __________ to determine a potential borrower's ability to repay debt.",
    "A": "bank addresses",
    "B": "credit reports",
    "C": "insurance premiums",
    "D": "credit unions",
    "answer": "B: credit reports",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One principle of good business-letter writing is to use",
    "A": "popular clich\u00e9s.",
    "B": "long paragraphs.",
    "C": "clear language.",
    "D": "minimum organization.",
    "answer": "C: clear language.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When we see a traffic light change from red to green, we know that it is time to go. This is an example of how?",
    "A": "we struggle to understand the nuances of human behavior.",
    "B": "our instinct to categorize people and things keeps us safe.",
    "C": "stereotypes are always negative and insulting to others.",
    "D": "everyone is affected by unconscious bias.",
    "answer": "B: our instinct to categorize people and things keeps us safe.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Individuals who respect their own personal rights, as well as the rights of others, have deve loped",
    "A": "passiveness.",
    "B": "defensiveness.",
    "C": "assertiveness.",
    "D": "aggressiveness.",
    "answer": "C: assertiveness.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Cypress wants to find out the estimated growth potential for marketing professionals over the next 10 years.\nWhich of the following sources will provide Cypress with the most relevant and up-to-date statistics:",
    "A": "Social media webinar",
    "B": "Career textbook",
    "C": "News magazine",
    "D": "Government website",
    "answer": "D: Government website",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Making both buyers and sellers feel they are getting good value is part of the __________ function of\nmarketing.",
    "A": "pricing",
    "B": "financing",
    "C": "promotion",
    "D": "purchasing",
    "answer": "A: pricing",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business has too much inventory on hand for an extended period of time, what type of business cost increases?",
    "A": "Holding",
    "B": "Stockout",
    "C": "Production",
    "D": "Maintenance",
    "answer": "A: Holding",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a way that accidents are costly to employees:?",
    "A": "Lost production",
    "B": "Expensive repairs",
    "C": "Lost income",
    "D": "Decreased sales",
    "answer": "C: Lost income",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way in which the government helps protect business property is by",
    "A": "setting tariffs.",
    "B": "granting subsidies.",
    "C": "issuing bonds.",
    "D": "registering trademarks.",
    "answer": "D: registering trademarks.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mark makes $52,000 a year. Looking at his pay stub, he sees he earned $1,000 this week and gets to take $800 of it home. The $1,000 Mark earned this week is his",
    "A": "gross income.",
    "B": "net income.",
    "C": "budget.",
    "D": "salary.",
    "answer": "A: gross income.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Banks and credit unions profit from which of the following items when issuing credit cards:",
    "A": "Principal",
    "B": "Interest",
    "C": "Stocks",
    "D": "Invoices",
    "answer": "B: Interest",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jhenae just realized she failed to do an important and difficult task her boss had assigned to her. The task needs to be completed by tomorrow morning. What should Jhenae do to show she has initiative?",
    "A": "Ask her boss to extend the deadline",
    "B": "Ask her teammates to help complete it",
    "C": "Complete what she can before her work shift is over",
    "D": "Work late to complete it on time",
    "answer": "D: Work late to complete it on time",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you know your own emotions, you are demonstrating?",
    "A": "self-control.",
    "B": "self-awareness.",
    "C": "social relationships.",
    "D": "social restraint.",
    "answer": "B: self-awareness.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Qualified employees who behave unethically on the job may harm themselves by being",
    "A": "rotated to similar positions.",
    "B": "sent to a training program.",
    "C": "held legally responsible.",
    "D": "passed over for promotions.",
    "answer": "D: passed over for promotions.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Offering to provide additional information after a job interview is often the function of a(n)",
    "A": "telephone call.",
    "B": "follow-up letter.",
    "C": "handwritten note.",
    "D": "email question.",
    "answer": "B: follow-up letter.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Bill, Tara, and Lauren work for a small manufacturing firm that produces designer jeans. Bill is the fabric buyer; Tara buys the small items needed to construct the jeans; and Lauren sews the jeans. What does Lauren need from Bill and Tara to do her job?",
    "A": "Thread, buttons, and zippers from Tara and denim from Bill",
    "B": "Zippers, buttons and snaps from Tara and corduroy from Bill",
    "C": "Buttons, thread, and denim from Bill and zippers from Tara",
    "D": "Corduroy from Tara and zippers, snaps, and pins from Bill",
    "answer": "A: Thread, buttons, and zippers from Tara and denim from Bill",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is appropriate to use slang during conversation when you are",
    "A": "meeting with a new customer.",
    "B": "socializing with close friends.",
    "C": "interviewing for a job.",
    "D": "being introduced to a new coworker.",
    "answer": "B: socializing with close friends.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a capital good:?",
    "A": "A hot dog purchased at the stadium",
    "B": "A printing press purchased by a newspaper",
    "C": "A cap and gown rented for graduation",
    "D": "A shirt monogrammed with your initials",
    "answer": "B: A printing press purchased by a newspaper",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first step in the staffing process?",
    "A": "Determining need",
    "B": "Hiring",
    "C": "Interviewing",
    "D": "Recruiting",
    "answer": "A: Determining need",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What kind of insurance combines death benefits with a savings and investment account?",
    "A": "Ordinary life",
    "B": "Term",
    "C": "Liability",
    "D": "Homeowner's",
    "answer": "A: Ordinary life",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Written communication is less effective when readers must",
    "A": "find the information they need within the communication.",
    "B": "follow the writer's logical train of thought.",
    "C": "work to understand what the communication means.",
    "D": "spend a minimum amount of time reading the communication.",
    "answer": "C: work to understand what the communication means.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To protect yourself against identity theft, you shoul d",
    "A": "write down all of your important passwords on paper.",
    "B": "throw away credit card receipts in public trash cans.",
    "C": "maintain at least six different credit cards in your name.",
    "D": "avoid providing sensitive information via telephone.",
    "answer": "D: avoid providing sensitive information via telephone.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following activities is part of accounting:?",
    "A": "Making decisions based on financial information",
    "B": "Developing marketing campaigns based on financial information",
    "C": "Creating financial information",
    "D": "Gathering financial information",
    "answer": "D: Gathering financial information",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ava doesn't agree with her classmate's opinion, but she listens carefully instead of starting an argument or insulting her. Which ethical principle is Ava illustrating?",
    "A": "Respect",
    "B": "Integrity",
    "C": "Transparency",
    "D": "Trust",
    "answer": "A: Respect",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way to develop an achievement orientation is to establish",
    "A": "personal relationships.",
    "B": "flexible deadlines.",
    "C": "reachable goals.",
    "D": "safe conditions.",
    "answer": "C: reachable goals.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Every time you spend money on yourself, you expose yourself to",
    "A": "future debt.",
    "B": "relational risk.",
    "C": "financial risk.",
    "D": "poverty.",
    "answer": "C: financial risk.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Dara is using Google to locate information on the Internet about her research report topic. She is using a search",
    "A": "machine.",
    "B": "engine.",
    "C": "technology.",
    "D": "group.",
    "answer": "B: engine.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Caroline explains the company's rules of conduct to a new employee, she should also expl ain?",
    "A": "who developed the rules.",
    "B": "the specific reasons for having all the rules.",
    "C": "the consequences of breaking the rules.",
    "D": "when the rules were implemented.",
    "answer": "C: the consequences of breaking the rules.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The opening sentences of an effective business letter should",
    "A": "be completely impersonal.",
    "B": "come right to the point.",
    "C": "always be formal.",
    "D": "avoid specific details.",
    "answer": "B: come right to the point.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It's important to look at ethical dilemmas as",
    "A": "negatives.",
    "B": "challenges.",
    "C": "opportunities.",
    "D": "experiments.",
    "answer": "C: opportunities.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following often presents an opportunity for current employees to be considered for a promotion:?",
    "A": "Occupation is high paying.",
    "B": "Entry-level job is available.",
    "C": "New position is created.",
    "D": "Career is being revised.",
    "answer": "C: New position is created.",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following should a person do first when facing the need to make a decisi on:?",
    "A": "Evaluate information",
    "B": "Make a choice",
    "C": "Analyze results",
    "D": "Define the objective",
    "answer": "D: Define the objective",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about writing professional email messages:?",
    "A": "The subject line should concisely describe the topic of the message.",
    "B": "It is appropriate to use all capital letters when the message is urgent.",
    "C": "Because email is an informal communication method, greetings are unnecessary.",
    "D": "It is acceptabl e to use texting acronyms because most businesspeople understand them.",
    "answer": "A: The subject line should concisely describe the topic of the message.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jamal needs to obtain a report from a vendor six months from now. He uses the calendar function in his email program to write a note that will automatically remind him to request the report on a specific date in the future. What is Jamal doing?",
    "A": "Using cloud applications to store important work documents",
    "B": "Managing his productivity by using scheduling applications",
    "C": "Acquiring information by reviewing internet articles and papers",
    "D": "Using project management software to track personal activities",
    "answer": "B: Managing his productivity by using scheduling applications",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a component that is necessary for the production of goods and services:?",
    "A": "Purchasing plans",
    "B": "Research facilities",
    "C": "Natural resources",
    "D": "Tangible items",
    "answer": "C: Natural resources",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a factor that affects a business's selection of policies to guide its operatio ns?",
    "A": "Nature of the business",
    "B": "Personal preferences of management",
    "C": "Communication skills of employees",
    "D": "Space available to display policies",
    "answer": "A: Nature of the business",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should employees in today's changing world do to prevent their skills fro m becoming obsolete?",
    "A": "Change jobs frequently",
    "B": "Modify personal behavior",
    "C": "Delegate responsibility",
    "D": "Continue their education",
    "answer": "D: Continue their education",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When reconciling bank statements, it is important to consider?",
    "A": "services not available online.",
    "B": "the number of transactions.",
    "C": "checks that have not cleared.",
    "D": "the types of payroll deposits.",
    "answer": "C: checks that have not cleared.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an employee who is accepting responsibility for their actions:?",
    "A": "Pete informed the team leader that Brenda's careless ness, rather than his own, was the reason for the inconsistencies in the group's project report.",
    "B": "Cynthia admitted to her supervisor about the billing mistake that she made on the Andrew's account.",
    "C": "Larry decided that he would require Bob to make the decision so Bob would be blamed if something went wrong.",
    "D": "Emily realized that she forgot to lock the warehouse door on the night that the equipment was stolen, and",
    "answer": "B: Cynthia admitted to her supervisor about the billing mistake that she made on the Andrew's account.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Althea just received her first paycheck at work. She's excited, but as she looks at her pay stub, she gets\nconfused. She wants to know how much money she made in this pay period, but there are so many different\nnumbers. If Althea wants to know how much money will actually be deposited in her bank a ccount, she shoul d\nlook at the",
    "A": "federal income tax.",
    "B": "gross pay.",
    "C": "net pay.",
    "D": "state tax.",
    "answer": "C: net pay.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tim works as an accounts-receivable clerk at a large law firm. In the past week, he has had problems with the computer system freezing up, crashing, and losing data. To work toward resolving the pro blem, Tim needs to talk with his manager. Tim's manager is most likely to be",
    "A": "Juan Sanchez, the payroll specialist.",
    "B": "Cynthia Sanford, the vice president of finance.",
    "C": "Samantha Beckham, the accounts-payable clerk.",
    "D": "Bob Crawley, the accounting manager.",
    "answer": "D: Bob Crawley, the accounting manager.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You've been asked to attend a meeting with an organization's board of directors to convince them to buy your company's customer relationship management software. Which of the following best describes the type of information you should provi de and how you should prepare it:",
    "A": "Create a brief marketing message to generate interest in the software.",
    "B": "Write a lengthy report that includes all of the technical details regarding the software you are recommending.",
    "C": "Create a custom slideshow presentation that explains how the software program will benefit the client.",
    "D": "Create a storyboard to share an exciting visual message about your software.",
    "answer": "C: Create a custom slideshow presentation that explains how the software program will benefit the client.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an effective way to support and encourage someone who is talking to you?",
    "A": "Avoid making any noise while the speaker is talking",
    "B": "Interrupt the speaker to debate what s/he has said",
    "C": "Clap as the speaker makes each of her/his main points",
    "D": "Make comments such as \"yes\" or \"I see\" occasionally",
    "answer": "D: Make comments such as \"yes\" or \"I see\" occasionally",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Mason Publishing included the following statement in a newsletter that was sent to its sales staff about its new tablet: CEO Lucinda Marcelli said, \"This product supports our ongoing efforts to revolutionize the ways in which students across the country learn.\" This is an example of",
    "A": "paraphrasing a comment to explain specific product benefits.",
    "B": "including a quotation to introduce an item during a sales meeting.",
    "C": "using a quotation to communicate product information.",
    "D": "summarizing the features of a new item by using a testimonial.",
    "answer": "C: using a quotation to communicate product information.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Thor's supervisor provides only general guidance, avoids giving specific or detailed directions, and wants employees to function independently. What leadership style is the supervisor following?",
    "A": "Authoritarian",
    "B": "Democratic",
    "C": "Assertive",
    "D": "Laissez-faire",
    "answer": "D: Laissez-faire",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do creative people tend to be more tolerant of ambiguity?",
    "A": "Ambiguity limits the ability to be expressive.",
    "B": "Uncertainty is an opportunity to be imaginative.",
    "C": "Creative people have more ambiguity in their lives.",
    "D": "Creative people tend to be less judgmental.",
    "answer": "B: Uncertainty is an opportunity to be imaginative.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Projects need to be __________ to their stakeholders so that those individuals will want to work with you again.",
    "A": "on schedule",
    "B": "interesting",
    "C": "challenging",
    "D": "meaningful",
    "answer": "D: meaningful",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following things should an employer do to prevent security breaches from oc curring:?",
    "A": "Allow all employees to have access to personal information.",
    "B": "There is no way to prevent security breaches from occurring.",
    "C": "Store information on highly secure computer systems.",
    "D": "Collect complete personal information from customers.",
    "answer": "C: Store information on highly secure computer systems.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true about the concept of price:?",
    "A": "Buyers and sellers have the same objectives.",
    "B": "Excess supply causes a decrease in price.",
    "C": "Consumer goods are almost always sold at the equilibrium price.",
    "D": "Rationing determines the rise and fall of prices.",
    "answer": "B: Excess supply causes a decrease in price.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Administrative support, operations management, and human resources management are types of __________ careers.",
    "A": "agriculture, food, and natural resources",
    "B": "government and public administration",
    "C": "science, technology, engineering, and mathematics",
    "D": "business management and administration",
    "answer": "D: business management and administration",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following people best demonstrates commitment to his/her job:?",
    "A": "Shay does the bare minimum amount of work to get by.",
    "B": "A manager insists that everyone arrive at the exact same time.",
    "C": "Aria agrees to work late to reach an important deadline.",
    "D": "Rob ignores meeting requests when he does not want to go.",
    "answer": "C: Aria agrees to work late to reach an important deadline.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of difficult customer may be the most trying on your patience and do the m ost damage to the image of your business?",
    "A": "Slow/Methodical",
    "B": "Domineering/Superior",
    "C": "Suspicious",
    "D": "Disagreeable",
    "answer": "D: Disagreeable",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a formatting characteristic of a full-block business letter:?",
    "A": "Double-spacing within the paragraph",
    "B": "No paragraph indents",
    "C": "Indented first paragraph",
    "D": "Paragraphs use right justification",
    "answer": "B: No paragraph indents",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The most flexible document within a project plan is the",
    "A": "risk-management plan.",
    "B": "project schedule.",
    "C": "project scope.",
    "D": "quality-management plan.",
    "answer": "B: project schedule.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One woman has an expensive car, lives in a luxury apartment, and takes frequent vacations. Her friend has two small children and lives on a modest income. These factors account for the differences in the women's",
    "A": "personalities.",
    "B": "job positions.",
    "C": "educations.",
    "D": "lifestyles.",
    "answer": "D: lifestyles.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following policies are designed to protect employees and customers from harm:?",
    "A": "Health and safety policies",
    "B": "Social media policies",
    "C": "Disciplinary policies",
    "D": "Leave policies",
    "answer": "A: Health and safety policies",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following marketing functions helps businesses answer the question \" Where will the products be offered?\"?",
    "A": "Channel management C. Promotion",
    "B": "Selling D. Product/Service management 69. You're writing a paper on the latest developments in vaccines. What type of information should you consult? A. Current",
    "C": "Controversi al B. Historical",
    "D": "Fictional",
    "answer": "A: Channel management C. Promotion",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Martha has been working with a customer on a printer purchase for the past 45 minutes. The customer has looked at all of the printers several times and still is not sure which one to purchase. With what type of customer is Martha working?",
    "A": "Disagreeable",
    "B": "Suspicious",
    "C": "Dishonest",
    "D": "Indecisive",
    "answer": "D: Indecisive",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Assertive people are direct and upfront rather than being",
    "A": "respectful.",
    "B": "considerate.",
    "C": "manipulative.",
    "D": "talkative.",
    "answer": "C: manipulative.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Penelope wants to use an interactive channel to communicate with her employees. Which cha nnel of communication should she choose?",
    "A": "A phone call",
    "B": "A voice mail",
    "C": "A letter",
    "D": "A report",
    "answer": "A: A phone call",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hannah attends a Greek festival in her town. She's showing cultural s ensitivity by",
    "A": "building friendships.",
    "B": "communicating.",
    "C": "being flexible and patient.",
    "D": "educating herself.",
    "answer": "D: educating herself.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of paradigm innovation:?",
    "A": "Energy-saving light bulbs",
    "B": "Windows computer operating system",
    "C": "The latest model of the Honda Civic",
    "D": "Rechargeable batteries",
    "answer": "B: Windows computer operating system",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Team leaders enlisting others in working toward a shared vision must remember that com munication",
    "A": "is not important in a team setting.",
    "B": "is more important than collaboration.",
    "C": "only involves conveying the vision to team members.",
    "D": "involves being receptive to feedback.",
    "answer": "D: involves being receptive to feedback.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true of good investment brokers:?",
    "A": "They are an investor's personal link to the stock exchange.",
    "B": "Most of them are research analysts.",
    "C": "They are responsible for making sure the investor makes money.",
    "D": "They control an investor's money.",
    "answer": "A: They are an investor's personal link to the stock exchange.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is the primary purpose of word-processing software programs:?",
    "A": "To arrange numerical data",
    "B": "To create text documents",
    "C": "To maintain tables of data",
    "D": "To store business records",
    "answer": "B: To create text documents",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the advantages to a business of having a centralized purchasing structure is that",
    "A": "the business can get better prices and services for quantity purchases.",
    "B": "purchasing authority is shared by all departments.",
    "C": "it is efficient for a business with several production facilities.",
    "D": "it helps to eliminate confusion for vendors.",
    "answer": "A: the business can get better prices and services for quantity purchases.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Alma is preparing a presentation about her department's budget to make to the company president. She wants to use a visual representation of the budget that shows parts in relation to the whole. Alma should consider using a",
    "A": "line graph.",
    "B": "pie chart.",
    "C": "bar graph.",
    "D": "table.",
    "answer": "B: pie chart.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If customers feel that a product's price is too high, they will probably",
    "A": "call the Better Business Bureau.",
    "B": "buy less of the product.",
    "C": "make a formal complaint.",
    "D": "try to negotiate the price.",
    "answer": "B: buy less of the product.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What can businesses do during an orientation session to help new employees feel comfortable in the workplace?",
    "A": "Introduce them to other employees",
    "B": "Emphasize the company's discipline policies",
    "C": "Provide copies of performance reviews",
    "D": "Give them a complex project to complete",
    "answer": "A: Introduce them to other employees",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "At home, Bill uses Firefox to view web pages. At work, he uses Google Chrome to look at the same pages. These software programs that \"translate\" HTML-encoded files into websites that Bill can read are examples of",
    "A": "search engines. C. listservs.",
    "B": "uniform resource locators. D. browsers. Test 1251 BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CORE EXAM 8 77. A database q uery allows a user to retrieve business records that contain A. the same criteria.",
    "C": "random statistics. B. different values.",
    "D": "dissimilar information.",
    "answer": "D: dissimilar information.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Centralized retail buying can become ineffective for a large chain when",
    "A": "purchasing responsibility is shared by buyers.",
    "B": "its stores are divided into districts.",
    "C": "all buying is carried out at one location.",
    "D": "its stores are located very far apart.",
    "answer": "D: its stores are located very far apart.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Gillian is a customer service associate for a small retailer. Which of the following would be an effective method for Gillian to prepare herself to handle customer inquiries:",
    "A": "Learn how to transfer calls t o upper management",
    "B": "Learn how to refer customers to online support forums",
    "C": "Become knowledgeable about local restaurants and entertainment",
    "D": "Become knowledgeable about her company's products and policies",
    "answer": "D: Become knowledgeable about her company's products and policies",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is most likely to be a result of competition:?",
    "A": "More monopolies",
    "B": "Reduction in product quality",
    "C": "High prices",
    "D": "Development of new products",
    "answer": "D: Development of new products",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Individuals can improve their chances of making a good first impression on others by",
    "A": "using street slang in conversation.",
    "B": "doing all the talking.",
    "C": "wearing dressy clothes at all times.",
    "D": "sitting up straight.",
    "answer": "D: sitting up straight.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To be an effective team member, an employee needs to be willing to",
    "A": "collaborate with others.",
    "B": "take on all jobs.",
    "C": "provide insensitive feedback.",
    "D": "withhold their opinions.",
    "answer": "A: collaborate with others.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jasmine owns a boutique on a busy street. Although her shop is small, it gets a lot of foot traf fic, and she has many customers. Which of the following security procedures should Jasmine follow:",
    "A": "Keep a large amount of cash in her cash register at all times.",
    "B": "Have another person present when she opens up in the morning.",
    "C": "Avoid making eye contact with customers who walk into the store.",
    "D": "Keep the lighting dim to create an upscale mood.",
    "answer": "B: Have another person present when she opens up in the morning.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The overall objective of the marketing process is the coordination of the",
    "A": "supply chain and retail outlets.",
    "B": "pricing and promotion of goods and services.",
    "C": "merchandise inventory and advertising plans.",
    "D": "production and consumption of goods and services.",
    "answer": "D: production and consumption of goods and services.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Craig recently opened a new credit card account. Since he's short on cash, he decides to make o nly the minimum payments toward his debt each month. At the end of the year, however, he notices that his overall balance has gone up quite a bit. This is a result of",
    "A": "the cost of credit.",
    "B": "income tax.",
    "C": "social security.",
    "D": "Craig's credit score.",
    "answer": "A: the cost of credit.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is most likely to affect a project's planning process:?",
    "A": "Advertising C. Hiring procedures",
    "B": "Employee benefits D. Budget 85. Which of the followi ng is a corrective action you could take if your project has derailed: A. Refocusing scope",
    "C": "Project failure B. Risk tracking",
    "D": "Stakeholder management",
    "answer": "D: Stakeholder management",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determine whether the following statement is true or false: Companies without an HR department do not\nparticipate in HR management activities.?",
    "A": "False; in companies without HR departments, all employees participate in HR management activities.",
    "B": "False; in companies without HR departments, other managers and supervisors participate in HR\nmanagement activities.",
    "C": "True; smaller companies have no need for HR management.",
    "D": "True; only HR managers can complete these activities.",
    "answer": "B: False; in companies without HR departments, other managers and supervisors participate in HR\nmanagement activities.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After solutions have been identified during a problem-solving meeting at an advertisin g agency, meeting participants should",
    "A": "gather information about the problem.",
    "B": "identify the cause of the problem.",
    "C": "evaluate the solutions.",
    "D": "verify the cause of the problem.",
    "answer": "C: evaluate the solutions.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sasha is tempted to look up the answers to her homework problems. She knows she will not get ca ught, and she doesn't think the homework is helpful. How could you best help Sasha in this situation?",
    "A": "Show her why ethical behavior is valuable to her and others.",
    "B": "Report Sasha's behavior to your teacher.",
    "C": "Follow the rules and hope Sasha notices.",
    "D": "Tell Sasha that you do not approve of her decision to cheat.",
    "answer": "A: Show her why ethical behavior is valuable to her and others.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To endorse a check, the payee must sign his/her name on the",
    "A": "back of the check.",
    "B": "signature block of the check.",
    "C": "check's memo line.",
    "D": "chec k's \"Pay to the order of\" section.",
    "answer": "A: back of the check.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What federal law must businesses follow when they offer revolving charge accounts and s end customers updated statements showing the status of their accounts?",
    "A": "Fair Credit Billing Act",
    "B": "Equal Credit Opportunity Act",
    "C": "Truth-in-Lending Act",
    "D": "Fair and Accurate Credit Transactions Act",
    "answer": "C: Truth-in-Lending Act",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a way that businesses can use financial information:?",
    "A": "To create an economic system C. To conduct focus groups",
    "B": "To select selling strategies D. To identify trends 66. Which of the following is a measure of how well a business generates cash flow: A. Capital structure",
    "C": "Return on capital B. Accounts receivable",
    "D": "Accounts payable",
    "answer": "D: Accounts payable",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following should you be sure to do when taking notes:?",
    "A": "Use correct spelling and grammar.",
    "B": "Write as legibly as possible.",
    "C": "Write in complete sentences.",
    "D": "Try to write down everything the teacher says.",
    "answer": "B: Write as legibly as possible.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Stefanie receives her credit card statement at the end of the month, she sees that she was charged for a down payment on a new car that she hadn't purchased. Which of the following is NOT something she should do:?",
    "A": "Call the car dealership",
    "B": "File a police report",
    "C": "Contact her credit card company",
    "D": "Check her credit report",
    "answer": "A: Call the car dealership",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To gather information about a career in finance, which of the following would be considered a primary source of career information:",
    "A": "Watching a documentary film about finance outsourcing",
    "B": "Reading a magazine article about finance job growth",
    "C": "Examining online reviews of several finance companies",
    "D": "Interviewing a finance director about their work experiences",
    "answer": "D: Interviewing a finance director about their work experiences",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Thoroughly examining a viewpoint requires reading or listening to information from",
    "A": "people that agree with you. C. several different sources.",
    "B": "a single authoritative source. D. politically affiliated sources. 51. Which of the following is a benefit of using your smartphone to make mobile payments when buying something from a brick-and-mortar store: A. Privacy",
    "C": "Convenience B. Accessibility",
    "D": "Standardization",
    "answer": "C: Convenience B. Accessibility",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Zach is inputting numerical data into an electronic worksheet containing a series of rows and col umns. What is Zach creating?",
    "A": "Spreadsheet",
    "B": "Presentation",
    "C": "Web ring",
    "D": "Business letter",
    "answer": "A: Spreadsheet",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "On January 3, Anna mailed her credit card payment, which was due on January 5. The credit card is suer received the payment on January 7. What most likely appeared on Anna's credit card statement th e following month?",
    "A": "Processing charge",
    "B": "Application charge",
    "C": "Late fee",
    "D": "Over-limit fee",
    "answer": "C: Late fee",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Stella has just finished designing the web page for her new business. Next, she needs to selec t a ___________ and register the website's ____________.",
    "A": "hyperlink, modem",
    "B": "web host, domain name",
    "C": "media permit, server",
    "D": "file link, ethernet",
    "answer": "B: web host, domain name",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Heather i s writing a report about a controversial issue-the death penalty. Which of the following sources is a good choice for Heather's research:",
    "A": "A blog post from a professor of economics at Harvard",
    "B": "A press release from a group of anti-death penalty activis ts",
    "C": "An article from a 1995 edition of the New York Times",
    "D": "An article from the current issue of Time magazine",
    "answer": "D: An article from the current issue of Time magazine",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When participating in staff meetings, business employees should be prepare d to?",
    "A": "remain silent.",
    "B": "join in the discussion.",
    "C": "comment on every detail.",
    "D": "argue.",
    "answer": "B: join in the discussion.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An employee notifying a government agency that the business is violating health a nd safety regulations is an example of",
    "A": "reporting noncompliance.",
    "B": "spreading gossip.",
    "C": "unethical behavior.",
    "D": "verbal communication.",
    "answer": "A: reporting noncompliance.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important to start early when planning for retirement?",
    "A": "To take advantage of compounded interest",
    "B": "To beat inflation rates",
    "C": "To benefit from the time value of money",
    "D": "To ensure that protections are in place for retirement plans",
    "answer": "A: To take advantage of compounded interest",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following situations best demonstrates the justice view of fairness:?",
    "A": "The soccer captain lets their best friend skip practice.",
    "B": "Every member of the Spanish Club has to fundraise $100.",
    "C": "All students must finish their exams in the same amount of time.",
    "D": "An employee with a back injury is given a special chair.",
    "answer": "D: An employee with a back injury is given a special chair.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Reese is writing a paper for his business class. He wants to include an idea he found i n one of his sources. He rewrites the main points in his own words, making sure to attribute his ideas to the or iginal source. Reese is",
    "A": "plagiarizing.",
    "B": "paraphrasing.",
    "C": "quoting.",
    "D": "summarizing.",
    "answer": "D: summarizing.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Calling in sick only if you are truly sick is an example of what type of behavior that bu ilds positive working relationships?",
    "A": "Carrying your own weight",
    "B": "Getting to know others on your work team",
    "C": "Having a good attitude",
    "D": "Being cooperative",
    "answer": "A: Carrying your own weight",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In the marketing concept, whose point of view matters most?",
    "A": "Marketer's",
    "B": "Seller's",
    "C": "Planner's",
    "D": "Buyer's",
    "answer": "D: Buyer's",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an effective strategy for identifying important information while reading:?",
    "A": "Skimming the text instead of reading it all word for word",
    "B": "Skipping the preface and introduction to spend more time on the main content",
    "C": "Paying special attention to headings, titles, and graphics",
    "D": "Reading only the first and last paragraphs of the text",
    "answer": "C: Paying special attention to headings, titles, and graphics",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a guideline for developing effective written communication:?",
    "A": "Be thorough.",
    "B": "Be repetitious.",
    "C": "Be wordy.",
    "D": "Be trite.",
    "answer": "A: Be thorough.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In some countries, maintaining eye contact in a conversation is generally considered a sign of respect and engagement. This is an example of a cultural norm regarding",
    "A": "nonverbal cues.",
    "B": "personal space.",
    "C": "verbal cues.",
    "D": "posture.",
    "answer": "A: nonverbal cues.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To influence others to work toward a shared vision, a leader should possess a high level of credibility and should be able to provide supporting",
    "A": "practices.",
    "B": "facts.",
    "C": "assumptions.",
    "D": "skills.",
    "answer": "B: facts.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jeff is a college student who just obtained his first credit card. Which of the following sho uld he NOT do:",
    "A": "Pay his bill on time",
    "B": "Buy more with his card than he can afford",
    "C": "Think of his card as a loan",
    "D": "Track his spending habits",
    "answer": "B: Buy more with his card than he can afford",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a message recipient is frowning and has clenched fists, the emotional response that s/he is mos t likely displaying is",
    "A": "anger.",
    "B": "sadness.",
    "C": "joy.",
    "D": "nervousness.",
    "answer": "A: anger.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You want to get straight A's and impress your teachers, so you consider cheating on tests to ma ke sure you do well. You're facing an ethical dilemma because of your",
    "A": "conflicting values.",
    "B": "desire to prove yourself.",
    "C": "pressure from others.",
    "D": "bad role models.",
    "answer": "B: desire to prove yourself.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Making a product more useful by altering or changing it in some manner creates __________ utility.",
    "A": "possession C. time",
    "B": "place D. form 25. How do producers answer the economic question of what to produce? A. By rationing goods and services",
    "C": "By buying more resources B. By developing incentives",
    "D": "By comparing relative prices",
    "answer": "D: By comparing relative prices",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the most effective methods of locating job leads is asking for tips from",
    "A": "friends.",
    "B": "retirees.",
    "C": "minors.",
    "D": "nonworkers.",
    "answer": "A: friends.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An electronic planning device that many employees use t o keep track of their activities is an example of a",
    "A": "presentation application. C. web-based program.",
    "B": "communication system. D. time-management tool. 74. Which of the following is an example of a \"stop\" word that a search engine is most likely to ignore when retrieving query results: A. Hat",
    "C": "Sew B. Cop",
    "D": "The",
    "answer": "D: The",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chloe recently took over the family business so that her parents could retire. While reorganizing her dad's desk so that she could use it, Chloe found several compact discs (CDs). She'd like to find out what is stored on each disc, but she doesn't have a computer with a CD drive. She can't access the data on the discs because CDs have become",
    "A": "networked. C. obsolete.",
    "B": "destructive. D. decentralized. 73. In an effective information management system, all information is A. accurate.",
    "C": "quantitative in nature. B. accessible to everyone.",
    "D": "abstract.",
    "answer": "C: quantitative in nature. B. accessible to everyone.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an aspect of any team project that you should monitor during the course of the project:?",
    "A": "Team members' friendships",
    "B": "The planning process",
    "C": "Emails",
    "D": "Team members' performance",
    "answer": "D: Team members' performance",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What information should employees avoid sharing with their coworkers?",
    "A": "Organizational tips",
    "B": "Current salary",
    "C": "Sales policies",
    "D": "Vacation plans",
    "answer": "B: Current salary",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What communication style is most appropriate to use when you are providing a frien d with personal advice?",
    "A": "Empathic",
    "B": "Formal",
    "C": "Judgmental",
    "D": "Businesslike",
    "answer": "A: Empathic",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What action can individuals take to reduce the cost of their health insurance coverage?",
    "A": "Make quarterly payments to the carrier",
    "B": "Increase the amount of their deductible",
    "C": "Increase the amount of their liability coverage",
    "D": "Enroll in the carrier's dis ability coverage",
    "answer": "B: Increase the amount of their deductible",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The following is written on the back of a check: \"For deposit only; Maria Evans; Ac count #285655.\" This is an example of a(n) __________ endorsement.",
    "A": "congruent",
    "B": "general",
    "C": "open",
    "D": "restrictive",
    "answer": "D: restrictive",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During the sale, touchpoints should be designed to",
    "A": "get the customer's attention.",
    "B": "show the customer what benefits the brand offers.",
    "C": "resolve any problems the customer has with the product.",
    "D": "reinforce that the customer is making the right buying decision.",
    "answer": "D: reinforce that the customer is making the right buying decision.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Fair Credit Reporting Act is important to consumers because it",
    "A": "provides guidelines that institutions must use in extending credit.",
    "B": "gives them the right to inspect the files of their credit history.",
    "C": "ensures that they are not denied credit for any discriminatory reason.",
    "D": "makes it easy for them to compare the terms of different credit systems.",
    "answer": "B: gives them the right to inspect the files of their credit history.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is part of the product/service management function:?",
    "A": "Getting products from producers to customers",
    "B": "Deciding on the products that a business will produce or order",
    "C": "Informing customers about new and improved products",
    "D": "Conducting research to find out as much as possible about customers",
    "answer": "B: Deciding on the products that a business will produce or order",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ramona's teacher is giving directions for the midterm; but the two students sitting on either side of Ramona are whispering to each other, and it's hard for her to hear. Ramona focuses all of her attention on the teacher, so she doesn't miss anything important. Which of the following steps for followi ng directions does this situation illustrate:",
    "A": "Acknowledging directions verbally or nonverbally",
    "B": "Eliminating distractions",
    "C": "Reaching consensus",
    "D": "Recommending alternatives",
    "answer": "B: Eliminating distractions",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way that businesses can protect the privacy of their customers is to limit the number of employees who have access to the customers'",
    "A": "purchasing histories.",
    "B": "personal information.",
    "C": "identification codes.",
    "D": "telephone numbers.",
    "answer": "B: personal information.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Adapting to a new situation is most likely to help a person",
    "A": "avoid facing change. C. develop confidence.",
    "B": "eliminate stress. D. stay comfortable. Test 1232 BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CORE EXAM 5 49. Maria and Marcos work together and occasionally speak to each other in their native language and bring native foods to share with coworkers. Brett, a new employee, began to make fun of them because their __________ was different fr om his. A. formal education",
    "C": "lifestyle B. mental ability",
    "D": "ethnic heritage",
    "answer": "C: lifestyle B. mental ability",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Raquel gives Emil feedback, she's sure to focus on what will help Emil improve. Although she tells Emil what he's doing wrong, she also explains how to correct the behavior and perform better the next time. Raquel is usin g?",
    "A": "open-ended questioning.",
    "B": "constructive criticism.",
    "C": "negative feedback.",
    "D": "nonverbal communication.",
    "answer": "B: constructive criticism.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Kinan's identity was stolen, and he needs to dispute an inaccuracy in his credit report data. He should reach out to __________ to have the mistake corrected.",
    "A": "the IFRS",
    "B": "his financial advisor",
    "C": "the credit bureau",
    "D": "the police",
    "answer": "C: the credit bureau",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a purpose of an exit interview:?",
    "A": "To gain constructive suggestions for improvement",
    "B": "To gauge employee attitudes about social issues",
    "C": "To negotiate compensation and benefits",
    "D": "To gain further insight into the competition",
    "answer": "A: To gain constructive suggestions for improvement",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When HR management executives participate in a company's long-range planning efforts, they are taking part in?",
    "A": "financial analysis.",
    "B": "marketing.",
    "C": "budgeting.",
    "D": "strategic managem ent.",
    "answer": "D: strategic managem ent.",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What kind of dangerous situation might result if a new employee operates specialized equipm ent without having received prior training on how to properly use that equipment?",
    "A": "Personal tension",
    "B": "Mental stress",
    "C": "Physical fatigue",
    "D": "Safety hazard",
    "answer": "D: Safety hazard",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Todd needs to develop an overall plan for his business but does not know what type of information to include in the document. Todd logs onto a search engine to quickly locate the information he needs. Which of the following search terms is most likely to provide Todd with desired search results:",
    "A": "Business plan elements",
    "B": "Develop planning document",
    "C": "Business document components",
    "D": "Plan components",
    "answer": "A: Business plan elements",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monica has $850 for a new computer. The salesperson at the electronics stores tries to get Monica to purchase a computer that costs $1,100, but Monica can't because she doesn't possess the",
    "A": "buying power.",
    "B": "equilibrium.",
    "C": "elasticity.",
    "D": "utility.",
    "answer": "A: buying power.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an appropriate attitude for a job applicant to demonstrate during a job interview:?",
    "A": "I have skills that this company could use.",
    "B": "I can do any job that I'm asked to do.",
    "C": "I think this company would be lucky to get me.",
    "D": "I know all about this company and its products.",
    "answer": "A: I have skills that this company could use.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Although Nolan feels that he has the right solution for a problem at work, he listens to what ot hers have to say and takes their opinions seriously. Nolan is",
    "A": "generous.",
    "B": "empathetic.",
    "C": "reliable.",
    "D": "open-minded.",
    "answer": "D: open-minded.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Effective coaches are patient, dependable, and",
    "A": "entertaining. C. distracted.",
    "B": "critical. D. approachable. 49. Personality is a combination of an individual's personal A. ethnic heritage.",
    "C": "characteristics, or traits. B. education.",
    "D": "religion.",
    "answer": "D: religion.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is best to organize a report in chronological order when the subject matter is",
    "A": "appeal based. C. time-oriented.",
    "B": "based on opinion. D. problem-oriented. Test 1232 BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CORE EXAM 2 13. The Putnam Company requires its employees to use the Modern Language Association (MLA) stylebook when writing business documents because it provides A. accuracy.",
    "C": "flexibility. B. creativity.",
    "D": "consistency.",
    "answer": "C: flexibility. B. creativity.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way that businesses maintain the security of data that they send over the Internet to clients is by using a software program that prevents a(n)",
    "A": "attachment from being included.",
    "B": "virus from being downloaded.",
    "C": "document from being forwarded.",
    "D": "search engine from being used.",
    "answer": "C: document from being forwarded.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What might businesses lose if their employees are injured on the job and are unable to work?",
    "A": "Sales",
    "B": "Goods",
    "C": "Assets",
    "D": "Benefits",
    "answer": "A: Sales",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When persuading others to go along with a proposed change, you should?",
    "A": "reinforce your proposal with facts and statistics.",
    "B": "tell them that there's a better way of doing things.",
    "C": "minimize the amount of information you give.",
    "D": "explain how the change will benefit them.",
    "answer": "D: explain how the change will benefit them.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a secondary dimension of diversity:?",
    "A": "Race/Ethnicity",
    "B": "Work experience",
    "C": "Date of birth",
    "D": "Age",
    "answer": "B: Work experience",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The best way for people to obtain information about a variety of career fields and options is b y",
    "A": "accessing online employment services.",
    "B": "joining social organizations.",
    "C": "completing job applications.",
    "D": "reading virtual textbooks.",
    "answer": "A: accessing online employment services.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The ultimate goal of all economic activity is",
    "A": "distribution.",
    "B": "production.",
    "C": "exchange.",
    "D": "consumption.",
    "answer": "D: consumption.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a reason to avoid lying:?",
    "A": "Lies can help you gain respect.",
    "B": "Lies are hard to keep track of.",
    "C": "Lies can get you out of trouble.",
    "D": "Lies may turn a bad situation around.",
    "answer": "B: Lies are hard to keep track of.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesspeople often use the calendar applications on their mobile devices to",
    "A": "check their email.",
    "B": "obtain driving directions.",
    "C": "send text messages to clients.",
    "D": "track their appointments.",
    "answer": "D: track their appointments.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following leaders is most likely to inspire their employees to achieve:?",
    "A": "Nick gives specific instructions on how to perform work.",
    "B": "Joon regularly sets high goals for team members to work toward.",
    "C": "Jose encourages his employees to use and develop their talents.",
    "D": "Yamini works independently without the help of others.",
    "answer": "C: Jose encourages his employees to use and develop their talents.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The three types of rules that companies implement fall into which of the following categories:",
    "A": "Prohibitions, protocols, and procedures",
    "B": "Policies, procedures, and protocols",
    "C": "Policies, prohibitions, and procedures",
    "D": "Protocols, prohibitions, and policies",
    "answer": "B: Policies, procedures, and protocols",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Investing can help build wealth because it",
    "A": "eliminates the need to save for retirement.",
    "B": "guarantees that you will not lose any money.",
    "C": "doesn't require any money to start investing.",
    "D": "increases your savings over your lifetime.",
    "answer": "D: increases your savings over your lifetime.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a brand promise:?",
    "A": "Henderson Photography...uniquely capturing your special moments is our priority.",
    "B": "Leather sofas only $499 this weekend-buy now at Fred's Furniture Warehouse.",
    "C": "Low credit terms are available for qualified customers until January 2014.",
    "D": "For your convenience, four Cup O' Joe locations are open in the greater metro area.",
    "answer": "A: Henderson Photography...uniquely capturing your special moments is our priority.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a capital good:?",
    "A": "Water C. Seeds",
    "B": "A plow D. A farmhand 23. Owen wants a new pair of running shoes. He also wants a new sweatshirt to wear while running, but he decides that he needs the shoes more. By purchasing the running shoes, Owen will give up the potential benefit of purchasing the sweatshirt. The potential benefit that Owen is giving up is the __________ cost of his decision. A. opportunity",
    "C": "marginal B. holding",
    "D": "menu",
    "answer": "B: A plow D. A farmhand 23. Owen wants a new pair of running shoes. He also wants a new sweatshirt to wear while running, but he decides that he needs the shoes more. By purchasing the running shoes, Owen will give up the potential benefit of purchasing the sweatshirt. The potential benefit that Owen is giving up is the __________ cost of his decision. A. opportunity",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sheila pays the minimum payment shown on her credit card bill each month. For the remaining amount on the bill, she will be charged a(n)",
    "A": "annual percentage rate. C. late fee.",
    "B": "annual fee. D. overdraft fee. 59. While review ing his credit report, Isaiah saw an inaccurate entry regarding a bank loan that he had obtained. The first step that Isaiah should take to correct the mistake is to A. file a complaint with the local business association. B. contact the bank.",
    "C": "contact the appropriate credit bureau.",
    "D": "file a claim with the federal banking agency.",
    "answer": "A: annual percentage rate. C. late fee.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You have just started a new job with coworkers who have been working together and are now friends. Whenever you ask a job-related question, your coworkers laugh at you. You can use self-c ontrol in this situation to help you with",
    "A": "job enrichment.",
    "B": "goal setting.",
    "C": "interpersonal relationships.",
    "D": "operational changes.",
    "answer": "C: interpersonal relationships.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way in which many businesses demonstrate their social responsibility tow ard employees is by providing them with",
    "A": "a stress-free atmosphere.",
    "B": "regular entertainment.",
    "C": "a safe working environment.",
    "D": "free meals.",
    "answer": "C: a safe working environment.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a business applying information to accomplish a tas k:?",
    "A": "Conducting research on consumer preferences",
    "B": "Reviewing data on trends to develop new products",
    "C": "Developing questionnaires for local surveys",
    "D": "Examining promotional activities of competitors",
    "answer": "B: Reviewing data on trends to develop new products",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can interest and enthusiasm give people a good outlook on life?",
    "A": "By enabling them to keep their frustrations to themselves",
    "B": "By keeping frustrations from coming their way",
    "C": "By minimizing the impact of frustrations",
    "D": "By enabling them to be aggressive with others who cause frustrations",
    "answer": "C: By minimizing the impact of frustrations",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your supervisor has given you a job to do which must be completed before you leave for the d ay. Another employee has finished her assignment and offers to help you. This person is d emonstrating",
    "A": "honesty.",
    "B": "initiative.",
    "C": "empathy.",
    "D": "assertiveness.",
    "answer": "B: initiative.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of point-of-sale fraud committed by employees:?",
    "A": "Accepting a check from a customer who lacks funds to cover it",
    "B": "Undercharging friends or family members for purchases",
    "C": "Overcharging customers and keeping the extra money",
    "D": "Using employee discount privileges for friends or family members",
    "answer": "A: Accepting a check from a customer who lacks funds to cover it",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To take responsibility for your decisions and actions, it's important to build yo ur self-confidence and",
    "A": "work portfolio.",
    "B": "grades.",
    "C": "self-esteem.",
    "D": "physical fitness.",
    "answer": "C: self-esteem.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You should expect some criticism on your job performance because a certain amount of critici sm on the job is",
    "A": "cruel.",
    "B": "tolerable.",
    "C": "necessary.",
    "D": "senseless.",
    "answer": "C: necessary.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does communicating with others help you to maintain a positive attitude?",
    "A": "By providing you with support for your ideas",
    "B": "By helping you to feel understood",
    "C": "By allowing you to justify your opinions",
    "D": "By informing you about others' achievements",
    "answer": "B: By helping you to feel understood",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a situation where acting responsibly is mandated by law:?",
    "A": "You must decide whether or not to lie to your parents about breaking curfew.",
    "B": "You must decide whether or not to drink with friends at a party.",
    "C": "You must decide whether or not to turn in the money you found on the ground.",
    "D": "You must decide whether or not to cheat on your chemistry test.",
    "answer": "B: You must decide whether or not to drink with friends at a party.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When you ask yourself, \"What would I attempt to do if I knew I could not fail?\", you are dete rmining your?",
    "A": "necessary resources.",
    "B": "aspirations.",
    "C": "reason for existing.",
    "D": "values.",
    "answer": "B: aspirations.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In addition to purchasing, Sherita's job responsibilities include developing partnerships and alliances with suppliers, watching for business threats and opportunities, and looking for ways to improve pr ocesses. Sherita is involved in",
    "A": "marketing planning.",
    "B": "negotiation.",
    "C": "strategic planning.",
    "D": "productivity.",
    "answer": "C: strategic planning.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one basic characteristic of self-esteem?",
    "A": "Saying \"no\" to things you really don't want to do",
    "B": "Caring about yourself and your personal life",
    "C": "Knowing and understanding what your own needs are",
    "D": "Doing something that makes you feel good",
    "answer": "C: Knowing and understanding what your own needs are",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Corbin watched the presidential debate on TV to decide whom he would vote for in the upcoming election. This is an example of using active listening to",
    "A": "understand instructions.",
    "B": "form an opinion.",
    "C": "increase satisfaction.",
    "D": "connect with others.",
    "answer": "B: form an opinion.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Employees who answer the telephone should give both the name of the business and",
    "A": "their names.",
    "B": "its purpose.",
    "C": "the time.",
    "D": "its address.",
    "answer": "A: their names.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a change in the relative price ratio when the original price of red apples is 60\u00a2 per pound and the original price of green apples is 80\u00a2 per pound:?",
    "A": "Red apples @ 45\u00a2 per pound; green apples @ 60\u00a2 per pound",
    "B": "Red apples @ 90\u00a2 per pound; green apples @ 80\u00a2 per pound",
    "C": "Red apples @ $1.20 per pound; green apples @ $1.60 per pound",
    "D": "Red apples @ 30\u00a2 per pound; green apples @ 40\u00a2 per pound",
    "answer": "B: Red apples @ 90\u00a2 per pound; green apples @ 80\u00a2 per pound",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an advantage to businesses of using web-based services f or storing business records online:?",
    "A": "Web-based service companies rarely experience technical problems.",
    "B": "The online service provider updates the records daily.",
    "C": "Outdated records are automatically discarded without permission.",
    "D": "The information is available at all times from any computer.",
    "answer": "D: The information is available at all times from any computer.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Bill punishes each of his staff exactly the same way when they break the rules. Bill is be ing",
    "A": "generous.",
    "B": "empathetic.",
    "C": "biased.",
    "D": "consistent.",
    "answer": "D: consistent.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What usually results when business operations and procedures are efficient and economical?",
    "A": "Consumers can buy quality products at competitive prices.",
    "B": "Consumer prices are raised to increase profits.",
    "C": "Monopolies can give all businesses a greater share of the market.",
    "D": "More equipment is needed to produce finished products.",
    "answer": "A: Consumers can buy quality products at competitive prices.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "People commonly resist change because they",
    "A": "have a positive attitude.",
    "B": "see the big picture.",
    "C": "show flexibility.",
    "D": "fear the unknown.",
    "answer": "D: fear the unknown.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hardware, software, and databases are all components of ___________ systems.",
    "A": "information",
    "B": "ethics",
    "C": "email",
    "D": "word-of-mouth",
    "answer": "A: information",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Visualizing yourself as you would like to be is a technique that",
    "A": "does not work well.",
    "B": "is seldom rewarding.",
    "C": "is quick and easy to learn.",
    "D": "takes time and practice.",
    "answer": "D: takes time and practice.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Most businesses consider initiative to be __________ for employees.",
    "A": "elective",
    "B": "optional",
    "C": "essential",
    "D": "irrelevant",
    "answer": "C: essential",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Dale is taking notes during a staff meeting, he should?",
    "A": "avoid abbreviations and symbols.",
    "B": "write his notes in complete sentences.",
    "C": "capture every word that is said.",
    "D": "organize his notes in a logical manner.",
    "answer": "D: organize his notes in a logical manner.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Jody finished her assigned duties, she began looking for another project that needed to be completed. Which of the following traits is Jody demonstrating:?",
    "A": "Assertiveness C. Interdependence",
    "B": "Innovation D. Initiative 34. Ross supervises a team of employees, and he enforces a strict policy against tardiness, sternly criticizing his employees when they are late. H owever, Ross regularly comes in late to work and misses important meetings. Ross's integrity is lacking because he A. does not act in accordance with his values.",
    "C": "is not honest with his staff. B. does not have any values.",
    "D": "does not respect confident iality or privacy.",
    "answer": "D: does not respect confident iality or privacy.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Expressing empathy and being willing to help others are the aspects of emotional intelligence that relate to",
    "A": "self-management.",
    "B": "relationship management.",
    "C": "self-awareness.",
    "D": "social awareness.",
    "answer": "D: social awareness.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The relationship between your traits and your personality can be described as",
    "A": "independent.",
    "B": "nonexistent.",
    "C": "interdependent.",
    "D": "indirect.",
    "answer": "C: interdependent.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Elizabeth has many ways of interacting with her favorite store. She can visit it in p erson and speak to an employee, check out the store's website online, receive one of its email newsletters, or look at i ts Facebook page. The ways Elizabeth interacts with the store are",
    "A": "contact spots.",
    "B": "touch points.",
    "C": "brand interactions.",
    "D": "customer exchanges.",
    "answer": "B: touch points.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Aisha wants to buy new ovens for her bakery. They'll be expensive, but she has some money s aved up that she can use for the purchase. Aisha plans to finance her new equipment using",
    "A": "accounts receivable.",
    "B": "dividends.",
    "C": "debt.",
    "D": "equity.",
    "answer": "D: equity.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Margaret recently took out a personal loan from her local bank. In exchange for receiving the loan, Margaret agreed to pay an additional 6.9% of the original loan amount to the bank each year. 6.9% is Margaret's",
    "A": "compound value.",
    "B": "present value.",
    "C": "interest rate.",
    "D": "inflation rate.",
    "answer": "C: interest rate.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tony's Pizza Shop recently started making 100 more pizzas on Saturday evenings. This incr ease demonstrates an increase in",
    "A": "pricing.",
    "B": "distribution.",
    "C": "publicity.",
    "D": "production.",
    "answer": "D: production.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses often use word-processing computer software to produce",
    "A": "detailed reports, memos, and contracts.",
    "B": "complex graphics, letters, and reports.",
    "C": "research reports, spreadsheets, and tables.",
    "D": "business plans, contracts, and spreadsheets.",
    "answer": "A: detailed reports, memos, and contracts.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of business policy is designed to attract customers by making the purchasing experience mor e\nconvenient for them?",
    "A": "Flexible",
    "B": "Employee",
    "C": "Service",
    "D": "Product",
    "answer": "C: Service",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Constructive criticism is advice that is",
    "A": "irrelevant and not intended to be taken seriously.",
    "B": "useful and intended to improve something.",
    "C": "personally offensive and usually uncalled for.",
    "D": "critical and intended to hurt someone's feelings.",
    "answer": "B: useful and intended to improve something.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Businesses often use presentation software to develop computerized training materials that contain interactive buttons, which allow employees to",
    "A": "test themselves.",
    "B": "conduct research.",
    "C": "study together.",
    "D": "access databases.",
    "answer": "A: test themselves.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) is responsible for",
    "A": "reporting job-related injuries or illnesses to supervisors.",
    "B": "seeking medical attention for injured employees.",
    "C": "insisting that businesses maintain safe, hazard-free workplaces.",
    "D": "complying with a business's safety rules.",
    "answer": "C: insisting that businesses maintain safe, hazard-free workplaces.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Camilla believ es that women tend to work more efficiently and focus more on important details than men do. Camilla's personal bias is associated with a stereotype based on",
    "A": "education. C. culture.",
    "B": "age. D. gender. 31. What do individuals often identify when assessing their personal strengths and weaknesses? A. Interests",
    "C": "Benefits B. Careers",
    "D": "Risks",
    "answer": "D: Risks",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do entrepreneurs develop their skills?",
    "A": "By training and continuous practice",
    "B": "By reducing their flexibility",
    "C": "By becoming an autocratic leader",
    "D": "By seeking little or no advice from others",
    "answer": "A: By training and continuous practice",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To help people who are impacted by a change to the status quo, it is important to",
    "A": "demonstrate groupthink behavior.",
    "B": "celebrate the success of your plan.",
    "C": "show understanding for their loss.",
    "D": "implement the change quickly.",
    "answer": "C: show understanding for their loss.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before you can understand others, you must first understand",
    "A": "the use of objectivity.",
    "B": "yourself.",
    "C": "Maslow's hierarchy.",
    "D": "what motivates people.",
    "answer": "B: yourself.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following pieces of information appears on a check:?",
    "A": "The payee's name",
    "B": "The payer's credit account number",
    "C": "The name of the payee's bank",
    "D": "The payer's credit score",
    "answer": "A: The payee's name",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a fire alarm goes off at Karen's office, she maintains her composure and leads her coworkers out of the building quickly and quietly. As a result, nobody was injured, and Karen's team made it out of the building before anyone else. This is an example of the importance of?",
    "A": "staying calm in emergency situations.",
    "B": "ignoring company protocol during emergencies.",
    "C": "the concept of \"every man for himself\" during emergencies.",
    "D": "doubting the seriousness of fire alarms.",
    "answer": "A: staying calm in emergency situations.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When creating your business's web page, you make it possible for Internet browsers to identify and locate various elements of your page through the proper placement of?",
    "A": "HTML. C. meta tags.",
    "B": "hyperlinks. D. ASCII. 78. A primary purpose of data mining is to A. develop services.",
    "C": "discover relationships. B. stabilize sales.",
    "D": "summarize ideas.",
    "answer": "C: discover relationships. B. stabilize sales.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Job interviewers often say to job applicants, \"Tell me about yourself.\" Which of the following is the purpose of this request:",
    "A": "To test the applicant's honesty and integrity",
    "B": "To test the applicant's communication skills",
    "C": "To uncover job-related problems the applicant has",
    "D": "To find out about the applicant's personal life",
    "answer": "B: To test the applicant's communication skills",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following will help you have a pleasant voice when speaking to customers:?",
    "A": "Speaking at a comfortable volume",
    "B": "Speaking very slowly",
    "C": "Speaking quickly",
    "D": "Speaking in a monotone voice",
    "answer": "A: Speaking at a comfortable volume",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Brandon has been given a 385-page report and does not have time to review the entire doc ument, but he does need to understand specific information that is included in the report. What section of the repor t will guide Brandon to the information he needs?",
    "A": "Analysis",
    "B": "Bibliography",
    "C": "Appendices",
    "D": "Table of contents",
    "answer": "D: Table of contents",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After Lucas successfully ran and organized a pep rally at school, he was told by several students and faculty members that they loved the event and would like to attend more events like it in the future. He then decided to plan another pep rally for the following semester. This is an example of how",
    "A": "it is important to measure efficient resource use.",
    "B": "evaluating the quality of project work is the most important step.",
    "C": "evaluating project success identifies needs for future projects.",
    "D": "all projects must offer financial value to stakehold ers.",
    "answer": "C: evaluating project success identifies needs for future projects.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an action that employees can take to meet their employer's expectations of honesty:?",
    "A": "Accepting responsibility for mistakes",
    "B": "Completing assignments on time",
    "C": "Helping coworkers with problems",
    "D": "Looking for better ways to do the j ob",
    "answer": "A: Accepting responsibility for mistakes",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can you keep stakeholders engaged throughout the planning process?",
    "A": "Develop quality standards.",
    "B": "Obtain feedback from your team.",
    "C": "Identify project risks.",
    "D": "Define the project scope.",
    "answer": "B: Obtain feedback from your team.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Each month, Maggie checks her bank statement against her own record of her deposits and withdrawals. Maggie is __________ her bank statement.",
    "A": "disputing",
    "B": "challenging",
    "C": "reconciling",
    "D": "creating",
    "answer": "C: reconciling",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Purchasing specialists who buy items such as furniture, supplies, and uniforms for their own company are buying for",
    "A": "transformation.",
    "B": "retail.",
    "C": "resale.",
    "D": "business use.",
    "answer": "D: business use.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rachel set a financial goal of saving $100,000 over the next five years. Her annual salary, however, is only $30,000-and she has no other sources of income. Between paying for rent, food, clothing, and student loans, it's unlikely that Rachel will be able to save $100,000 in five years. Rachel's goal i s",
    "A": "unattainable. C. irrelevant.",
    "B": "timely. D. measurable. 55. Individuals often gain wealth from saving money in a retirement account because A. retirement accounts guarantee future financial security. B. employers sometimes match employees' contr ibutions.",
    "C": "many governments offer loan relief as a reward for saving.",
    "D": "retirement account holders can accumulate rewards points.",
    "answer": "A: unattainable. C. irrelevant.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do service-oriented companies often improve their levels of service?",
    "A": "By evaluating internal product development procedures",
    "B": "By requesting input through employee and customer surveys",
    "C": "By providing customers with product testimonials",
    "D": "By conducting a feasibility analysis for company expansion",
    "answer": "B: By requesting input through employee and customer surveys",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sasha's science teacher is explaining lab directions to the class. They'll be performing a complicated experiment with many steps that will take about a week. The next day, Sasha tries to remember a step of the directions, but she can't. Which step of following oral directions shoul d Sasha have followed?",
    "A": "Take notes.",
    "B": "Acknowledge directions verbally or nonverbally.",
    "C": "Make eye contact.",
    "D": "Eliminate distractions.",
    "answer": "A: Take notes.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a limited decision:?",
    "A": "Where you'll take your bike for repair",
    "B": "When you'll leave for school",
    "C": "What college you'll attend",
    "D": "Which car you'll buy",
    "answer": "A: Where you'll take your bike for repair",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Christie's coworkers know that she won't repeat what they tell her if they ask her not to do so. This indicates that Christie is a(n) __________ coworker.",
    "A": "trustworthy",
    "B": "straightforward",
    "C": "tactful",
    "D": "efficient",
    "answer": "A: trustworthy",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What should individuals consider when identifying occupations that are of interest to them?",
    "A": "Their personalities",
    "B": "Parents' occupations",
    "C": "Family history",
    "D": "Friends' opinions",
    "answer": "A: Their personalities",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an essential element of responsible behavior:?",
    "A": "Positivity",
    "B": "Hopefulness",
    "C": "Decisiveness",
    "D": "Compassion",
    "answer": "D: Compassion",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Two salespeople show little interest in their own activities as well as the activities of others. What type of attitude is being exhibited by the salespeople?",
    "A": "Pessimistic C. Positive",
    "B": "Constructive D. Indifferent 40. One of the ways that empathy benefits a business's employees directly i s by helping them A. get along with their coworkers.",
    "C": "plan effectively for the future. B. focus on people's differences.",
    "D": "move quickly up the career ladder.",
    "answer": "D: move quickly up the career ladder.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Being tactful is an example of what type of behavior that builds positive working relationships?",
    "A": "Being cooperative C. Getting to know others on your work team",
    "B": "Carrying your own weight D. Demonstrating courtesy and respect 51. Which of the following is an example of processing a transaction with a debit card: A. Jayden purchased a new video game from Great Deal Electronics using a store-issued card given to him by his grandfather. B. Tyler provided his card number and expiration date to the online travel agency so he could obtain his airline tickets now and receive his bill for the tickets later.",
    "C": "After Ava finished her meal at an upscale restaurant, she presented the server with a card that provided Ava with a special discount off her bill.",
    "D": "When Naomi purchased office supplies, she presented the cashier with a card that automatically",
    "answer": "D: When Naomi purchased office supplies, she presented the cashier with a card that automatically",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jack says to Wendi, \"If I understand you correctly, you are saying that you want to change the format of the inventory report so it will be easier for the man agers to analyze.\" What communication technique is Jack using to clarify Wendi's suggestion?",
    "A": "Paraphrasing",
    "B": "Expressing an opinion",
    "C": "Quoting",
    "D": "Passive listening",
    "answer": "A: Paraphrasing",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is NOT a concept related to the time value of money:?",
    "A": "Opportunity cost",
    "B": "Scarcity",
    "C": "Interest rates",
    "D": "Future value",
    "answer": "B: Scarcity",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a business risk that can be covered by purchasing insurance:?",
    "A": "Economic conditions",
    "B": "Robbery",
    "C": "Spoilage",
    "D": "Competition",
    "answer": "B: Robbery",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ricky's startup company recently received an investment from a wealthy business owner who likes to support budding entrepreneurs. In other words, the wealthy business owner is a(n)",
    "A": "business analyst. C. financial advisor.",
    "B": "debt financer. D. angel investor. 27. In a private enterprise economy, business grow th is driven by A. risk.",
    "C": "profit and competition. B. governmental regulations.",
    "D": "price.",
    "answer": "D: price.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Institutions and individuals have __________ wants and __________ resources.",
    "A": "limited; unlimited",
    "B": "unlimited; limited",
    "C": "unlimited; unlimited",
    "D": "limited; limited",
    "answer": "B: unlimited; limited",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When evaluating the reliability of a journal article that addresses a complex issue or top ic, it is important to consider the author's?",
    "A": "expertise and knowledge.",
    "B": "age and expertise.",
    "C": "gender and age.",
    "D": "knowledge and gender.",
    "answer": "A: expertise and knowledge.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The supervisor who exercises very little or no control over employees is using the __________ style of\nleadership.",
    "A": "democratic",
    "B": "authoritarian",
    "C": "laissez-faire",
    "D": "subordinate",
    "answer": "C: laissez-faire",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your annual income, an inheritance, and the money from the sale of an asset are all consi dered events that contribute towards your",
    "A": "sales tax.",
    "B": "untaxable income.",
    "C": "tax loophole.",
    "D": "tax liability.",
    "answer": "D: tax liability.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a customer sees a news story on TV about a certain company or brand, it's an example of a(n)?",
    "A": "slogan.",
    "B": "advertisement.",
    "C": "touchpoint.",
    "D": "brand promise.",
    "answer": "C: touchpoint.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a habit-forming substance that many people may not consider harmful:?",
    "A": "Cigarettes",
    "B": "Alcohol",
    "C": "Coffee",
    "D": "Prescription painkillers",
    "answer": "C: Coffee",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following types of broker usually charges the highest commissions:?",
    "A": "Online",
    "B": "Discount",
    "C": "Full-service",
    "D": "Stock",
    "answer": "C: Full-service",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following would most benefit from a customer service mindset that helps reduce complaints and increase profits:?",
    "A": "Businesses C. Customers",
    "B": "Employees D. Competitors 98. Which of the following are the best references to list in a r\u00e9sum\u00e9: A. Coworkers",
    "C": "Former employers B. Family members",
    "D": "Classmates",
    "answer": "A: Businesses C. Customers",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Putting $100 in a savings account today and earning 4% interest over the next year illustrates the concept of",
    "A": "principal modification.",
    "B": "the time value of money.",
    "C": "opportunity cost.",
    "D": "inflationary impact.",
    "answer": "B: the time value of money.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is central to the concept of empathy:?",
    "A": "Respect for others",
    "B": "College degree in psychology",
    "C": "Friendship",
    "D": "Similar occupation",
    "answer": "A: Respect for others",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an internal distraction that could disrupt the listening process:?",
    "A": "Other people talking",
    "B": "A headache",
    "C": "A ringing cell phone",
    "D": "A TV",
    "answer": "B: A headache",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Interest paid on a loan can be understood as compensation to __________ for __________.",
    "A": "the borrower; spending now rather than later",
    "B": "the borrower; repa ying on time",
    "C": "the lender; avoiding bad investments",
    "D": "the lender; taking a risk",
    "answer": "D: the lender; taking a risk",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When showing why change is necessary, change leaders should?",
    "A": "speak only to coworkers.",
    "B": "avoid giving too many details.",
    "C": "provide evidence.",
    "D": "create charts and graphs.",
    "answer": "C: provide evidence.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an ownership investment:?",
    "A": "Money market accounts",
    "B": "Certificates of deposit (CDs)",
    "C": "Stocks",
    "D": "Savings accounts",
    "answer": "C: Stocks",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Throwing out junk mail and unnecessary documents on a regular basis will help you",
    "A": "delegate your workload.",
    "B": "ensure that you meet your deadlines.",
    "C": "prioritize routine work activities.",
    "D": "maintain an organized workspace.",
    "answer": "D: maintain an organized workspace.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Robert and Martha are an elderly couple with three children and nine grandchildren. When they pass away, their three children will each inherit one third of Robert and Martha's assets. In other words, the couple's children are __________ of their parents' will.",
    "A": "beneficiaries",
    "B": "directors",
    "C": "executors",
    "D": "arbitrators",
    "answer": "A: beneficiaries",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Liam is taking notes during a class lecture. He listens carefully, writes down everything the speaker says, and writes as legibly as possible. What common note-taking mistake is Liam making?",
    "A": "Listening carefully",
    "B": "Writing down everything the speaker says",
    "C": "Writing legibly",
    "D": "Taking notes-he should listen carefully without writing",
    "answer": "B: Writing down everything the speaker says",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If an individual wants to purchase a good or service using money directly from their bank account, they should\npay using",
    "A": "a bond.",
    "B": "cash.",
    "C": "a credit card.",
    "D": "a debit card.",
    "answer": "D: a debit card.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Jeremy develops his personal budget, he should categorize the money that he spends o n food, clothing, and entertainment as?",
    "A": "periodic investments.",
    "B": "fixed costs.",
    "C": "relational outflows.",
    "D": "variable expenses.",
    "answer": "D: variable expenses.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Antonio is giving a presentation on his company's annual budget that involves complicated financial information. What could he do to present this information in a more understandable way?",
    "A": "Provide the audience with detailed financial reports",
    "B": "Fit as much text as possible on his presentation slides",
    "C": "Use a visual aid such as a pie chart or bar graph",
    "D": "Start his presentation with an accounting lesson",
    "answer": "C: Use a visual aid such as a pie chart or bar graph",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Megan is working with a group member who's explaining her part of a project. Megan wants to make sure her group member knows she's listening, so she says things like, \"I see,\" \"Okay,\" and \"I understand.\" Which active listening skill is Megan demonstrating:",
    "A": "Paraphrasing the message to test her understandi ng",
    "B": "Repeating critical information",
    "C": "Using a verbal acknowledgement response",
    "D": "Collecting all the information possible",
    "answer": "C: Using a verbal acknowledgement response",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a way that you can use nonverbal communication to express your approval of an idea:?",
    "A": "Making a fist",
    "B": "Folding your arms",
    "C": "Smiling broadly",
    "D": "Raising your eyebrows",
    "answer": "C: Smiling broadly",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Midnight is interested in working with a financial institution that provides financial advice and helps with buying and selling stocks and bonds. Midnight is looking for a(n)",
    "A": "savings and loan association.",
    "B": "brokerage firm.",
    "C": "insurance company.",
    "D": "credit union.",
    "answer": "B: brokerage firm.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To complete a report about commercial loans, Lola needs to review a specific online article called \"The Truth About Commercial Interest Rate Increases.\" Which of the following search entries will provide Lola the most accurate results:",
    "A": "\"the truth a bout commercial interest rate increases\"",
    "B": "truth_ commercial interest rate_ increases}",
    "C": "\"-the_truth_about_commercial_interest_rate_increases-}\"",
    "D": "[-the-truth-about-commercial-interest-rate-increases]",
    "answer": "A: \"the truth a bout commercial interest rate increases\"",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To learn objective information about a news topic, you should",
    "A": "read opinion columns in the newspaper.",
    "B": "rely on a single news source for information.",
    "C": "distrust the national news media.",
    "D": "compare numerous different sources.",
    "answer": "D: compare numerous different sources.",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a category of innovation:?",
    "A": "Psychological C. Piloting",
    "B": "Product D. Physical 93. The manager asked a few staff members for their opinions about what color to paint the office reception area. What decision-making style did the manager use in this sit uation? A. Moderate input",
    "C": "Autocratic B. Minimum input",
    "D": "Laissez faire",
    "answer": "B: Product D. Physical 93. The manager asked a few staff members for their opinions about what color to paint the office reception area. What decision-making style did the manager use in this sit uation? A. Moderate input",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Like any product that is effectively marketed, your personal appearance is",
    "A": "likely to require a lot of money for you to be successful.",
    "B": "of little value or importance to your overall success.",
    "C": "not as critical as what's on the inside.",
    "D": "the \"brand\" that will help you sell yourself to others.",
    "answer": "D: the \"brand\" that will help you sell yourself to others.",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What must happen before the consumption of any economic goods can take place?",
    "A": "Payment C. Capitalism",
    "B": "Scarcity D. Production 24. Recently, the number of homes for sale in a metropolitan area has increased tremendously. However, the number of potential homeowners has declined. This market condition is called a A. buyer's market.",
    "C": "law of demand. B. law of supply.",
    "D": "seller's market.",
    "answer": "D: seller's market.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements regarding job applications is true:?",
    "A": "You should never include personal information that is inaccurate.",
    "B": "You do not need to disclose any felonies you have been convicted of.",
    "C": "It's okay to omit a previous job if you left on bad terms.",
    "D": "Job applications require you to have a cosigner if you are under 18.",
    "answer": "A: You should never include personal information that is inaccurate.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following situations best demonstrates why businesses should retain their r ecords:?",
    "A": "A business is planning to send press releases to the local newspaper.",
    "B": "A business is planning to send anniversary cards to employees on the date of their empl oyment.",
    "C": "A business is planning to sell out to another company.",
    "D": "A business is planning to use webinars for employee training.",
    "answer": "C: A business is planning to sell out to another company.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Paul is responding to an inquiry he received in the mail. His response includes som e good news and some bad news. How should he structure his response in light of the bad news?",
    "A": "Place the bad news in the post-script (P.S.) section of the response.",
    "B": "Place the bad news at the beginning and the good news in the closing paragraph.",
    "C": "Place the good news at the beginning and the bad news in secondary position(s).",
    "D": "Give more space to bad news than good news to emphasize urgency.",
    "answer": "C: Place the good news at the beginning and the bad news in secondary position(s).",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Individuals are most likely to require the services of a mortgage company when they want to",
    "A": "invest in the stock market.",
    "B": "acquire liability insurance.",
    "C": "purchase real estate.",
    "D": "earn interest on savings.",
    "answer": "C: purchase real estate.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a guideline for effective verbal communication:?",
    "A": "Try to avoid eye contact",
    "B": "Keep the voice at the same pitch",
    "C": "Use speech mannerisms",
    "D": "Use gestures for emphasis",
    "answer": "D: Use gestures for emphasis",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Maria, a human resources manager, wants to send a message to everyone in her office about upcoming changes in the company's insurance policy. She should deliver this message",
    "A": "with an informal email. C. through a letter.",
    "B": "verbally. D. in a memo. 13. When writing an email to your coworkers, you should always A. put your main point in your last paragraph. B. use all capitals to get important points across.",
    "C": "make sure your message is as long as possible.",
    "D": "write \"please\" and \"thank you\" when necessary.",
    "answer": "D: write \"please\" and \"thank you\" when necessary.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tim wrote a letter to thank an interviewer for meeting with him to discuss a job opening with the Cortland\nCompany. What type of letter did Tim write?",
    "A": "Application",
    "B": "Cover",
    "C": "Follow-up",
    "D": "Inquiry",
    "answer": "C: Follow-up",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of personal financial information:?",
    "A": "Pay stub C. Expense report",
    "B": "Sales invoice D. Accounts payable record 6. Which of the following is a guideline that employees should follow to be effective listeners: A. Interrupt often",
    "C": "Ask questions B. Ignore body language",
    "D": "Read directions",
    "answer": "A: Pay stub C. Expense report",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sylvia needs to buy a new computer for her com pany. Instead of bartering for the computer, she uses money to purchase it. Which function of money does this illustrate?",
    "A": "Double coincidence of wants C. Store of value",
    "B": "Unit of measure D. Medium of exchange 53. Investing can help build wealth because it A. guarantees that you will not lose any money.",
    "C": "doesn't require any money to start investing. B. increases your savings over your lifetime.",
    "D": "eliminates the need to save for retirement.",
    "answer": "D: eliminates the need to save for retirement.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Monica is shopping for a new car. Car A costs $15,000, and Car B costs $17,000. Monica can deduce that Car\nB is more valuable by using money as a(n)",
    "A": "incentive.",
    "B": "medium of exchange.",
    "C": "store of value.",
    "D": "unit of measure.",
    "answer": "D: unit of measure.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Emma's teacher is giving directions for an essay test in class. Emma should",
    "A": "avoid looking her teacher in the eye while directions are being given.",
    "B": "pay close attention to the teacher while directions are being given.",
    "C": "interrupt her teacher whenever she has a question.",
    "D": "get a head start on her test while the teacher is giving directions.",
    "answer": "B: pay close attention to the teacher while directions are being given.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You're giving a presentation about your company's budget, and you want to show how the bud get is divided among departments. Which type of visual aid should you use?",
    "A": "A line graph",
    "B": "A pie chart",
    "C": "A bar graph",
    "D": "A table",
    "answer": "B: A pie chart",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Andreas is listening to his coworker Melissa present her idea for a marketing campaign to their manager. What could Andreas do to encourage and support Melissa during her presentation?",
    "A": "Look down at the papers in front of him",
    "B": "Nod, smile, and maintain eye contact",
    "C": "Avoid eye contact and act preoccupied",
    "D": "Laugh and smile at everything Melissa says",
    "answer": "B: Nod, smile, and maintain eye contact",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a potential risk involved with information management:?",
    "A": "Higher interest rates",
    "B": "Increased use of outsourcing",
    "C": "Privacy and security issues",
    "D": "Increased competition",
    "answer": "C: Privacy and security issues",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is usually the quickest way that businesses can obtain information abo ut unknown potential new vendors that are located in other parts of the country:?",
    "A": "Phone an agent",
    "B": "Send an email to the vendors",
    "C": "Fax a request to the vendors",
    "D": "Search the Web",
    "answer": "D: Search the Web",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why are better trained and educated workers often more productive?",
    "A": "They are more likely to become managers.",
    "B": "They tend to have a higher gross domestic product per capita.",
    "C": "They are less likely to take vacation and sick days.",
    "D": "They tend to be more organized and able to manage their time wisely.",
    "answer": "D: They tend to be more organized and able to manage their time wisely.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an advantage of practicing effective human relations skills at w ork:?",
    "A": "Decline in employee morale",
    "B": "Increased employee loyalty",
    "C": "Increased employee absenteeism",
    "D": "Decreased customer loyalty and patronage",
    "answer": "B: Increased employee loyalty",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jasmine needs to hold a staff meeting in the conference room at the same time that Jason needs the conference room to meet with a new client. The reason for conflict in this situation is",
    "A": "limited resources.",
    "B": "unclear boundaries.",
    "C": "inconsistent behavior.",
    "D": "desire for authority.",
    "answer": "A: limited resources.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "You want to be sure the book you're using to research a science project is relevant and valid. You should confirm the book is",
    "A": "available at every public library nearby.",
    "B": "published by a special interest group.",
    "C": "by an author with appropriate credentials.",
    "D": "has been reprinted multiple times.",
    "answer": "C: by an author with appropriate credentials.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are businesspeople who fail to adapt their communication styles to appeal to their international clients likely to do?",
    "A": "Earn the clients' trust",
    "B": "Offend the clients",
    "C": "Impress the clients",
    "D": "Persuade the clients to buy",
    "answer": "B: Offend the clients",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Information that has been printed for publication is often more reliable than many Internet sourc es because",
    "A": "the information is typically carefully checked for accuracy.",
    "B": "authors have affiliations with professional organizations.",
    "C": "published information is current and up to date.",
    "D": "publishers do not support special interest groups.",
    "answer": "A: the information is typically carefully checked for accuracy.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jamel is an employee responsible for making sure that his company's business initiatives and computer/IT processes work smoothly together. What area of business is Jamel working in?",
    "A": "Business information management",
    "B": "Operations management",
    "C": "Accounting",
    "D": "Securities and investments",
    "answer": "A: Business information management",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As a team member, should you try to encourage others on the team?",
    "A": "No, this isn't part of your role as a team member.",
    "B": "No, management should encourage the team members.",
    "C": "Yes, this will help your fellow team members.",
    "D": "Yes, share praise you receive for your own work.",
    "answer": "C: Yes, this will help your fellow team members.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The ability to quickly and accurately calculate mathematical data is one of the characteristi cs of a __________ software program.",
    "A": "spreadsheet",
    "B": "database",
    "C": "graphics",
    "D": "word-processing",
    "answer": "A: spreadsheet",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Another employee is upset because of a reprimand from the manager. You listen quietly and then share how you handled a reprimand. You are demonstrating __________ behavior.",
    "A": "critical",
    "B": "impatient",
    "C": "indifferent",
    "D": "empathetic",
    "answer": "D: empathetic",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Computer programs that allow businesses to manage all types of activities, such as inventory c ontrol and finance, are known as",
    "A": "wireless connectivity programs.",
    "B": "electronic communications programs.",
    "C": "interactive information display packages.",
    "D": "integrated software application packages.",
    "answer": "D: integrated software application packages.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lauren was filling out an employment application and encountered a question for which she was unsure of the answer. What should she do?",
    "A": "Make up an answer",
    "B": "Leave a blank space",
    "C": "Write in \"unknown\"",
    "D": "Mark down \"personal\"",
    "answer": "C: Write in \"unknown\"",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Todd needs to develop an overall plan for his business but does not know what type of information to include in the document. Todd logs onto a search engine to quickly locate the information he needs. Which of the following search terms is most likely to provide Todd with desired search resul ts:",
    "A": "Business plan elements",
    "B": "Develop planning document",
    "C": "Plan components",
    "D": "Business document components",
    "answer": "A: Business plan elements",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Certain health and safety regulations require many types of businesses to",
    "A": "install security cameras.",
    "B": "purchase new machinery.",
    "C": "offer exercise programs.",
    "D": "routinely inspect equipment.",
    "answer": "D: routinely inspect equipment.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the most appropriate closing to include in a response to a customer's email inqui ry for product information?",
    "A": "The model 2CR is available in three colors-red, black, and white. Reply by email with the color that you want.",
    "B": "On behalf of LVN Industries, thank you for your order. Your confirmation number is 24 3597.",
    "C": "We apologize for the inconvenience and will send a corrected invoice to you within 24 ho urs.",
    "D": "Thank you for your interest in XWQ products. Please let me know if you have any additi onal",
    "answer": "D: Thank you for your interest in XWQ products. Please let me know if you have any additi onal",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following things should senders (speakers) and receivers (listeners) do to ensure that their\nnonverbal communications are positive and effective:?",
    "A": "Speak very softly",
    "B": "Make consistent eye contact",
    "C": "Avoid using any facial expressions",
    "D": "Slouch or hunch over",
    "answer": "B: Make consistent eye contact",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Failing to pay credit card bills on time will likely result in",
    "A": "an increase in credit score.",
    "B": "no penalties or consequences.",
    "C": "late fees and interest charges.",
    "D": "being fired from your job.",
    "answer": "C: late fees and interest charges.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Economics is concerned primarily with evaluating alternatives and",
    "A": "increasing foreign trade.",
    "B": "financing the national debt.",
    "C": "making economic decisions.",
    "D": "producing goods and services.",
    "answer": "C: making economic decisions.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for business employees to follow established security procedures?",
    "A": "To develop a healthy environment",
    "B": "To create a pleasant facility",
    "C": "To avoid the risk of accidents",
    "D": "To reduce the possibility of loss",
    "answer": "D: To reduce the possibility of loss",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of retirement plan gives employees little control but guarantees a specific amount for employees?",
    "A": "401(k)",
    "B": "Defined contribution",
    "C": "Defined benefit",
    "D": "Social Security",
    "answer": "C: Defined benefit",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The key factors involved in compounding growth are the amount of money you invest, ho w much your investment grows each year, and",
    "A": "how long your money is invested.",
    "B": "how you earn the money that you invest.",
    "C": "your educational background and career.",
    "D": "your mutual fund manager's education.",
    "answer": "A: how long your money is invested.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Operations activities are most closely related to a business's",
    "A": "taxes.",
    "B": "name.",
    "C": "product.",
    "D": "location.",
    "answer": "C: product.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After Porter realized that he processed an order incorrectly, he waited too long to correct the prob lem. As a result, an incorrect item was shipped to the customer. Now, the customer will need to ship the item back to the warehouse, and Porter's company will need to pay extra charges to have the product returned. This situation illustrates that",
    "A": "the company has unrealistic expectations about Porter's ability to perform his job.",
    "B": "employees should tell their supervisors about all problems as soon as they occur.",
    "C": "an employee's decisions and actions can negatively impact others.",
    "D": "customers are likely to be very angry when employees make simple mistakes.",
    "answer": "C: an employee's decisions and actions can negatively impact others.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What are the most effective deterrents to shoplifting?",
    "A": "Guards and detectives C. Fitting room staffs and mirrors",
    "B": "Electronic article surveillance tags D. Concealed closed-circuit televisions 84. To maintain workplace security and minimize breaches, you must be A. a team player.",
    "C": "observant. B. distracted.",
    "D": "friendly.",
    "answer": "B: Electronic article surveillance tags D. Concealed closed-circuit televisions 84. To maintain workplace security and minimize breaches, you must be A. a team player.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before you analyze the available information to solve a problem, it is important to",
    "A": "determine the best solution from several alternatives.",
    "B": "brainstorm possible solutions.",
    "C": "identify and check your assumptions.",
    "D": "ask for input from your peers.",
    "answer": "C: identify and check your assumptions.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of deposit-taking institution is owned by its members or customers?",
    "A": "Full-service broker C. Credit union",
    "B": "Investment bank D. Discount broker 64. Ethan has health insurance through his employer. Each time Ethan needs medical attention, he must write a check in the amount of $25 to the doctor's office to cover his out-of-pocket expense. This out-of-pocket expense is Ethan's A. copayment.",
    "C": "surrender charge. B. total premium.",
    "D": "waiver.",
    "answer": "C: surrender charge. B. total premium.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Rashid's business always puts the customer first. All of the company's decisions are made to satisfy customer wants and needs. Rashid's company is using the __________ concept.",
    "A": "marketing",
    "B": "relative",
    "C": "utility",
    "D": "customer",
    "answer": "A: marketing",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why do businesses often make it possible for employees to meet during work time and participate in group discussions?",
    "A": "To discuss personal issues",
    "B": "To plan extracurricular activities",
    "C": "To have casual conversations",
    "D": "To share many different opinions",
    "answer": "D: To share many different opinions",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What course of action can a lender take if a debtor's account is past due?",
    "A": "Claim defamation",
    "B": "File a judicial lien",
    "C": "Apply for bankruptcy",
    "D": "Liquidate assets",
    "answer": "B: File a judicial lien",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important for individuals to assess their personal strengths and weakness es?",
    "A": "To be able to negotiate their contracts",
    "B": "To get the most bang for their buck",
    "C": "To be able to respond appropriately in a crisis",
    "D": "To improve their performance",
    "answer": "D: To improve their performance",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Trina's sales team won the company-wide competition, she was sure to share the credit with all her team members. Trina is demonstrating that she is?",
    "A": "consistent.",
    "B": "open-minded.",
    "C": "generous.",
    "D": "impartial.",
    "answer": "C: generous.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chad's friend wrote down instructions for him to change the oil in his car. Chad makes sure he follows the direction to put something for catching the oil in place first, so it doesn't spill everywhere. Which of the following steps for following directions does this situation illustrate:",
    "A": "Note key words",
    "B": "Ask",
    "C": "Go in order",
    "D": "Accept responsibility",
    "answer": "C: Go in order",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Siobhan always treats others the way that she'd like to be treated. She is building trust by",
    "A": "communicating often and openly. C. being fair.",
    "B": "keeping her promises. D. taking responsibility for her mistakes. 36. When Tori considers taking something that doesn't belong to her, which ethical principle could help her recognize that she's facing an ethical dilemma? A. Accountability",
    "C": "Respect B. Transparency",
    "D": "Trust",
    "answer": "C: Respect B. Transparency",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is true about listening:?",
    "A": "Passive listening is best for complex messages.",
    "B": "Listening occurs automatically.",
    "C": "Listening requires effort.",
    "D": "Hearing and listening are the same thing.",
    "answer": "C: Listening requires effort.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Employees should use the find-and-replace function in a word-processing program to",
    "A": "track the changes made to the document.",
    "B": "verify that the document is free of spelling and punctuation errors.",
    "C": "change the default language in the document to another language.",
    "D": "change a phrase that appears several times in a long document to another phrase.",
    "answer": "D: change a phrase that appears several times in a long document to another phrase.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a workplace emergency situation that all employees s hould know how to handle and report:?",
    "A": "Civil disorder",
    "B": "Bomb threat",
    "C": "Check fraud",
    "D": "Identity theft",
    "answer": "B: Bomb threat",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The act of reflecting on and processing information is often referred to as",
    "A": "mental fitness.",
    "B": "objective research.",
    "C": "compulsive thought.",
    "D": "critical thinking.",
    "answer": "D: critical thinking.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Companies that provide an orientation and training to new employees are most likely to help those employees",
    "A": "earn promotions.",
    "B": "deal with transition.",
    "C": "eliminate their fear.",
    "D": "improve personal relationships.",
    "answer": "B: deal with transition.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Keegan is taking a business course, but he doesn't like his instructor's style. He deci des he'll go to two more classes to see if it improves, and if not, he'll switch to a different course. Keegan is showi ng adaptability by developing a(n) __________ plan.",
    "A": "objective",
    "B": "contingency",
    "C": "corrective",
    "D": "learning",
    "answer": "B: contingency",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is important to your assertiveness for you to consider yourself to be a(n) __________ person.",
    "A": "inferior",
    "B": "worthwhile",
    "C": "superior",
    "D": "enviable",
    "answer": "B: worthwhile",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jamison is ignorant of his new classmate's culture. In other words, Jamison is",
    "A": "individualist.",
    "B": "ethnocentric.",
    "C": "unintelligent.",
    "D": "uninformed.",
    "answer": "D: uninformed.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What procedure should always be performed before posting a web page on a web server?",
    "A": "Apply for a patent to protect the web page contents from plagiarism",
    "B": "Consult an attorney to verify the accuracy of the web page legal content",
    "C": "Review the page to make sure the content meets international trade requirements",
    "D": "Test the page to identify broken links, missing images, or unclear instructions",
    "answer": "D: Test the page to identify broken links, missing images, or unclear instructions",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Communicating with others is a good way to demonstrate fairness because it",
    "A": "prevents bias from affecting decision-making.",
    "B": "promotes the equality approach to fairness.",
    "C": "allows you to ignore critical feedback.",
    "D": "allows everyone to have a fair chance to be heard.",
    "answer": "D: allows everyone to have a fair chance to be heard.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Writing a follow-up letter after a job interview allows a job applicant the oppor tunity to",
    "A": "provide references and recommendations.",
    "B": "restate his/her interest in the position.",
    "C": "explain her/his training and experience.",
    "D": "describe personal strengths and weaknesses.",
    "answer": "B: restate his/her interest in the position.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Recently, Miranda met with a Brazilian entrepreneur to sign a business contract. When Miranda smiled and gave the entrepreneur the \"OK\" sign after the contract was signed, the entrepreneur frowned in disbelief and immediately left the room. Later, Miranda learned that Brazilians view the \"OK\" sign as an offensive gesture. Miranda could have avoided the embarrassin g breach of etiquette by",
    "A": "conducting research about the country's culture before her meeting.",
    "B": "touring the Brazilian embassy to obtain information about the country's regulations.",
    "C": "learning to speak in the country's official language fluently.",
    "D": "taking courses about Brazilian literature and history.",
    "answer": "A: conducting research about the country's culture before her meeting.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a business uses computer technology to manage its money and move it among different acc ounts, it is taking advantage of?",
    "A": "electronic transfer of funds.",
    "B": "hardware.",
    "C": "expert systems.",
    "D": "electronic data interchange.",
    "answer": "A: electronic transfer of funds.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One principle on which the marketing concept is based is that a business should be abl e to meet its own goals when it",
    "A": "sells products at fair and reasonable prices.",
    "B": "focuses on the wants/needs of the business.",
    "C": "achieves maximum production.",
    "D": "demonstrates social responsibility.",
    "answer": "A: sells products at fair and reasonable prices.",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How does appropriate information management affect a business's relationship with its customers?",
    "A": "Businesses earn higher profits.",
    "B": "Businesses serve customers more effectively.",
    "C": "Businesses lose focus on customers.",
    "D": "Businesses make better financial decisions.",
    "answer": "B: Businesses serve customers more effectively.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is important to learn how to handle conflicting viewpoints because",
    "A": "it is impossible for people to change their minds.",
    "B": "other people's opinions are generally wrong.",
    "C": "you need to know how to convince others that you are right.",
    "D": "you will face conflicting viewpoints many times in life.",
    "answer": "D: you will face conflicting viewpoints many times in life.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do you need to know in order to dif ferentiate between consumer and industrial goods or services?",
    "A": "Who sold the product and at what price?",
    "B": "Who produced the product?",
    "C": "Who bought the product and for what purpose?",
    "D": "Who bought the product?",
    "answer": "C: Who bought the product and for what purpose?",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Giving more buying responsibility to local stores that are part of large retail chains is a form of",
    "A": "centralization.",
    "B": "decentralization.",
    "C": "shared buying.",
    "D": "price-agreement planning.",
    "answer": "B: decentralization.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To handle customer complaints effectively, the first thing that employees should do is",
    "A": "listen to the customers to understand their concerns.",
    "B": "take the customers' problems personally.",
    "C": "give the customers what they want to make them happy.",
    "D": "state the business's policies to prevent misunderstandings.",
    "answer": "A: listen to the customers to understand their concerns.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Barnes Company has just opened an account for a customer with a credit limit of $2,000 and an interest rate of 18%. This type of credit is a(n) __________ credit account.",
    "A": "installment",
    "B": "budget",
    "C": "regular",
    "D": "revolving",
    "answer": "D: revolving",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following marketing functions focuses on informing all current and potential cust omers about the business's products:?",
    "A": "Marketing-information management",
    "B": "Promotion",
    "C": "Product/Service Management",
    "D": "Pricing",
    "answer": "B: Promotion",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jean, Keisha, and Kyle want to start their own business but are concerned about the higher tax r ate for corporations as well as the double taxation on corporate profits and dividends paid to stockholder s. What type of business ownership should they consider?",
    "A": "\"S\" corporation",
    "B": "Partnership",
    "C": "Open corporation",
    "D": "Close corporation",
    "answer": "A: \"S\" corporation",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Jeremy develops his personal budget, he should categorize the money that he spends on food, clothing, and entertainment as?",
    "A": "relational outflows.",
    "B": "variable expenses.",
    "C": "fixed costs.",
    "D": "periodic investments.",
    "answer": "B: variable expenses.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following symbols placed before a word in a search-engine query field will exclude the word from the search:?",
    "A": "Number sign",
    "B": "Exclamation point",
    "C": "Minus sign",
    "D": "Quotation marks",
    "answer": "C: Minus sign",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Deciding how to transport goods is part of which operations activity?",
    "A": "Safety and security",
    "B": "Scheduling",
    "C": "Logistics",
    "D": "Maintenance and repairs",
    "answer": "C: Logistics",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a group confronts a conflict, it is a good idea to?",
    "A": "remain judgmental. C. compromise on some points.",
    "B": "establish boundaries. D. apologize for disagreeing. 45. It is important for effective leaders to be positive role models because A. most people tend to take unnecessary risks. B. people often imitate the behavior of their leaders.",
    "C": "most people do not want to assume responsibility for their actions.",
    "D": "people do not want to learn from their own mistakes.",
    "answer": "B: establish boundaries. D. apologize for disagreeing. 45. It is important for effective leaders to be positive role models because A. most people tend to take unnecessary risks. B. people often imitate the behavior of their leaders.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of intellectual property:?",
    "A": "A business owner buys new computers for the office.",
    "B": "A manufacturing company hires a new human resources director.",
    "C": "A restaurant kitchen is stocked with food.",
    "D": "An inventor obtains a patent for a new product.",
    "answer": "D: An inventor obtains a patent for a new product.",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Financial planning is important because it can help you",
    "A": "meet needs and wants.",
    "B": "understand economics and finance.",
    "C": "predict the future.",
    "D": "increase your income.",
    "answer": "A: meet needs and wants.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements regarding the chain of command is true:?",
    "A": "Chains of command are only useful for retail businesses.",
    "B": "Most employees dislike working within a chain of command.",
    "C": "Businesses of all shapes, sizes, and industries have chains of command.",
    "D": "Chains of command are rarely used by modern companies.",
    "answer": "C: Businesses of all shapes, sizes, and industries have chains of command.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why should a business inform employees that their email will be monitored?",
    "A": "To reduce its liability",
    "B": "To communicate policies",
    "C": "To respect their privacy",
    "D": "To control operating costs",
    "answer": "C: To respect their privacy",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Most businesses stress to their sales force that the most important person is the",
    "A": "supervisor.",
    "B": "wholesaler.",
    "C": "manager.",
    "D": "customer.",
    "answer": "D: customer.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is necessary to the actual production of goods and services:?",
    "A": "Consumers",
    "B": "Capital resources",
    "C": "Utility",
    "D": "Fiscal control",
    "answer": "B: Capital resources",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because her employer requests that employees refrain from engaging in distracting acti vities and noise in the workplace, Alicia turns off her smartphone's ringer when she arrives at work each day. Alic ia is",
    "A": "performing her work efficiently.",
    "B": "respecting her coworkers' privacy.",
    "C": "following a company policy.",
    "D": "exhibiting a positive attitude.",
    "answer": "C: following a company policy.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Joseph received an email message from his supervisor and wants to send it to his coworker, Jackie. What email function key would Joseph use to send the message to Jackie?",
    "A": "Edit",
    "B": "New",
    "C": "Reply",
    "D": "Forward",
    "answer": "D: Forward",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How are entrepreneurs similar?",
    "A": "They have strong personal traits, such as determination and confidence.",
    "B": "They are born with excellent leadership and communication skills.",
    "C": "Most entrepreneurs go on to start other businesses.",
    "D": "Startup business owners rarely fail at their entrepreneurial ventures.",
    "answer": "A: They have strong personal traits, such as determination and confidence.",
    "topic": "Entrepreneurship"
  },
  {
    "Question": "During a meeting, Kevin provided an idea for cutting departmental costs by 20 percent. Which a ction would indicate that Kevin's supervisor liked his idea?",
    "A": "Rolling his/her eyes while sarcastically stating, \"Great idea, Kevin\"",
    "B": "Nodding, smiling, and writing down the idea",
    "C": "Making eye contact, frowning, and crossing his/her arms",
    "D": "Cutting Kevin off while he's speaking and asking for more ideas",
    "answer": "B: Nodding, smiling, and writing down the idea",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Ava is proud of her culture, but she doesn't assume that other cultures are inferior to hers. She avoids showing",
    "A": "subcultures.",
    "B": "globalization.",
    "C": "ethnocentrism.",
    "D": "cultural sensitivity.",
    "answer": "C: ethnocentrism.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To use various software programs, a computer must have a(n)",
    "A": "Internet connection.",
    "B": "operating system.",
    "C": "search-engine mechanism.",
    "D": "task toolbar.",
    "answer": "B: operating system.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way to protect yourself against identity theft is to",
    "A": "limit the number of credit cards you have.",
    "B": "give out your bank account number by phone.",
    "C": "open every email you have been sent.",
    "D": "carry your passport and birth certificate with you.",
    "answer": "A: limit the number of credit cards you have.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determine whether the following statement is true or false: \"As the United States grew and expanded, government's role in business grew as well.\"?",
    "A": "False, government involvement increased as the government grew.",
    "B": "True, as businesses grew, the country grew, and the government had to grow to keep up.",
    "C": "False, the growth of businesses and their activities forced the government to get more involved.",
    "D": "True, as the country grew, there were more businesses, and the government had to increase its involvement",
    "answer": "D: True, as the country grew, there were more businesses, and the government had to increase its involvement",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is often the best way for a salesperson to handle the slow/methodical type of difficult\ncustomer:?",
    "A": "Summarize benefits",
    "B": "Be brief",
    "C": "Let the customer do the talking",
    "D": "Ask their advice",
    "answer": "A: Summarize benefits",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements is true about determining your personal vision for the future:?",
    "A": "It depends more on emotion than logic.",
    "B": "It is risk free and time bound.",
    "C": "It involves following a step-by-step plan.",
    "D": "It requires facts and concrete goals.",
    "answer": "A: It depends more on emotion than logic.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way to effectively contribute to a group discussion when you don't know much about the topic bei ng\ndiscussed is to",
    "A": "ask questions to clarify what someone else is saying.",
    "B": "let the more informed group members handle the conversation.",
    "C": "quickly form an opinion to share with the group.",
    "D": "bring up a different topic that you know more about.",
    "answer": "A: ask questions to clarify what someone else is saying.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a primary characteristic of individuals with a high tolerance for ambiguity:?",
    "A": "Detail-oriented",
    "B": "Optimistic",
    "C": "Emotional",
    "D": "Routine-oriented",
    "answer": "B: Optimistic",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important to avoid considering prejudice and bias when judging others?",
    "A": "To improve negotiation",
    "B": "To be fair and equitable",
    "C": "To be persuasive",
    "D": "To communicate effectively",
    "answer": "B: To be fair and equitable",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As Kevin edits a professional report, he is not sure whether to italicize or underscore a book title. T o obtain the correct information, Kevin should",
    "A": "identify the readers' preferences.",
    "B": "seek a coworker's opinion.",
    "C": "look up the information in a current dictionary.",
    "D": "refer to the appropriate publisher's style manual.",
    "answer": "D: refer to the appropriate publisher's style manual.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After Courtney finds a man's missing order that he was inquiring about, she lets him know it will arrive later that afternoon. He seems to be pleased, so Courtney knows she did the right thing. Which step of problem-solving does this situation illustrate?",
    "A": "Define the problem",
    "B": "Determine possible solutions",
    "C": "State and check your assumptions",
    "D": "Evaluate the solution",
    "answer": "D: Evaluate the solution",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a safety procedure that businesses use to track employees who must evacu ate a building during an emergency:?",
    "A": "Training an employee to perform CPR if others are injured",
    "B": "Assigning an employee to change the smoke-alarm batteries",
    "C": "Requiring employees to call managers when they arrive home",
    "D": "Designating a central meeting place for all employees",
    "answer": "D: Designating a central meeting place for all employees",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first step to monitoring projects?",
    "A": "Gathering data using appropriate tools",
    "B": "Making changes and corrections",
    "C": "Deciding what to monitor and who will monitor it",
    "D": "Communicating changes to stakeholders",
    "answer": "C: Deciding what to monitor and who will monitor it",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As employees go about their daily activities, their actions should be driven by whether the actions will",
    "A": "be witnessed by customers.",
    "B": "result in additional sales.",
    "C": "bring them personal fulfillment.",
    "D": "result in customer satisfaction.",
    "answer": "D: result in customer satisfaction.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the safest and most responsible ways to determine whether an expensive item you're interested in is worth the money is by",
    "A": "buying the item to see for yourself. C. contacting the company.",
    "B": "reading verified customer reviews. D. searching for other advertisements. 62. Which of the following is often considered one of the safest types of investments: A. Commodities",
    "C": "Government bonds B. Penny stocks",
    "D": "Precious metals",
    "answer": "B: reading verified customer reviews. D. searching for other advertisements. 62. Which of the following is often considered one of the safest types of investments: A. Commodities",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Apex Company is a large, growing company with finance, accounting, operations, and sales departments. The company needs additional outside funding to pay for new buildings and equipment. What business department is responsible for ensuring the monies are available when needed?",
    "A": "Sales C. Operations",
    "B": "Accounting D. Finance 67. Which of the following is a compliance issue: A. Performance management",
    "C": "Car-pool organization B. Conflict mediation",
    "D": "Minimum wage",
    "answer": "D: Minimum wage",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Claire receives a lot of email messages every day. One client has sent her a message requesti ng some information that won't be available to Claire until next week. What can Claire do to remind hers elf to send the client the information when it is available?",
    "A": "Forward the message to her supervisor",
    "B": "Flag the message for follow-up",
    "C": "Place the client's name in her address book",
    "D": "Move the message to her spam folder",
    "answer": "B: Flag the message for follow-up",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When shopping for an investment broker, which of the following things should you always do:?",
    "A": "Disclose how much money you have to invest.",
    "B": "Choose the same broker as your parents.",
    "C": "Run a background check.",
    "D": "Read the broker's advertisements.",
    "answer": "C: Run a background check.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Major Company decided to use a loss-prevention technique that would monitor employee activity in the\nbusiness to detect theft as it takes place. What type of security device should Major Company implement?",
    "A": "Closed-circuit television",
    "B": "Undercover shoppers",
    "C": "Electronic sensors",
    "D": "Convex, one-way, and two-way mirrors",
    "answer": "A: Closed-circuit television",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The preparation of income statements and balance sheets is usually the responsibility of the business's\n__________ department.",
    "A": "marketing",
    "B": "accounting",
    "C": "purchasing",
    "D": "human resources",
    "answer": "B: accounting",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To evaluate an Internet source, what aspect would you consider when assessing whether its informati on is clearly laid out so that it is easy to read?",
    "A": "Relevance",
    "B": "Presentation",
    "C": "Objectivity",
    "D": "Timeliness",
    "answer": "B: Presentation",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Goods and services that are purchased by producers for resale, to make other goods and services, and/or to use in operating a business are known as __________ goods and services.",
    "A": "convenience",
    "B": "shopping",
    "C": "specialty",
    "D": "industrial",
    "answer": "D: industrial",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Under which of the following circumstances is a cosigner held legally responsible for paying the b alance owed on a bank loan:",
    "A": "The borrower defaults on the loan.",
    "B": "The lender defaults on the loan.",
    "C": "The borrower's interest rate increases.",
    "D": "The lender's interest rate increases.",
    "answer": "A: The borrower defaults on the loan.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "\"To form my business, I used all of my savings and borrowed from the bank, and I' m personally liable for all of the debts.\" This is an example of which of the following forms of business ownership:",
    "A": "Sole proprietorship",
    "B": "Partnership",
    "C": "Corporation",
    "D": "Cooperative",
    "answer": "A: Sole proprietorship",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When checking a personal credit report for accuracy, you should?",
    "A": "report suspicious activity immediately.",
    "B": "request multiple credit reports per year from each credit agency.",
    "C": "ignore accounts you don't remember opening.",
    "D": "only ask for a credit report from one of the major credit agencies.",
    "answer": "A: report suspicious activity immediately.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can an individual employee help protect company information on a daily basis?",
    "A": "Check personal email on a work computer",
    "B": "Log out of their computer when leaving work",
    "C": "Transfer files from a home computer to a work computer",
    "D": "Store log-in information in a desk drawer at work",
    "answer": "B: Log out of their computer when leaving work",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "For budgeting purposes, which of the following would be considered a long-term financial goal:",
    "A": "Buying a used car",
    "B": "Saving for retirement",
    "C": "Saving for an annual vacation",
    "D": "Creating an emergency fund",
    "answer": "B: Saving for retirement",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the most appropriate closing to include in a response to a customer's email inquiry for product\ninformation?",
    "A": "The model 2CR is available in three colors: red, black, and white. Reply by email with the color that yo u\nwant.",
    "B": "On behalf of LVN Industries, thank you for your order. Your confirmation number is 243597.",
    "C": "We apologize for the inconvenience and will send a corrected invoice to you within 24 hours.",
    "D": "Thank you for your interest in XWQ products. Please let me know if you have any additional questions.",
    "answer": "D: Thank you for your interest in XWQ products. Please let me know if you have any additional questions.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Technological advancements have made it possible for some entrepreneurs to",
    "A": "reduce the need for maintaining financial records.",
    "B": "run their businesses with fewer computer skills.",
    "C": "operate their businesses entirely from their computers.",
    "D": "eliminate the need to pay income and Social Security taxes.",
    "answer": "C: operate their businesses entirely from their computers.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Betty is hard working, but she often comes to work in clothes that are spotted or wrinkled. Which of the following is the most likely reason why Betty has never been promoted?",
    "A": "Job attitude C. Personal appearance",
    "B": "Lack of skill D. Interpersonal relationships Test 1232 BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CORE EXAM 9 91. Which of the following is a short-term goal: A. A salesperson wants to get five new clients this week. B. A student wants to earn a bachelor's degree.",
    "C": "A new employee wants to become president of the company.",
    "D": "A culinary student wants to open her own restaurant.",
    "answer": "C: A new employee wants to become president of the company.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Determine the assets of a business based on the following information: cash of $4,000, accounts receivable of $2,300, inventory of $8,460, equipment worth $3,500, and long-term debt of $12,850.",
    "A": "$18,260",
    "B": "$16,320",
    "C": "$5,410",
    "D": "$4,980",
    "answer": "A: $18,260",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a typical behavior for a person with a high achievement orientation:?",
    "A": "Impatience C. Ruthlessness",
    "B": "Persistence D. Irresponsibility 47. Which of the fol lowing people is more likely to challenge the status quo: A. A person who is benefiting from the current situation B. A person who views old ways as superior",
    "C": "A person who uses critical thinking to evaluate a situation",
    "D": "A person who always follows t he crowd",
    "answer": "B: Persistence D. Irresponsibility 47. Which of the fol lowing people is more likely to challenge the status quo: A. A person who is benefiting from the current situation B. A person who views old ways as superior",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "People who are treated fairly on the job are more likely to be",
    "A": "time wasters.",
    "B": "less productive.",
    "C": "satisfied workers.",
    "D": "absent more.",
    "answer": "C: satisfied workers.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the main purpose of writing a follow-up letter after a job interview?",
    "A": "To send a reference list",
    "B": "To thank the interviewer",
    "C": "To ask for the job",
    "D": "To forward a r\u00e9sum\u00e9",
    "answer": "B: To thank the interviewer",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The most positive words to use in selling are",
    "A": "brand names.",
    "B": "customers' names.",
    "C": "technical terms.",
    "D": "credit terms.",
    "answer": "B: customers' names.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a reason why someone might have trouble adapting to new circumstances:?",
    "A": "Objectivity",
    "B": "Empathy",
    "C": "Missed opportunities",
    "D": "Contentment",
    "answer": "D: Contentment",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an important consideration when selecting graphics and posting them on a business's website?",
    "A": "Font size",
    "B": "Download time",
    "C": "Descriptive links",
    "D": "Log files",
    "answer": "B: Download time",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The office photocopier is jammed again! Fortunately, there is an instruction manual to guide you through t he\nprocess of removing the jammed paper. What is the best way to use the manual to clear the photocopier?",
    "A": "Read the entire manual in sequential order, and then perform all steps in reverse order to remove t he\njammed paper.",
    "B": "Read step one and then perform step one. Repeat this process in sequential order until all steps ar e\ncompleted and you have removed the paper.",
    "C": "Perform the first step, and then verify that you have performed it correctly in the manual. Repeat this\nprocess in sequential order until all steps are completed.",
    "D": "Briefly skim the manual in reverse order, and then follow the steps in sequential order to remove t he",
    "answer": "B: Read step one and then perform step one. Repeat this process in sequential order until all steps ar e\ncompleted and you have removed the paper.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Entry-level positions provide employees with",
    "A": "high salaries.",
    "B": "basic job experience.",
    "C": "few advancement opportunities.",
    "D": "limited training.",
    "answer": "B: basic job experience.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one thing you can do to protect yourself from becoming a victim of identity thef t?",
    "A": "Use unusual passwords rather than your birth date to access your bank accounts.",
    "B": "Place your Social Security number or your social insurance number on all documents.",
    "C": "Keep your passport with you at all times.",
    "D": "Always pay with cash rather than credit cards or check.",
    "answer": "A: Use unusual passwords rather than your birth date to access your bank accounts.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To develop a professional-looking resume, the writer should",
    "A": "create interest by using colorful text. C. begin by describing their work history.",
    "B": "include a photograph of themselves. D. proofread the document for spelling errors. 98. Sally is interested in working with animals. In her free time, Sally goes to the local animal shelter to help feed, walk, and care for the stray dogs and cats. Sally is gaining experience in her field of interest by A. job shadowing a veterinarian.",
    "C": "doing volunteer work. B. participating in an internship.",
    "D": "organizing a charitable event.",
    "answer": "D: organizing a charitable event.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following restaurant assets would be considered intangible:?",
    "A": "The waiter's uniforms C. The building",
    "B": "An expensive oven D. A secret recipe 83. To establish weekly work priorities, employees should consider developing a list of A. routinely performed tasks.",
    "C": "short-term accomplishments. B. critical activities.",
    "D": "long-term goals.",
    "answer": "D: long-term goals.",
    "topic": "Strategic Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a benefit that businesses receive from using the internet:?",
    "A": "The ability to call employees on the road",
    "B": "Easier use of satellite radio",
    "C": "Improved methods of manufacturing",
    "D": "Faster connections with suppliers",
    "answer": "D: Faster connections with suppliers",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An American manufacturer launches a product line that offends many customers in Middle Eastern countries where the product line is considered inappropriate. This is an example of",
    "A": "product adaptation.",
    "B": "nationalization.",
    "C": "cultural imperialism.",
    "D": "globalization.",
    "answer": "C: cultural imperialism.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Who is responsible for verifying that all the information reported on a consumer's credit report ac curately reflects his/her personal transactions?",
    "A": "Organizations reporting consumer payments",
    "B": "Credit bureaus",
    "C": "Organizations that have extended credit",
    "D": "Consumers",
    "answer": "D: Consumers",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "GAAP is a system that provides accountants with",
    "A": "acceptable procedures.",
    "B": "professional development.",
    "C": "the newest technology.",
    "D": "networking opportunities.",
    "answer": "A: acceptable procedures.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Being able to feel what another person is feeling is known as",
    "A": "empathy.",
    "B": "perspective.",
    "C": "jealousy.",
    "D": "suspicion.",
    "answer": "A: empathy.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following computer functions enables a computer user to bring the text and the graphics from documents and spreadsheets created in other software programs into a presentation software program:?",
    "A": "Caption",
    "B": "Import",
    "C": "Style",
    "D": "Draw",
    "answer": "B: Import",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Matt works in customer service and often has to deal with customer inquiries. Which of the foll owing should he do if he wants to respond in an appropriate way:",
    "A": "Act disinterested while the customer is asking a question.",
    "B": "Answer the question immediately, even if he doesn't know the answer for sure.",
    "C": "Pay close attention to the question and ask for clarification, if needed.",
    "D": "Spend as much time talking to and answering the customer as possible.",
    "answer": "C: Pay close attention to the question and ask for clarification, if needed.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important to select an occupation that matches your aptitudes?",
    "A": "Selecting a career based on your aptitudes will require less time in college.",
    "B": "Matching aptit udes to careers leads to the highest possible income.",
    "C": "A positive aptitude will allow you to succeed in any career.",
    "D": "Considering your aptitudes will make achieving your career goals realistic.",
    "answer": "D: Considering your aptitudes will make achieving your career goals realistic.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a tool that often helps individuals organize and manage their mortgage, ut ility, and insurance bills:?",
    "A": "Credit report",
    "B": "Scatter chart",
    "C": "Daily work calendar",
    "D": "Monthly payment schedule",
    "answer": "D: Monthly payment schedule",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Because front desk clerks give out information to callers, it is very important for them to have",
    "A": "good body-language skills.",
    "B": "a professional appearance.",
    "C": "excellent verbal skills.",
    "D": "a wide range of experience.",
    "answer": "C: excellent verbal skills.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Jake pays his bills, he must write a check or provide his credit card number on the bil ls, which he then places in envelopes to mail. To protect himself from identity theft, he should?",
    "A": "put the envelopes in his mailbox for pick up.",
    "B": "take the envelopes to the post office.",
    "C": "make sure that he includes his address on the envelope.",
    "D": "verify that his billing information is correct.",
    "answer": "B: take the envelopes to the post office.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What must Preston Enterprises pay to the insurance company to maintain its business liabi lity insurance?",
    "A": "Stipend",
    "B": "Commission",
    "C": "Fine",
    "D": "Premiums",
    "answer": "D: Premiums",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To complete a report about commercial loans, Lola needs to review a specific online article called, \"The Truth About Commercial Interest Rate Increases.\" Which of the following search entries will provi de Lola the most accurate results:",
    "A": "[-the-truth-about-commerci al-interest-rate-increases]",
    "B": "{truth_ commercial interest rate_ increases}",
    "C": "\"the truth about commercial interest rate increases\"",
    "D": "\"{-the_truth_about_commercial_interest_rate_increases-}\"",
    "answer": "C: \"the truth about commercial interest rate increases\"",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Being exposed to conflicting viewpoints can help you",
    "A": "earn more money at work.",
    "B": "improve your social standing.",
    "C": "decrease your workload.",
    "D": "broaden your horizons.",
    "answer": "D: broaden your horizons.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What do you need to know to differentiate between consumer and industrial goods or services?",
    "A": "Who bought the product?",
    "B": "Who sold the product and at what price?",
    "C": "Who produced the product?",
    "D": "Who bought the product and for what purpose?",
    "answer": "D: Who bought the product and for what purpose?",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about listening skills while handlin g telephone calls:?",
    "A": "If you listen very carefully, you will not have to ask questions.",
    "B": "It is easy to listen while carrying on other activities.",
    "C": "Listening is a natural skill that doesn't require practice.",
    "D": "Being a good listener requires active-listening skills.",
    "answer": "D: Being a good listener requires active-listening skills.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a payroll deduction:?",
    "A": "Pay rate C. Net pay",
    "B": "Overtime hours D. Health insurance Test 1232 BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CORE EXAM 6 59. The primary reason that people review their personal credit reports is to A. eliminate the risk of identity theft. B. change or update their credit ratings.",
    "C": "ensure that they obtain bank loans.",
    "D": "verify that the credit agencies have correct information.",
    "answer": "D: verify that the credit agencies have correct information.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a tool that people use when participating in discussions:?",
    "A": "Building on someone else's comment",
    "B": "Avoiding asking questions",
    "C": "Sharing rumors",
    "D": "Hiding new ideas",
    "answer": "A: Building on someone else's comment",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Lodging facilities install Internet firewalls to protect their confidential inform ation from",
    "A": "web rings.",
    "B": "binary users.",
    "C": "frugging activities.",
    "D": "computer hackers.",
    "answer": "D: computer hackers.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an effective way to respond to constructive criticism:?",
    "A": "Treating the criticism as simply a misunderstanding",
    "B": "Joking and attempting to find common ground with your supervisor",
    "C": "Making eye contact and asking clarifying questions",
    "D": "Asking for detailed examples and blaming your coworker",
    "answer": "C: Making eye contact and asking clarifying questions",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "\"I'd like to have that in writing before I give you my money,\" best describes the __________ customer.",
    "A": "slow/methodical",
    "B": "dishonest",
    "C": "disagreeable",
    "D": "suspicious",
    "answer": "D: suspicious",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following statements regarding problems is accurate:?",
    "A": "You should seek assistance to solve all problems.",
    "B": "You should plan for every problem in advance.",
    "C": "Problems come in all shapes and sizes.",
    "D": "Problems are situations where things are going your way.",
    "answer": "C: Problems come in all shapes and sizes.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Paul prepared a job resume that addressed how his background and qualifications would meet the specific\nrequirements of the job he wanted. Paul's resume is an example of a __________ resume.",
    "A": "generalized",
    "B": "chronological",
    "C": "targeted",
    "D": "traditional",
    "answer": "C: targeted",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An employee accidentally quoted the wrong price to an important customer. How should the employee deal with this problem?",
    "A": "Admit the mistake and quote the correct price",
    "B": "Tell the customer the typist made an error",
    "C": "Ask a coworker to accept responsibility",
    "D": "Say the manager provided inaccurate information",
    "answer": "A: Admit the mistake and quote the correct price",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Workplace safety is primarily the responsibility of",
    "A": "insurance companies.",
    "B": "business management.",
    "C": "employers and employees.",
    "D": "human resource departments.",
    "answer": "C: employers and employees.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a rule of good listening:?",
    "A": "Be thinking about what you will say next.",
    "B": "Eliminate background noise.",
    "C": "Listen with empathy.",
    "D": "Stand as close as possible to the speaker.",
    "answer": "C: Listen with empathy.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Susie is not happy with her job because her coworkers are always telling her she d oesn't do her share of the work. Susie's feelings are the result of",
    "A": "negative feedback.",
    "B": "consideration.",
    "C": "lack of skill.",
    "D": "cooperation.",
    "answer": "A: negative feedback.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a factor that prevents some private enterprise systems from being considered pure private enterprise systems:?",
    "A": "Lack of any government regulation C. Government quotas on production",
    "B": "Partial government ownership of business D. Limited amount of government control 8. When providing legitimate responses to inquiries, it is usually best to begin by A. giving a standard response.",
    "C": "making assumptions. B. providing an appropriate answer.",
    "D": "being sympathetic.",
    "answer": "D: being sympathetic.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following responses to a difficult situation would damage your professional image:?",
    "A": "Listening without interrupting C. Showing empathy toward others",
    "B": "Using inappropriate language D. Controlling your facial expression 41. Which of the following comments by a supervisor is an example of destructive criticism: A. \"If you try to work when you have such a cold, you may give it to customers.\" B. \"Try both methods and decide which works better.\"",
    "C": "\"I would prefer that you do the job this way.\"",
    "D": "\"You must be stupid if you don't know how to do that by now.\"",
    "answer": "B: Using inappropriate language D. Controlling your facial expression 41. Which of the following comments by a supervisor is an example of destructive criticism: A. \"If you try to work when you have such a cold, you may give it to customers.\" B. \"Try both methods and decide which works better.\"",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "To reduce the risk of injury in the workplace, the government requires businesses to follow",
    "A": "organizational health policies.",
    "B": "privacy laws.",
    "C": "conservation ordinances.",
    "D": "safety regulations.",
    "answer": "D: safety regulations.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement about emotional intelligence:?",
    "A": "Emotional intel ligence means ignoring your emotions.",
    "B": "Emotional intelligence can be defined in different ways.",
    "C": "Emotional intelligence means being an emotional person.",
    "D": "Emotional intelligence is less important than traditional intelligence.",
    "answer": "B: Emotional intelligence can be defined in different ways.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Selling shares in the company to raise money for a new venture is referred to as __________ funding.",
    "A": "equity",
    "B": "dividend",
    "C": "accounts payable",
    "D": "debt",
    "answer": "A: equity",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a production activity that helps businesses decide how much to produce?",
    "A": "Budgeting C. Forecasting",
    "B": "Scheduling D. Transforming Test 1251 BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CORE EXAM 9 88. A soft drink manufacturer needs to keep the right number of sodas on hand to satisfy customer demand without producing excess product that will go unused. This is an example of which aspect of supply chain management? A. Customer service",
    "C": "Cost management B. Inventory management",
    "D": "Logistics management",
    "answer": "C: Cost management B. Inventory management",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Written communication is less effective when readers must",
    "A": "work to understand what the communication means.",
    "B": "find the information they need within the communication.",
    "C": "follow the writer's logical train of thought.",
    "D": "spend a minimum amount of time reading the communication.",
    "answer": "A: work to understand what the communication means.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Due to obsolescence, the format in which a business stores its information must often be",
    "A": "archived.",
    "B": "summarized.",
    "C": "processed.",
    "D": "updated.",
    "answer": "D: updated.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hazel is organizing her company's unpaid invoices. She orders them by date, starting with the earliest unpaid invoice and ending with the most recent. Hazel is organizing the invoices",
    "A": "chronologically.",
    "B": "by order of importance.",
    "C": "geographically.",
    "D": "deductively.",
    "answer": "A: chronologically.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Giving yourself a pat on the back and a \"good job\" when you know you've done well is an example of",
    "A": "pessimism.",
    "B": "positive self-talk.",
    "C": "thought stopping.",
    "D": "flexibility.",
    "answer": "B: positive self-talk.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a goal that takes priority over other activities:?",
    "A": "Performance goal",
    "B": "Effective goal",
    "C": "Learning goal",
    "D": "SMART goal",
    "answer": "B: Effective goal",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "An employee who is able to adjust to changing conditions possesses the desirable trait of",
    "A": "loyalty.",
    "B": "adaptability.",
    "C": "friendliness.",
    "D": "tact.",
    "answer": "B: adaptability.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Matt is balancing his checkbook for the first time. He compares the checks he has written over the last month with those listed on his statement and finds that all of his checks have cleared. Next, h e verifies that his latest paycheck, which he deposited the previous day, is on the list. It is not, s o he adds it to his statement balance. After this, he should",
    "A": "call the bank for a new statement.",
    "B": "subtract any interest.",
    "C": "subtract fees and charges.",
    "D": "consider everything done.",
    "answer": "C: subtract fees and charges.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "After Mrs. Green provided the cashier with $2.50 in cash and coins, she left the grocery store with a gallon of milk. In this situation, money is being used as a",
    "A": "bartering mechanism.",
    "B": "store of wealth.",
    "C": "negotiating tool.",
    "D": "medium of exchange.",
    "answer": "D: medium of exchange.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Operations managers must work closely with managers and employees in",
    "A": "all other parts of the business.",
    "B": "the marketing department only.",
    "C": "competing businesses.",
    "D": "foreign markets.",
    "answer": "A: all other parts of the business.",
    "topic": "Marketing"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Before sending a professional email message to a business associate, a businessperson s hould",
    "A": "make sure that the message is typed in capital letters.",
    "B": "code the message's importance as \"high priority.\"",
    "C": "proofread the message for spelling and grammatical errors.",
    "D": "insert a vague statement in the message subject line.",
    "answer": "C: proofread the message for spelling and grammatical errors.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jasmine needs to hold a staff meeting in the conference room at the same time that Jason needs th e\nconference room to meet with a new client. The reason for conflict in this situation is",
    "A": "unclear boundaries.",
    "B": "limited resources.",
    "C": "inconsistent behavior.",
    "D": "desire for authority.",
    "answer": "B: limited resources.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When customers complain, what is the general rule that business personnel follow in order to assure that customers receive fair and consistent treatment?",
    "A": "Store policy C. Customer service plan",
    "B": "Store procedure D. Customer complaint plan 21. A company consistently fulfills its brand promise by using A. external publicity.",
    "C": "product-line extensions. B. touchpoints.",
    "D": "tangible services.",
    "answer": "A: Store policy C. Customer service plan",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Compared to businesses in the manufacturing or medical industry, a retail business typically has greater need for __________ because it resells finished products.",
    "A": "safety and security",
    "B": "scheduling",
    "C": "routing",
    "D": "inventory control",
    "answer": "D: inventory control",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When a company experiences a change in human resources management, it will also experience a change in?",
    "A": "financial analysis.",
    "B": "market share.",
    "C": "profits.",
    "D": "name.",
    "answer": "A: financial analysis.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of a limited decision:?",
    "A": "Brushing your teeth",
    "B": "Buying a jacket",
    "C": "Ordering lunch",
    "D": "Getting married",
    "answer": "B: Buying a jacket",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following situations may represent a risk to the business:?",
    "A": "A regular customer brings a new neighbor to shop at the business.",
    "B": "A new customer's check is for an amount larger than the purchase total.",
    "C": "A new customer with a check provides a piece of photo identification.",
    "D": "A regular customer is impatient when the cashier takes a phone order.",
    "answer": "B: A new customer's check is for an amount larger than the purchase total.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One of the reasons that organized workers are more efficient than disorganized workers is that organized workers have",
    "A": "their materials in order.",
    "B": "more experience.",
    "C": "better skills.",
    "D": "their careers well planned.",
    "answer": "A: their materials in order.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Developing a personal budget is an effective way to",
    "A": "pay bills. C. calcula te assets.",
    "B": "manage money. D. increase debt. 57. For a school project, Megan needs to calculate her net worth. Using the following information, help Megan determine her net worth. Car value = $6,000 Savings account = $250 Credit card debt = $500 Computer value = $100 A. $5,850",
    "C": "$5,650 B.-$5,850",
    "D": "$5,150",
    "answer": "B: manage money. D. increase debt. 57. For a school project, Megan needs to calculate her net worth. Using the following information, help Megan determine her net worth. Car value = $6,000 Savings account = $250 Credit card debt = $500 Computer value = $100 A. $5,850",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Associations with colors are cultural issues that are most important for",
    "A": "travelers.",
    "B": "families.",
    "C": "businesses.",
    "D": "individuals.",
    "answer": "C: businesses.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following activities are part of the revision step of professional writing:?",
    "A": "Outlining, writing, and proofreading",
    "B": "Analyzing, prewriting, and summarizing",
    "C": "Brainstorming, outlining, and drafting",
    "D": "Rereading, rearranging, and removing",
    "answer": "D: Rereading, rearranging, and removing",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Where are a company's protocols, policies, and procedures most likely to be found?",
    "A": "Posted in the company cafeteria C. They usually aren't written down.",
    "B": "On the company's public website D. In a company handbook 100. When navigated properly, your company's chain of command can A. guide you toward better financial health.",
    "C": "be your personal map for career success. B. reveal to you your hidden talents.",
    "D": "help you discern your true purpose in life.",
    "answer": "D: help you discern your true purpose in life.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Employees who value differences in the workplace are more satisfied and increas e the company's",
    "A": "benefits.",
    "B": "workforce.",
    "C": "productivity.",
    "D": "assets.",
    "answer": "C: productivity.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of information may be listed in the work experience section of a r\u00e9sum\u00e9 if the pe rson has had only a few paying jobs?",
    "A": "Personal references",
    "B": "Technical training",
    "C": "Career objectives",
    "D": "Volunteer positions",
    "answer": "D: Volunteer positions",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Building positive customer relations is one of the least expensive ways for a business to",
    "A": "compete with other businesses.",
    "B": "manufacture goods.",
    "C": "offer employee bonuses.",
    "D": "attract investors.",
    "answer": "A: compete with other businesses.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Laura has made a list of the things she most enjoys doing and the way she likes to spen d her time. This list will help Laura",
    "A": "increase her level of ability.",
    "B": "improve her study habits.",
    "C": "measure her work skills.",
    "D": "identify an appropriate career.",
    "answer": "D: identify an appropriate career.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an example of an informational message geared toward an external audience:?",
    "A": "A print advertisement C. An inventory report",
    "B": "An employee handbook D. An office calendar 15. When posting to social media, business employees should understand that A. social media posts do not have the same legal protection as private conversations. B. there is no need to keep their personal and business lives separate.",
    "C": "their personal messages have no effect on their employer.",
    "D": "employers using social media to make employment decisions are protected by law.",
    "answer": "A: A print advertisement C. An inventory report",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "In North America, what nonverbal cue often indicates defensiveness?",
    "A": "Crossed arms",
    "B": "Fingernail biting",
    "C": "Raised eyebrows",
    "D": "Hands behind head",
    "answer": "A: Crossed arms",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can a consumer find evidence of fraudulent credit accounts opened in his/her name?",
    "A": "Obtain his/her credit score from a credit bureau.",
    "B": "Review credit card statements for unauthorized activity.",
    "C": "Review credit reports for the creation of unauthorized credit accounts.",
    "D": "Contact his/her credit card company and ask if fraud has been detected.",
    "answer": "C: Review credit reports for the creation of unauthorized credit accounts.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tyrone is writing a research paper for his business class. What question should T yrone ask as he looks for valid sources?",
    "A": "Does this source provide relevant graphic aids?",
    "B": "Is this material interesting and easy to read?",
    "C": "Is the information in this source up to date?",
    "D": "Do I agree with the viewpoint of this author?",
    "answer": "C: Is the information in this source up to date?",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is a primary consideration when evaluating the time value of money?",
    "A": "Credit limit",
    "B": "Premiums",
    "C": "Interest rate",
    "D": "Tariffs",
    "answer": "C: Interest rate",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "One way that employees can help prevent accidents is by practicing",
    "A": "emergency methods.",
    "B": "first-aid techniques.",
    "C": "good health habits.",
    "D": "security procedures.",
    "answer": "C: good health habits.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding ethical behavior:?",
    "A": "Ethical behavior always leads to increased profits.",
    "B": "If you see the importance of ethics, you will never make mistakes.",
    "C": "Ethical behavior is not difficult to implement.",
    "D": "Sometimes even ethical people are tempted to act unethically.",
    "answer": "D: Sometimes even ethical people are tempted to act unethically.",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is a computer-software technology that helps a business automate an d track its sales, marketing, and service efforts:?",
    "A": "Automated Clearinghouse (ACH)",
    "B": "Materials requirements planning (MRP)",
    "C": "Computer-aided engineering (CAE)",
    "D": "Customer relationship management (CRM)",
    "answer": "D: Customer relationship management (CRM)",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Sometimes, the ability to follow directions is a skill that is necessary for survival. This is known as a(n)\n__________ skill.",
    "A": "academic",
    "B": "social",
    "C": "life",
    "D": "cultural",
    "answer": "C: life",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an indicator that your project is a success:?",
    "A": "It is temporary.",
    "B": "The team is challenged by the work.",
    "C": "It offers financial value.",
    "D": "It comes in under budget.",
    "answer": "C: It offers financial value.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Blue Shark Company needs a way to allow employees to share messages and files securely. They shoul d\ncreate a(n)",
    "A": "intranet.",
    "B": "Facebook page.",
    "C": "public website.",
    "D": "internet.",
    "answer": "A: intranet.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following types of computer software programs usually contain a thesaurus:?",
    "A": "Communications",
    "B": "Graphics and design",
    "C": "Presentation",
    "D": "Word processing",
    "answer": "D: Word processing",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Often, the most effective way to interpret others' nonverbal cues is to look at their",
    "A": "clothing style.",
    "B": "leg movements.",
    "C": "facial expressions.",
    "D": "office decor.",
    "answer": "C: facial expressions.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "As employees go about their daily activities, their actions should be driven by whe ther the actions will",
    "A": "result in additional sales.",
    "B": "result in customer satisfaction.",
    "C": "bring them personal fulfillment.",
    "D": "be witnessed by customers.",
    "answer": "B: result in customer satisfaction.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Your friend tells you that reading books is more fun than watching TV. This is a(n)",
    "A": "opinion.",
    "B": "criticism.",
    "C": "fact.",
    "D": "statistic.",
    "answer": "A: opinion.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Jackie is starting a T-shirt business. When should Jackie read the instructions for the heat press, vinyl cutter, and printer that he'll be using to create his products?",
    "A": "When any of the equipment malfunctions",
    "B": "Before using the equipment for the first time",
    "C": "Never; he can figure out the equipment on his own.",
    "D": "When he hires his f irst employee",
    "answer": "B: Before using the equipment for the first time",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Chris is at the grocery store deciding between two very similar candy bars. One is $1.50, and the other is $3.00. He decides to buy the $1.50 candy bar because it is cheaper. Chris is using money as a ____________ to make his decision.",
    "A": "store of value",
    "B": "medium of exchange",
    "C": "unit of measure",
    "D": "commodity",
    "answer": "C: unit of measure",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Marlon buys a new oven for his bakery, he receives a three-year warranty from the oven company. If the oven breaks or has any problems within three ye ars, the company promises to repair or replace it free of charge. This is an example of __________ business risk.?",
    "A": "transferring C. preventing/controlling",
    "B": "avoiding D. retaining 29. Which of the following is true of emotional intelligence: A. It helps you manage your emotions.",
    "C": "It's also known as \"book smarts.\" B. It means you're an emotional person.",
    "D": "It's not a good predictor of future success.",
    "answer": "A: transferring C. preventing/controlling",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Leslie and her siblings have been fighting over household chores. Leslie points out that the conflict exists\nbecause their parents haven't made specific chore assignments. Which step of problem-solving does this\nsituation illustrate?",
    "A": "State and check your assumptions",
    "B": "Evaluate the solution",
    "C": "Define the problem",
    "D": "Collect information",
    "answer": "C: Define the problem",
    "topic": "Emotional Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is one of the identifying characteristics of private enterprise?",
    "A": "Freedom in the marketplace",
    "B": "Little competition",
    "C": "Unlimited government control",
    "D": "Equality in income",
    "answer": "A: Freedom in the marketplace",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Selling goods and services to customers in their homes is an example of",
    "A": "wholesaling.",
    "B": "retailing.",
    "C": "discounting.",
    "D": "producing.",
    "answer": "B: retailing.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When Matthew receives a check four times a year for income he has earned on his stock investments, he is receiving?",
    "A": "credit.",
    "B": "dividends.",
    "C": "cash.",
    "D": "deposits.",
    "answer": "B: dividends.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Expressing empathy and being willing to help others are the aspects of emotional intell igence that relate to",
    "A": "self-management.",
    "B": "social awareness.",
    "C": "relationship managemen t.",
    "D": "self-awareness.",
    "answer": "B: social awareness.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Melissa recently spoke to her friend James about a personal problem James was experiencing. Later on, when hanging out with another group of friends, Melissa accidentally revealed some of the private information that James shared with her. When James learned that Melissa had told other people about his problem, he was furious-and Melissa felt terrible. This is an example o f the importance of",
    "A": "fairness.",
    "B": "confidentiality.",
    "C": "privacy.",
    "D": "secrecy.",
    "answer": "B: confidentiality.",
    "topic": "Information Management"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following is an additional duty for which a business's buyers may be responsible:?",
    "A": "Organizing inventory counts",
    "B": "Placing advertisements",
    "C": "Designing visual displays",
    "D": "Managing sales personnel",
    "answer": "D: Managing sales personnel",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Information that a business keeps in its accounting records includes its",
    "A": "goods and services.",
    "B": "revenues and expenses.",
    "C": "trends and forecasts.",
    "D": "market share and profit.",
    "answer": "B: revenues and expenses.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Workers who enjoy close supervision and specific instructions will feel most c omfortable working under a(n) __________ leader.",
    "A": "republican",
    "B": "authoritarian",
    "C": "democratic",
    "D": "laissez-faire",
    "answer": "B: authoritarian",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is effective to follow a step-by-step order when applying written directions to",
    "A": "take notes.",
    "B": "give commands.",
    "C": "read materials.",
    "D": "achieve tasks.",
    "answer": "D: achieve tasks.",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How can you let people know that you are really thinking about what they are saying?",
    "A": "By using clich\u00e9s",
    "B": "By making jokes",
    "C": "By asking questions",
    "D": "By making comments",
    "answer": "C: By asking questions",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Workers should demonstrate honest behavior on and off the job because they will",
    "A": "be more likely to receive promotions.",
    "B": "show that they can be trusted.",
    "C": "probably earn more money.",
    "D": "be less likely to have problems.",
    "answer": "B: show that they can be trusted.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Qualified employees who behave unethically on the job may harm themselves by being",
    "A": "held legally responsible. C. passed over for promotions.",
    "B": "sent to a training program. D. rotated to similar positions. 34. When a person fails to take responsibility for decisions and actions, they will likely experience difficulty A. choosing a college.",
    "C": "creating goals. B. understanding math homework.",
    "D": "getting along with others.",
    "answer": "C: creating goals. B. understanding math homework.",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The formula that is generally used to measure productivity is",
    "A": "goods divided by time.",
    "B": "inputs divided by labor.",
    "C": "labor divided by resources.",
    "D": "outputs divided by inputs.",
    "answer": "D: outputs divided by inputs.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which of the following often makes it necessary for workers to continue their education and obtain training to pursue different careers:?",
    "A": "Changes in geography",
    "B": "Increases in responsibility",
    "C": "Advances in technology",
    "D": "Limits to confidentiality",
    "answer": "C: Advances in technology",
    "topic": "Human Resources"
  },
  {
    "Question": "The Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) is responsible for",
    "A": "insisting that businesses maintain safe, hazard-free workplaces.",
    "B": "complying with a business's safety rules.",
    "C": "reporting job-related injuries or illnesses to supervisors.",
    "D": "seeking medical attention for injured employees.",
    "answer": "A: insisting that businesses maintain safe, hazard-free workplaces.",
    "topic": "Operations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What type of law is based on past rulings and precedents set by the judicial system?",
    "A": "Civil law",
    "B": "Administrative law",
    "C": "Criminal law",
    "D": "Common law",
    "answer": "D: Common law",
    "topic": "Business Law"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why is it important to use the appropriate writing style when developing research reports?",
    "A": "Ensures the writer's objectivity",
    "B": "Enhances the writer's credibility",
    "C": "Allows the writer to express creativity",
    "D": "Reduces the need to edit the content",
    "answer": "B: Enhances the writer's credibility",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "When setting financial goals, it is important to make sure that they are realistic and?",
    "A": "specific.",
    "B": "general.",
    "C": "conservative.",
    "D": "durable.",
    "answer": "A: specific.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Using a credit card is",
    "A": "like getting a free loan if you pay the balance each month.",
    "B": "a good way to pay for impulsive purchases.",
    "C": "an inexpensive way to borrow money for an extended period.",
    "D": "a privilege reserved for working adults.",
    "answer": "A: like getting a free loan if you pay the balance each month.",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If a business wants to send a mailing to customers in specific geographic regions, it should s et the database query to sort its customer information by",
    "A": "name.",
    "B": "sales volume.",
    "C": "state.",
    "D": "street number.",
    "answer": "C: state.",
    "topic": "Customer Relations"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is an example of a written business inquiry?",
    "A": "A form describing an employee's performance review",
    "B": "A memo outlining an upcoming meeting agenda",
    "C": "An email requesting vendor pricing and discounts",
    "D": "A report summarizing annual financial information",
    "answer": "C: An email requesting vendor pricing and discounts",
    "topic": "Communication Skills"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which activities are likely to increase a firm's profit?",
    "A": "Increasing supplies and decreasing production",
    "B": "Increasing sales and decreasing expenses",
    "C": "Decreasing sales and increasing expenses",
    "D": "Decreasing supplies and increasing production",
    "answer": "B: Increasing sales and decreasing expenses",
    "topic": "Financial Analysis"
  },
  {
    "Question": "If the money supply is low and the demand for money is high, interest rates on loans will",
    "A": "increase, then decrease.",
    "B": "decrease.",
    "C": "stay about the same.",
    "D": "increase.",
    "answer": "D: increase.",
    "topic": "Economics"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Writing down your goals will help you",
    "A": "modify or cancel your goals.",
    "B": "distract yourself from your goals.",
    "C": "keep yourself on target.",
    "D": "choose your goals.",
    "answer": "C: keep yourself on target.",
    "topic": "Professional Development"
  }
]